[L] Hey [S] How you doing?
[L] Fine and you? [S] Doing, doing good, doing good
[S] Um I had a terrible, terrible experience a couple of weeks ago
[S] Um [L] What happened?
[S] Um you like to air travel? You like air travel? Yeah
[S] See, see you already feel me [L] Not so much
[S] Um so I was traveling
[S] I, I got this last minute deal in one of the websites
[S] And uh going to Brussels for the weekend [L] Hmm
[S] A couple of weekends ago um
[S] It was very cheap, so I took it, it was night
[S] I was already planning to go for a holiday for the weekend and this was a place, I hadn't seen it before [L] Okay
[S] So I took this flight um
[S] It was a night flight, pretty much I think the last flight of the night or something before they closed the airport [L] Okay
[S] Um so I reach the airport a couple of hours ago
[S] It was a bit raining and it was a bit storming, so I thought, I expected a bit of delay
[L] Uh-huh [S] So I reached a bit early, and I realized as soon as I reached the airport
[S] That I'm not gonna reach the boarding
[S] Cause the airport was full of people
[S] The check in queue was like this huge queue [L] Ah
[S] Uh apparently all the flights before this one were delayed because of the weather [L] Hmm
[S] So it was just jam packed
[S] Um somehow I lurch through things
[S] Through security and everything, I just barely manage to
[S] Reach the boarding gate before they closed it [L] Hmm
[S] Um I think it was uh five minutes left before I  and enter [L] Ah
[S] Uh and then I, I was able to board the plane um
[S] And uh you know these uh some of these flights don't have like the bridge to the, to the plane
[S] You have to go down and take the bus, and the bus goes.. I hate that [L] Yeah
[S] Um so they just fill you up in this bus
[S] And then you have to wait at the tarmac for some time [L] Of course, yeah
[S] So they took the bus onto the plane
[S] And uh what I see is actually this really small propeller plane
[S] Like the sixty, seventy seater or something [S] Oh
[S] Uh which I hate a lot
[S] Because I don't really trust the propeller planes that much, I have not had good experiences with it [L]  oh
[S] Uh so I.. normally I only take the bigger flights
[S] With the, with the jet planes so that uh in my head I'm not going crazy
[S] But I didn't have an option here because I didn't even see which plane it was, just got this deal and
[S] At that point of time I couldn't say  I'm not boarding anymore because I was like outside the plane [L] Hmm
[S] So we got in and they kind of rushed us in because they were getting late or something, so (they?)
[S] Pretty much were, were rude and just pushed us in
[S] And then they said yeah get seated as soon as possible and we're gonna start and
[S] Everything.. we sat down and um..
[S] The, the air staff was not very polite, I would say
[S] They were just.. pushing people around, just getting them seated so that they could start
[S] It's weird.. um probably it happens with cheap flights.. anyway [L]
[S] So ah as soon as we all ah sat in
[S] And then we were ready to fly, there was announcement saying that yeah but we cannot take off right now
[S] Because the air traffic control has told us that there's a bad weather
[S] And we can't really took, take off
[S] And can you imagine we stayed at the tarmac for one hour?
[S] Waiting for the plane to take off [L] Oh my
[S] Which is weird because earlier they were just pushing is in to start
[S] And now we had to sit there for an hour [L] Yeah
[S] And it was like.. you know they don't even switch on the air conditioning while it's on the.. tarmac
[S] Er just.. you couldn't breathe, it was just getting crampy, and just so bad
[S] Um after an hour we actually took off
[S] Um.. the took off was also not that great
[S] It was like this weird wind thing that happened
[S] And we reach this cruising altitude, er everything seemed to be fine
[S] And you know as soon as it reaches cruising, you remove your seat belt
[S] Or loosen it, and you wanna use the restroom or something [L] Yeah
[S] But they said we couldn't because there was a lot of turbulence
[S] We couldn't take off our seat belts, the lavatories were not allowed to be used, we couldn't go there
[S] And the plane was literally shaking left to right uh because of the turbulence [L] Oh
[S] And in my head all my worst dreams about
[S] Um propeller planes  that come into mind is not going, go, go well [L] Oh no
[S] And then all of the sudden, the lights go off
[S] And we see the lights flashing, the lightning outside
[S] And we see these lights flashing in.. the plane is
[S] Scene out of a horror movie or something
[S] And uh you, we experience this uh this sudden fall
[S] You see the, sometimes when the air turbulence is the plane seems to be falling a lot, and getting up and falling [L] Yeah
[S] But this weird because it kept on falling for like seconds, like 10, 15 seconds we fell this fall [L] Oh
[S] And I'm pretty claustrophobic
[S] And I don't like that whole environment anyhow, and this is getting even worse for me [L] Nobody does
[S] Um.. and then to make matters even worse
[S] The oxygen masks drop.. um [L] Oh
[S] I couldn't breathe anyway.. and this is the first time I'm experiencing oxygen masks
[S] And I don't know how to use it, although they tell it every time, but it's very difficult when it happens to you [L] Uh-huh
[S] Somehow the guy sitting next to me helped me put it on, so I could breathe again
[S] But it was this harrowing experience, we all were scared
[S] The plane was going up and down and.. it was just.. the lights were off and
[S] I, we could see that the air staff was also pretty scared of what  was happening
[S] And after like, I think 20 minutes of this tough experience
[S] Going up and down, the plane kind of stabilized [L] Oh
[S] We were asked to remove our masks, the lights came on again
[S] Everybody was completely shaken um..
[S] The.. they were fighting with the air staff, you know?
[S] What, what has happened? Aren't they gonna do anything? But er.. [L] Yeah
[S] It was just weird, the whole experience
[S] And I think we were nearing our destination, so they started to descend
[S] Even the.. the landing was.. like worse
[S] We bumped onto the.. eh runway twice before we landed er.. [L] Oh
[S] I don't know what the hell was going on [L] Terrible
[S] It put me off from the air travel so much that  I canceled my flight back
[S] I didn't want to fly again.. er because I believe it was a similar flight [L]
[S] I took the train back from Brussels, I
[S] It took me long but well.. I was at least in my head safe [L] Yeah
[S] And I talk to myself, I'm never gonna take.. like a night flight again
[S] Especially when I know it's a small propeller plane
[S] Just put me off these propeller planes forever
[S] Er I don't think.. I'll be able to fly with these planes ever in my life [L] Okay
[S] Weird holiday, right? Was a weird, weird holiday [L] Yeah