[L] Hi
[S] How was your weekend?
[L] Yeah, it was awesome. Cool stuff huh.
[S] Yeah..I went to Norway to visit a friend..ah..in Tromso
[S] you know? Have you ever been there? Norway? Sweden? Scandinavian?
[L] No.
[S] Uh yeah. I went there. It was nice. You know it’s a bit cold in this period.
[S] But, i mean, it is kind of always cold there, but, it was really here  this guy..
[S] Um, so yeah Tromso is an interesting city. It’s kind of expensive, so..you know we just went out a couple of times to drink a beer, have dinner, but..
[S]  you know it’s not the kind of life that you can afford as a student
[L] Huh.
[S] Um, and then he you know had this thing with..he asked me if I had ever tried this..um..kind of..fish
[S] This really smelly fish which is supposed to be the smelliest food in the world. I think the name is something like Surstromming or something like that
[S] Herring, fermented with salt, which you know..it really smells disgusting, that’s what you say, but he told me that it actually tastes really good.
[S] So we just made a bet like if we were able to you know eat this thing. Um and we went to supermarket. We got it, it’s like you know a tuna can.
[S] But you’re not supposed to open that or eat that indoors because it really smells so you’re not encouraged to open that at home or whatever.
[S] So we have to go outdoors. It’s kind of small forest behind his place there and then we ah you know we just have to eat it.
[S] The thing is I hate fish in general so it doesn’t have to be smelly to be disgusting for me.
[L] Huh.
[S] You know, I kind of like salmon but not a lot. So..anyway I just didn’t want to lose the bet so we went for it.
[S] So we went for it and uh..these two cans..so the idea was that the guy finishing the..this thing..this fish first would win.
[S] And I don’t like losing so okay I just do it. And as soon as we you know..actually open this can it was such this strong smell, the smell is really disgusting..
[S] I was..something strange I mean I tried this smelly tofu thing in China which was really, really weird.
[S] But this was, man, such a strong fishy smell, something that could, really you know.  So I was almost crying because of the smell
[S] But now the worst parts..the worst part that..was that now I have to eat you know
[S] So, I also saw he was kind of really disgusted. So then I knew uh, man, you know this is not gonna taste good.
[S] There is no way this gonna taste good, you know. But I, well, we went for it. So, three, two, one, bam!
[S] I really just you know took a piece, tried to put it in my mouth, but I mean I was crying so I really have to you know like this  my nose
[S] and I started eating it  and it was probably the most disgusting thing I ever tried in my life.
[S] It’s not only smell, it was also the, the, the texture of the, you know, kind of this jello thing in your mouth and wow.
[S] But, and also that guys was..but he was eating fast, maybe I don’t know maybe, he is used to it or maybe he like fish.
[S] So then again I just you know closed my eyes, I went for it but I couldn’t finish it.
[L] No?
[S] I..you know, at that point it’s like when you..when you’re eating and you just..I’m not..just..no way I can finish this it was really disgusting.
[S] But it’s a nice story I can tell. We also took some pictures of each other while you know enjoying this.
[L] Or crying
[S] Yeah, great dish from Norway
[L] Yeah, sounds cool.