[S] Hey!
[L] Hi
[S] How are you?
[L] Good, and you?
[S] Yeah? Cool, cool, cool, cool..
[S] I was thinking.. remembering some stuff from the past these days and
[S] How was your high school? You liked it? High school time..
[S] Yeah, I had a great time in high school
[S] Yeah?
[L] Yeah
[S] Yeah, I had a great time in high school
[S] It was ok?
[L] Yeah
[S] Yeah
[S] Because I have.. Everyone I ask.. They.. They are always fifty fifty, others had a very good time and liked it, others were awful
[L] For some reason, right?
[S] For me.. I was in the awful side, I mean.. I moved..
[S] In the middle of high school, so in the second year of high school I moved from another school
[S] I was completely alone so.. everyone were grouped up together, studied in the same school and then I was the new guy, you know?
[L] Uh-huh
[S] I could not connect to anyone there it was strange..
[S] And..
[S] Together with that there is the whole structure of the school, the teachers.. they were really..
[S] This.. undidatic..
[S] Very authoritarian way to teach..
[S] I really could not connect to that, I really could not learning with that, so I was always Um..
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Average.. so I always did every think to pass
[S] But that's all, I never tried to be more than that, you know?
[L] Uh-huh
[S] And this was.. Yeah.. Following me through the whole year
[S] But then there is a time that.. Um..
[S]
[S] A new teacher arrived..
[S] Uh.. he was a history teacher
[S] And I never liked history, history was always like.. memorizing dates and memorizing.. Uh.. names and things ..
[L] Yeah.. Boring stuff
[S] Completely right? Yeah this is awful
[S] And I never liked history, history was always like.. memorizing dates and memorizing.. Uh.. names and things ..
[S] But then this guy arrived, and he was a very good guy, very.. Uh.. he was a younger guy
[S] Very dynamic teacher  very good didactic, trying to aggregate the students and.. to make something more funny..
[S] Than memorizing dates and names, right?
[S] Uh-huh
[S] And actually.. The.. the class of history, the history class became more funny
[S] I started to go  it.. and I'm.. ok it's actually nice and.. cool
[S] And then I did my Uh.. first exam
[S] And I failed..
[S] Oh
[S] Convenient I really failed and I was like, wow, that's not good
[S] And then I started to get bad, but then the teacher came and talked to me
[S] This was something new and he said, ya I see that you are there all the time..
[S] And you are paying attention, so what happen and then we started to talk and trying to..
[S]  what happen and.. He gave me some nice hints about study and..
[S] The most important he gave me a lot of motivation
[S] Of how to study, right? To like like he liked the class
[S] And.. Then..
[S] Couple time passed, and then I did the second exam, I failed again
[L]
[S] It's like, wow that's awful
[S] Wow that was really bad and then I started to feel really really bad
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Because it was the second time now.. shouldn't be like that
[L] Yeah
[S] Right
[S] And then I had only one more exam
[S] The final exam  pass it otherwise I would fail the class
[S] And then I said, Yeah, now I get a bit desperate
[S] Started to study like a crazy and tried to memorize like crazy a completely wrong stuff
[S] But one day before the exam I became very.. in panic
[S] So I was having a lot of panic attacks and really angry issues
[S] Afraid to fail completely the exam
[S] So what I did exactly, took some straps of paper, make some annotations and put those on my sleeve
[S] So, yeah, so that was my super dooper plan
[L] Oh..
[L] Uh-huh
[S] You know, er.. Yeah
[L] Smart plan
[L]
[S] Awful right
[S] Um.. on the day of the test
[S] I was doing the test and I was using my straps and it was actually working.. so I was passing
[S] Answering everything properly
[S] But by the ending of the test before I handing I started to feel so bad
[S] So.. So.. So.. I don't know, so unconnected with me so..
[S] Disgusted for what I were doing, I was doing you know..
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Wow, i'm breaking the trust with this guy
[S] Who really care about me and care about all
[S] I was going and with my self
[S] By going this kinda of things, right?
[L] Uh-huh
[S] I handed the test in the end, and I passed
[S] But it was such a bad, bad, bad feeling
[S] Since after it I've never did this anymore, I think I learned my lesson
[S] But it was a milestone on me was like ya
[S] I should be bad at that, I could not
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Really strong, strong feeling yeah..
[S] And this was maybe the best thing I could call from high school times
[L] I guess you learned
[L] I think I learned