[S] So then where were we before we were rudely interrupted
[S] Ah.. right I moved to Sweden my friend had moved away kind of thing
[S] Um but when I did move to Sweden I started to get more into kind of
[S]  I started really getting into music, I started listening to a lot of music
[S] And I also just felt that I really wanted to kind of be cool and play a musical instrument
[S] Or like at least do something with music like
[S] So I kind of pestered my parents for it, but they didn't really like
[S] They treated it more as a kind of a flight of fancy, so they they didn't really care that I was interested in music
[S] Essentially like they just said yeah you do whatever  makes you feel happy
[S] They didn't want to shell out for a big like guitar or anything so  that was unfortunate
[S] But er.. do you like music by the way?
[L] Depends on what kind of music yeah
[S]  That's.. a good answer  reasonable
[S]  Ah yeah but eventually I did, after nagging them for a particularly long period of time
[S] I did eventually convince them that they would send me to a music oriented high school kind of
[S] As long as the high school had like kind of additional like maths and sciences, the necessary stuff, so you could do music on the side kind of an extra thing
[S] So I was very happy about that ah.. and once I got there I really liked it, it was like a really great school, I had great fun there, I learnt a lot
[S] Ah.. there was one such that I really hated and that was classical music theory and it was mostly because of the teacher
[S] And I'm pretty sure she was some kind of evil demon in the shape of a human being or something
[S] She was pretty awful as a human being, she was mean and judgmental and  [L] Ah
[S] Almost a bit spiteful  I guess side effect of having to teach children all day
[S] I suppose  but yeah I really liked it there but that one class really made my life hell essentially, I couldn't, I had trou
[L] I did meet some frieds and actually what really brought us together was how much we hated this particular teacher
[S] Which is a bit weird when you think about it but um.. if it works I guess
[S] Um.. yeah so the thing was that happened was kind of especially like everything was going fine for a while
[S] But eventually we had to give this kind of big presentation on classical music theory and
[S] I was really stressing out before this happened kind of, I was worried about partially giving the presentation
[S] Like I'm a bit of an introvert as per se, so like presenting is a bit of a thing in itself [L] Hmm
[S] But then you have to present to this kind of hellion of a teacher essentially um
[S] And man I.. was scared of  scared of having to give that presentation ah..
[S] But I did, I really prepared I gave a presentation, I was nervous, I thought I'd done a really good job
[S] But wow she really.. cause everyone applauded and stuff, but then she just kind of
[S] Shredded my presentation, she said that this was wrong, you were so quiet about this, why didn't you do this better
[S] And I.. couldn't handle this kind of, I just kind of broke down, I went home to my parents crying
[S] Look I can't be here, I need to take this course but this one teacher like we can't deal with her essentially like she's too much
[S] So we talked to the school about it, and the school just told us like she's there to stay we can't get rid of her kind of
[S] She's there so you have to just kind of  deal with  so what we did do is we eventually arranged a transfer back over to like a normal high school
[S] Which shared a lot of courses with the musical school essentially, especially the technical subjects
[S] Um so then I could at least continue my schooling there so I could at least finish and graduate with a degree kind of
[S] So I did that and I finished and I eventually lost contact with these, with my friends I met there kind of
[S] What did happen though was later on when we well went to college kind of I eventually met up with these guys again
[S] Cause they'd also graduated as well from the school, finishing eventually, and they went to this one college
[S] And then we all met up and I was like  it was great to see them, I hadn't seen them again for so long
[S] And they'd also been playing in a band kind of so.. we were discussing and it's like
[S] Hey don't you want to join our band? I was like what? Like me? Yeah, it's like
[S]  kind of said eh, I'd love to
[S] Ah.. so then we did practice and together as a group and then eventually we played a concert and then it was great, it was like
[S] I felt so liberated, it's so weird kind of  cause i'd always been very reclusive as we mentioned
[S] So like the chance to really perform and like.. wow it was amazing, so yeah
[S] And it was a great experience, so yeah.. I got in a band and I was a vocalist so  it was a pretty great experience