[S] So where were we before we were interrupted, it's a really um, right
[S] So my friend left essentially um [L] Uh-huh
[S] And this can be pretty hard kind of, I was in a pretty, I was pretty lonely once again kind of
[S] Cause she was a very close friend of mine, everyone else was a bit more out there so it's like
[S] How long have you spent with her? 7 months? [L] .. about seven months, kind of
[S] So it took a while for me to kind of get over that
[S] I did actually start to look for some way to kind of cope with that essentially um
[S] So I started to look a lot into music kind of, and look a lot into kind of
[S] Perhaps going to play some instrument as to kind of vent in some sense essentially
[S] Were you doing that time, like studying the language?
[S] Ah.. studying the language and going to normal school, cause I, cause I spoke English
[S] I can go to normal school with the other kids basically, cause I just  spoke English [L] Uh-huh.. uh-huh
[S] So that was a good uh a good thing for me um..
[S] Yeah but.. basically so I started to look a lot into music kind of
[S] Very, you know, got into this you're going to be a musician essentially
[S] It just kind of, I don't know, it just felt like it would be a good idea
[S] I know I was a kid, I don't know what I was thinking but  [L] Yeah
[S] Uh so I nagged my parents a lot, like I want a guitar, or like I want a piano or something
[S] I tried to convince them about them, they weren't too into it [L] Uh-huh
[S] They just treated it like a phase that thought I would get over eventually kind of thing [L]
[S] I kept nagging them but they never really let up er..
[S] The closest I got to convincing them was that
[S] That when I was going to transfer between a (local?) middle school to like high school [L] Hmm
[S] They let me go to a kind of more music oriented high school
[S] If the high school actually gave like maths and science and like real courses
[S] Instead of just the weird music courses  [L] Uh-huh like a plan b
[S] Like a plan b exactly ah yeah [L]
[S] So they agreed to that, I kind of started at this school
[S] It was a very nice school, um it was a very
[S] Er I learned a lot while I was there, very nice campus
[S] The food was a bit better than here uh you know  [L]
[S] Ah it was a, it was a very, it was a very nice ah school in general
[S] I really enjoyed my time while I was there
[S] But we'll get to that, there's one course I had a problem with, one mandatory course
[S] And that course was called classical music theory [L] Hmm
[S] Uh and the issue I had with this course was that there was this teacher
[S] And I, she really must have been a demon in the shape of a human being kind of thing cause [L]
[S] She was just really bad, she yelled at the kids a lot
[S] She.. and she used to like take kids by the ear and drag them around the classroom and stuff like that [L]
[S] It was pretty awful to ever have to be in her class kind of [L]
[S] She was a really just like, terrible, terrible person [L]
[S] And she really made my life hell  (during?) this course, it was pretty bad [L]
[S] Um me and, I actually met some friends, just like
[S] Me and these 4 other guys like used to bond over just hating this one teacher essentially [L]
[S] Cause like she was so awful that we would sit and talk about how awful she was after class
[L] Uh-huh [S] Um so I made some friends there at the school, which was nice
[S] Just through this teacher essentially
[S] And for the most part the school was okay
[S] Except for this one course that really like made my life awful kind of  [L]
[S] Uh and this continued for about a year kind of
[S] Uh and then after one year we had to give this very big presentation
[S] In this like uh what's uh classical music theory course [L] Uh-huh
[S] Um [L] Are you playing anything in that time?
[S] Uh yeah I played a quite, I played a decent amount, I learned a lot
[S] Um it was a lot of just normal school classes essentially
[S] I only had these music classes like an extra curricular thing like
[S] When you, sometimes you would have, other people wuld have sports, we would have music essentially [L] Uh-huh
[S] Um.. yeah and so I had to give this one presentation essentially
[S] To the class, in classical music theory, and..
[S] I was super nervous, cause I was still very shy at this point in time in some sense [L] Uh-huh
[S] Ah.. but on the, cause on the one hand I had to like present everything to the entire class
[S] Which is like scary enough to actually speak in front of a group of people
[S] And then on the other hand I was terrified of this teacher, so like  [L] Uh-huh
[S] I was really scared of like what she would say about my presentation and stuff er
[S] So I did prepare a lot for this presentation, I prepared slides, I practiced in front of my mirror and stuff like that [L] Hmm
[S] Ah and then I finally gave this presentation kind of
[S] Um and I thought the presentation went well
[S] Uh I presented it to the class kind of and they all laughed throughout mostly in the presentation
[S] They clapped when I was done, I felt pretty good about it
[S] But then when I was done this teacher really ripped into like my, what's it called, presentation kind of
[S] She really like said no why would say this, why did you do this, this was entirely wrong kind of thing [L] Hmm
[S] And she really just like was very mean and like uh..
[S] Mean about it, like the feedback she gave essentially [L] Uh-huh
[S] Uh and that kind of really uh really impacted my self esteem kind of
[S] Because I'm a very fra, I was a very fragile person back  [L] Negatively
[S] Yeah, it very negatively impacted my self esteem kind of, cause I was a very fragile back then
[S] As a person I had very low self esteem still at that time
[S] So it was very difficult for me to handle that kind of negative unfiltered feedback kind of
[S] Uh so I basically returned to my parents in tears kind of
[S] And told them like look uh this is just not working like I can't deal with this teacher, I don't want to
[S] Uh so  we went and talked with the school, but the school said they can't really do anything like
[S] This lady, she, they'd had reports about her before
[S] But she's on a bunch of boards and she couldn't really be replaced that easily kind of
[S] And it was up to her how she uh her class and stuff [L] Hmm
[S] So we couldn't really deal much about that
[S] But the course was still mandatory so it's like
[S] She'd still be around kind of, and she made people's life difficult anyway, even when they weren't in her class
[S] So we discussed possibly like just
[S] Uh cause we had, they were, the normal high school also shared a couple of courses with this uh music school
[S] So they suggested that we could transfer
[S] What was left of my education over to this normal high school kind of
[S] And I could just go back to a more technical like oriented thing
[S] Where I wouldn't have to do these music courses with her [L] Hmm
[S] Ah which was okay, it was a solution kind of
[S] Which we took uh, it wasn't, it would've been better if I could've con
[S] Or I would've been happier if I could've continued with the music place
[S] But my parents were just happy that I can switch to a technical, you know, school kind of
[S] My parents are very practical like that so  [L] Hmm
[S] Ah it was unfortunate but I did eventually finish off kind of
[S] Graduating with this kind of more technical degree in high school
[S] Um.. yeah I didn't really pursue music too much [L] But you gave up about finding
[S] It was a bit of a traumatic experience kind of
[S] So it kind of left a bad taste in my mouth kind of for a very long time [L] Hmm
[S] Uh eventually I had to go to college after this kind of uh..
[S] And I, the weird thing is I actually did bump into one of those people I'd been in a band back at this music school
[S] Who, and they still hated the teacher by the way, cause they'd actually been there for the last two years
[S] Had to deal with the teacher the last, last two years [L]
[S] Ah but we start talking a lot, and talking about how things were
[S] And he said that he and the other guys had started up a band
[S] And they play a bit casually every now and then kind of
[S] And he said that hey yeah you should us. I was like, what? Me?
[S] I was like really?  cause like I didn't like [L]
[S] Wow I was like wow  I'm surprised you were even like remember that I exist
[S] Like yeah you were a good vocalist, and like uh wow okay
[L]  [S] Ah so  so I joined them and we like rehearsed a bit
[S] And we try out some stuff and it was really fun and
[S] And eventually we actually had, have like a small concert, or a small concert for like uh
[S] Some friends and stuff, a group of friends and like
[S] It went very well, and I felt really like liberated and free and I got to do the performance kind of stuff
[S] It was really cool, I really felt amazing [L] Uh-huh
[S] It really helped my self uh, self esteem quite a lot so
[S] Yeah that was a good experience for me [L] Hmm
[L] Cool, fantastic [S] Ah yeah