[S] hi, how are you?
[L] hi
[L] good
[S] yeah?
[L] fine, how are you?
[S] cool cool I'm ok
[S] yeah yeah uh man I had such a interesting weekend just remembering stuff from the past you know when was really
[S] reminded my time in high school and stuff and do you like your time in high school?
[S] yeah somehow not all of it
[S] yeah? not all of it I think no one likes it really right? there is always something... there is always something a problem or so
[S] yeah I remember I was... I moved a lot from city to city and then I moved in the middle of high school
[S] and yeah you know new guy arrived, no one knows you, you know no one so it's kind of you know lonely and
[S] not connecting to everyone, to anyone in particular you know was weird and I mean I was not a good student I was really bad I mean not really bad I never failed
[S] but I didn't like to study I just did the minimum to pass jut to get out of there as soon as possible and yeah I really
[S] dislike also the teachers they were so bad they were these very old teachers with this.. not didatic at all just reading through..
[S] slides and stuff like that and just writing stuff but without any passion for it you know just mechanical stuff and this was not helping at all
[S] bad bad thing pretty bad thing uh.. but yeah there is.. at some point I met this teacher from history and I never liked history
[S] was kind of boring was just dates and names of people that you had to memorize otherwise you don't pass the test etc
[S] but this guy was different this guy was a new teacher he was quite young, he was very cool, very fresh, very full of life and
[S] he passed it to the students you know he was very dynamic it was a very different way to teach the course and although I didn't like history I
[S] start to pay attention more on the lecture you know? and then come the time for making my first exam
[S] and I failed and I was like yeah  that makes some sense I was a bit sad and was the first time I was paying attention to the thing
[L] oh..
[S] and I failed but then the teacher came talk to me and then he asked yeah what's happening why you failed?
[S] you always pay attention you're always in the lecture you always make good questions and taking notes then we talked a lot for a long time and I got this boost of um..
[S] motivation you know like yeah it's not that bad to fail but it's important that I learn what they  and then I can get better next time
[S] then I studied more and I started studying I started liking it a bit um.. understanding the area not just memorizing dates and numbers and stuff like that
[S] and there was a second exam and I make the second exam and I fail again
[S] and then was like wow something wrong and then I started to panic I really really like.. wow that's not possible
[S] I finally connected with one course I like it and I like to learn it
[S] and I failed what's wrong here and I was really down really depressed and the teacher came and talk to me hey what's happening
[S] I see that you're really interested and it's the second time you fail now but don't give up go for it and study again calm down and then I tried again to study and
[S] repeat to myself every night to study the course um.. the night before the final exam so I had to pass this final exam otherwise I fail the course right
[S] the night before the final exam I completely panicked I completely completely panicked so what I did? I took some stripes of paper and I make some notes on it
[S] and then my plan was to bring this during the exam into my sleeve so I could take it out during the exam and kind of cheat the exam
[S] but the.. yeah and then came the day of the exam and I did it
[S] so I really took it and I don't know if he saw it he didn't tell anything so I made the exam
[S] by the end of the exam I was feeling so bad I was feeling so.. so guilty so heavily
[S] these heavy shoulders you know really like wow how can I do that it was really ridiculous in the end I passed the exam
[S] but the day after it was like wow that was not right that was really like wow really really down really dense
[S] and I carried this with me over over and over I mean I never did this anymore I think maybe because of that maybe because of the feeling of guilt of um..
[S] failing from.. with myself so so strong like it is a lesson that I learned was really strong in my teenage times