[S] cool that was that how's your weekend being so far?
[L] yeah my weekend is about thesis
[S] yeah
[S] like I'm I'm writing my thesis but on.. on saturday night? I hang out with a bunch of good friends so that was really good
[S] yeah yeah I get that
[S] yeah
[S] like I'm I'm writing my thesis but on.. on saturday night? I hang out with a bunch of good friends so that was really good
[S] it's nice that you'd come here to do this kind of to come here and listen to the stories that I'm gonna tell you know so it's nice that you could after you've enjoyed your weekend that you'd come here and like enjoy this
[S]
[L] hm yeah that's not bad
[S]  it's alright, right?
[L]  yeah
[S] yeah anyway today I'm gonna tell you two stories about myself kinda  a bit about me so first I'm gonna tell you a little bit about like.. would you say that you're an introvert ?
[L] sure sure sure yeah..
[L] sorry what?
[S] would you say that you're an introverted person?
[L] I I.. it depends so in a new environment I'll be more like (aside?), introverted but yeah.. once the ice is
[S] yeah
[S] yeah I get it
[L] I I.. it depends so in a new environment I'll be more like (aside?), introverted but yeah.. once the ice is
[S] yeah
[S] hm
[L] I I.. it depends so in a new environment I'll be more like (aside?), introverted but yeah.. once the ice is
[L]  broken  I'll be a different person
[S] hm
[S] yeah 'cause I
[L]  broken  I'll be a different person
[S] yeah 'cause I'd say I'm a very introverted person kinda and I was like this since I was young right? 'cause we just  and for that you don't tell that much I was very introverted person I tended to stay at home a lot I tended to
[S] yeah 'cause I
[L] ok
[S] yeah 'cause I'd say I'm a very introverted person kinda and I was like this since I was young right? 'cause we just  and for that you don't tell that much I was very introverted person I tended to stay at home a lot I tended to
[L] yeah yeah
[L] ok
[S] yeah 'cause I'd say I'm a very introverted person kinda and I was like this since I was young right? 'cause we just  and for that you don't tell that much I was very introverted person I tended to stay at home a lot I tended to
[S] play a lot of like video games on my own kind of I was very.. I was lonely but didn't hate it kinda.. yeah
[L] uh-huh
[L] yeah you enjoyed your serenity
[S] play a lot of like video games on my own kind of I was very.. I was lonely but didn't hate it kinda.. yeah
[S] yeah I enjoyed being on my own quite a lot which is nice kinda 'cause I got to be a lot on my own and this kinda continued for a long time and eventually at some point I moved to
[L] ok yeah yeah
[L] yeah yeah
[S] yeah I enjoyed being on my own quite a lot which is nice kinda 'cause I got to be a lot on my own and this kinda continued for a long time and eventually at some point I moved to
[S] Sweden when I.. I must have been in the age of like eleven, twelve or something
[L] uh-huh
[L] well that's quite young
[S] Sweden when I.. I must have been in the age of like eleven, twelve or something
[S] yeah it was quite young it was quite young it's a.. it was a bit of a sad moving I remember my dad told me I actually cried like so later on I actually cried for having to come and move to Sweden 'cause like I'd be away from my friends I wouldn't get
[L] hm
[S] to see my family my grandma I was moving away from my grandparents and stuff so that was like uh..
[L] ok
[L] so like you moved with your parents or ?
[S] uh.. yeah I moved with my parents yeah yeah so eventually I moved to Sweden kinda I was a bit lonely in the beginning kinda 'cause obviously new country new language it was a bit weird
[L] ok yeah
[L] yeah yeah yeah
[S] uh.. yeah I moved with my parents yeah yeah so eventually I moved to Sweden kinda I was a bit lonely in the beginning kinda 'cause obviously new country new language it was a bit weird
[S] I did eventually start school kinda so I started in a normal class 'cause I spoke English and they had to learn English
[L] yeah yeah yeah
[L] hm
[S] I did eventually start school kinda so I started in a normal class 'cause I spoke English and they had to learn English
[L] yeah yeah yeah
[L] uh-huh
[S] I did eventually start school kinda so I started in a normal class 'cause I spoke English and they had to learn English
[S]  culture exchange um.. so I got to start I didn't have a lot of friends but one of the first friends I made was this one girl kinda she was very nice she was very independent and outgoing which
[L]  ok
[S] was very different from me 'cause I was very reserved kinda but she was like very independent she had this kinda Swedish mentality where she was very brave and outgoing and  and stuff and she also speak English which helped
[L] ok ok
[L] hm hm
[S] was very different from me 'cause I was very reserved kinda but she was like very independent she had this kinda Swedish mentality where she was very brave and outgoing and  and stuff and she also speak English which helped
[S]  you know?
[L] hm hm
[L] oh yeah that's a big convenience
[S]  you know?
[S] yeah it's good it was good for me it would be very quiet and awkward otherwise and.. so I became very good friends with this girl we kinda used to like uh.. watch a lot of cartoons together and play video games and go out and kinda
[L] oh yeah that's a big convenience
[L] uh-huh uh-huh
[S] yeah it's good it was good for me it would be very quiet and awkward otherwise and.. so I became very good friends with this girl we kinda used to like uh.. watch a lot of cartoons together and play video games and go out and kinda
[S] get on to a lot of mischief one of  yeah yeah
[L] yeah (always?) nice
[S] one of the things that we actually did is we lived close to a kinda of a like lumbered processing planks you know where they make kinda planks for furniture kinda so they have this big yard where they
[L] ok.. yeah.. oh ok
[S] store all the planks before they chopped like IKEA or whatever and.. and what.. her and me used to.. we used to like sneak into this place and used to like steal planks essentially
[L]  ok
[S] uh.. and what we would do with this planks is that we would
[L] from strangers or from ?
[S] they wouldn't.. they wouldn't miss them it's just like some leftover planks so we took this leftover planks and like.. what we would do with this planks is that we would kinda build this a go kart essentially so we would nail this planks
[L] ok ok yeah yeah uh-huh
[S] together like a kart wheel yeah it's so was like we would uh.. we build  this go kart over weekends kinda and then we'd put on some like we'd add an extra seat kind of and then we'd add a trunk in the back
[L] go kart?
[S] kind of we'd add these (fenders?) to the side to make it go faster.. yeah it was a very  it was a fun like project kinda and this thing could actually go right? pretty
[L] that's cool! that's very cool!
[L] yeah
[S] kind of we'd add these (fenders?) to the side to make it go faster.. yeah it was a very  it was a fun like project kinda and this thing could actually go right? pretty
[S] fast it's like what we would do is I had this big asphalted slope next to my house kinda and what we'd do is we'd take the go kart to the top of this and then someone was is in and we'd just roll it down the hill
[L] uh-huh uh-huh
[S]  (so mean?) uh.. well I mean just about 'cause the actually the thing with this thing was it was a bit dangerous
[L] yeah I get that you still (like it?)
[S] so this one time I did actually hurt myself pretty badly uh.. so we'd actually take it to the top of the hill and I was sitting in it and like she was behind she'd give me a push but then she gave me this super hard push
[L] ok ok
[L]  yeah
[S] so this one time I did actually hurt myself pretty badly uh.. so we'd actually take it to the top of the hill and I was sitting in it and like she was behind she'd give me a push but then she gave me this super hard push
[S] so like she really launched it down this hill kinda it was going  I was trying to hold on and this thing was like bobbling kinda and eventually it turned and flipped kind of and the thing is I was stuck
[L]  yeah
[S] so this one time I did actually hurt myself pretty badly uh.. so we'd actually take it to the top of the hill and I was sitting in it and like she was behind she'd give me a push but then she gave me this super hard push
[S] so like she really launched it down this hill kinda it was going  I was trying to hold on and this thing was like bobbling kinda and eventually it turned and flipped kind of and the thing is I was stuck
[L] yeah
[S] in this thing right? so it's like I like it flipped my legs were still inside of it so I had to lake brace it with the right side of my body and what happened is I kinda of landed on the asphalt I like skied for like
[L] uh-huh
[L] uh..
[S] in this thing right? so it's like I like it flipped my legs were still inside of it so I had to lake brace it with the right side of my body and what happened is I kinda of landed on the asphalt I like skied for like
[S] a sure couple of feet kind of like and it was really bloody that my arm really scraped off the hill  skin and it was pretty bad and I was just on the ground
[L] ew my god yeah
[S] crying and like half like  from the pain and like she was just screaming and she had to run off and get my dad who was working at the yard  and so it was like
[L] yeah yeah  ok
[S] yeah that was.. that wasn't great  was recover from that was pretty painful but uh.. I did get over it kind of eventually uh..
[L] yeah yeah
[L] yeah it's not like you know
[S] yeah that was.. that wasn't great  was recover from that was pretty painful but uh.. I did get over it kind of eventually uh..
[S] that comes with
[S] yeah yeah it's a stupid thing to do which  that you remember kind of  but then uh it was I really enjoyed spending time with this girl and like we got to stuff like that and it's like pretty awful
[L]  yeah
[L] uh-huh uh-huh
[S] yeah yeah it's a stupid thing to do which  that you remember kind of  but then uh it was I really enjoyed spending time with this girl and like we got to stuff like that and it's like pretty awful
[S] that was one of the worst experiences but it's like yeah
[L] uh-huh uh-huh
[L]
[S] that was one of the worst experiences but it's like yeah
[S] yeah I remember I remember it very well.. yeah oh yeah so me and her had a lot of fun so what happened was that was this one thing with this girl like I'd know her for a couple
[L] trying new things.. yeah
[S] of months now and we'd spent a lot of time together but.. it was weird because like she quickly got to know that her dad had gotten a job in Asia yeah so she.. so she had to
[L] yeah
[L] yeah? ok
[S] of months now and we'd spent a lot of time together but.. it was weird because like she quickly got to know that her dad had gotten a job in Asia yeah so she.. so she had to
[S] move kinda her family had to move essentially which was really bad for me 'cause I just found this new friend kind of and we spent a lot of time together and then like
[L] uh..
[L] yeah yeah right
[S] move kinda her family had to move essentially which was really bad for me 'cause I just found this new friend kind of and we spent a lot of time together and then like
[S] so it's like no I'm moving it's like I was like uh.. so I was a bit stressed out and depressed by this 'cause my first real friend was moving kind of so I was really
[L] yeah.. yeah and just a few months and..
[S] awkward and bit .. yeah it's not a long time to know each other kind of a.. and we  numbers kinda to try to keep in touch 'cause it was a bit before social media stuff
[S] so we  numbers to try to keep in touch and like a called her and after she moved I couldn't get in touch with her kind of it's like  was going to be kind of (before?) hand and like
[L] hm hm hm hm hm
[S] apparently Swedish sim calls don't work so well in China so we couldn't really get in touch with each other kind of so we kind of dropped out of contact for a while which was it was a shame I recovered from it eventually
[L]
[L] ok
[S] apparently Swedish sim calls don't work so well in China so we couldn't really get in touch with each other kind of so we kind of dropped out of contact for a while which was it was a shame I recovered from it eventually
[S] but uh.. it took a while
[L] ok
[L] yeah it's kinda sad that you guys didn't exchange address
[S] yeah yeah yeah I mean I don't feel like sending posts like I'm (realistic?) I moved around quite when they got there
[L] yeah
[L] ok yeah
[S] yeah yeah yeah I mean I don't feel like sending posts like I'm (realistic?) I moved around quite when they got there
[S] and she
[L] ok yeah
[L] what's her name by the way?
[S] and she
[S] uh.. Emily
[L] Emily ok yeah
[S] so yeah because the thing is that eventually she did get in touch with me again after Facebook so I think actually it's kinda.. it was kinda like five years later or something so we were quite
[L] ok ok ok
[S] I was seventeen or something it was quite a long time later and I was pretty impressed to see her kinda to hear from her was like insane it's like the magic of the technology right?
[L] ok
[L] yeah it's really nice
[S] I was seventeen or something it was quite a long time later and I was pretty impressed to see her kinda to hear from her was like insane it's like the magic of the technology right?
[L] it's like losing touch for five years and then suddenly you know that connection is back again
[S] so we actually started to chat a lot with each other about stuff it was a very nostalgic kinda  talked about what happened uh.. but the thing is that I didn't even notice that she had changed quite a lot inside
[L] yeah
[S] there and I changed quite a lot obviously as well 'cause like it's been five years right? so we're very different as people uh.. and we kept exchanging messages for a while but it kinda
[L] ok
[L] yeah
[S] there and I changed quite a lot obviously as well 'cause like it's been five years right? so we're very different as people uh.. and we kept exchanging messages for a while but it kinda
[S] towards the end because like we've become very different people kind of I was more interested in (nostalgia?) and she was just kinda busy with other stuff I guess uh.. yeah
[L] ok
[L] sure sure.. yeah that's understandable
[S] towards the end because like we've become very different people kind of I was more interested in (nostalgia?) and she was just kinda busy with other stuff I guess uh.. yeah
[S] so yeah sadly people change but that's it was a good experience to me
[L] yeah sure I mean it's like everyone moves forward eventually
[S] yeah we all grow don't we?
[L] and die eventually
[S]  that's true.. uh ok and that's..