[S] before  interrupt it, ok right? so I told you about my friend and how she left.. this left me with a bit of an issue kinda 'case I was very lonely at that
[S] point in time when she had left obviously uh.. so I was really looking for that coping mechanism I got a lot into this idea of being a musician kinda just this kind of vent
[L] hm..
[S] uh.. this kinda feeling I needed to get rid of this.. this kinda loneliness and this kinda need to achieve something kinda
[S] um.. so I  my parents to kind of buy me some kind of instrument like a guitar or something essentially.. they were not  they treated it more as
[S] phase in some sense essentially I need to kind of get over this uh.. I kept  but they really kind of just ignored it eventually I managed to negotiate, the best
[S] I could negotiate essentially was that when I was transferring from low to middle school to high school is that they would send  me to a kind of musical (rendered?) highschool essentially so I could
[S] go to that high school as long as the high school had real courses well as like the music stuff um..  so I did that and then I yeah so started off at the school
[S] and the school was very good I'd say it was a very nice campus most of.. most of the stuff except  for one person we'll get back to later were very friendly
[S]  food was very good unlike here um..  but uh yeah so was really good going there and I learned I lot kinda of being there but there was one course in particular that a had
[L]
[S] problems with and that course was um.. classical music fear is what the course was called
[L] makes sense.. interesting
[S] yeah it was an experience um.. and the reason I had an issue with this particular course was the teacher was.. I'm pretty sure she was some kind of a devil in the shape of a human essentially
[L]
[S] she used to be very like demeaning to students, she would like yell at students and drag them by their ears kinda if they did something
[S] something wrong.. yeah that kind of teacher you sound like you have experience
[L] hm.. that kind of teacher
[L] yeah
[S] something wrong.. yeah that kind of teacher you sound like you have experience
[S] yeah but she was uh.. yeah she was an experience  so yeah but so she uh.. that was.. having classes was a big issue I did actually make some friend from that it surprised me because like
[S] I met these four guys essentially which also like really did dislike this music teacher and we used to like bond over how much we hated this particular person kinda uh.. yeah so
[S] it was survivable I wouldn't say I enjoyed her classes but like she had the held of this mandatory course I didn't have much of a choice uh.. anyway but after..
[S] this didn't last too long 'cause after one year I think then we had to give this fairly big presentation of classical music for the class and I was kind of terrified for two reasons one I had to present in front of the entire class and I
[S] still fairly with the  fragile at this time I would say but at the same time I also had to present in front of this evil demon woman kinda and  just the thought
[S] of her getting me terrified me kind of at a primal level in some sense uh.. I spent a lot of time preparing for this presentation I made slides I rehearsed in front of a mirror all of that
[S] kind of good stuff and  the day came and I had to give this presentation in front of the class and I gave the presentation I thought it went very well people applauded  the presentation and I was very happy with it
[S] but then the teacher really just tore into my presentation (which I gonna give her?) comments like she was really sitting there this is awful why would you say this why did you do this you need to speak louder kind of thing
[S] and I did not take this right to be honest I basically was reduced to tears and I got home and I talked to my parents kinda and we talked with the
[S] school kinda of can we get rid of this teacher she's obviously just an awful person kinda can we do something about this and the school said no I mean she's on a bunch of boards like we can't really get rid of her she's very like
[S] important then we discussed with the school is there anything that we can do kinda 'cause I really just couldn't stand this teacher anymore she was just too much for me kind of essentially she was very traumatic to be around essentially
[S] and  as a kid um.. so we um.. so because the other local high school she shared a lot of courses with this music school we essentially arranged so I could just
[S] transfer into program at the local high school instead of the musical school so I could still get my exam without needing all this special music (courses?) as they normally required uh.. and then I would transfer
[S] away from the musical school essentially into a more technical class which my parents were happy about but I was obviously like less enthusiastic about essentially um.. so I did eventually finish
[S] finished high school there in this technical subject kinda of uh.. and I continued that to college but the thing was when I got to college I actually
[S] bumped into one of the people I used to uh go to the musical school with one of these four people that used to like hate on this teacher with me it turns out they still hated this teacher after all this time so that
[L]  it didn't change
[S] scar for life so to speak  uh.. and I was talking with them and they started like playing in this band kinda and we talked a lot about the band and he said hey you should join us I was like me?
[S] he was like yeah you used be pretty good at (vocals?)  me? wow ok  so we talked a bit and then we met up with the other guys kinda and we actually started to like
[L]
[S] play using  of the weekends and stuff that was pretty cool uh.. eventually we would have like a small concert for some of my close friends and stuff
[S] that was really fun I felt really amazing when I was performing I felt really inebriated kind of so it was really cool yeah so.. it was a good experience.. I enjoy singing
[S]
[L] nice