[L] Hi!
[S] How are you?
[L] I'm great.
[S] Yeah? Cool!
[S] I was thinking these days about uh...
[S] old time, so.. high school time.
[L]
[S] Did you like your high school time?
[L] No
[S] No? really it's was bad?
[L] Yeah, it was bad.
[S] really? oh, wow .
[L] Yeah.
[S] My was also awful. was really , really, really  bad.
[L] Uh-huh.
[S] I was really bad student, really bad grade uh..
[S] People under around me was really weird people. So, the whole students. I had no friend at high school. It was strange.
[S] People were strange. I couldn't connected to all of them.
[S] The teachers were so bad. They were so, so so, bad. Everything so awful.
[L]
[L] Uh-huh.
[S] The teachers were so bad. They were so, so so, bad. Everything so awful.
[S] I didn't no fail, but it was almost.  You know? It was really like wow, really, really bad, bad..
[L] Uh-huh.
[L] (I've been there?)
[S] I didn't no fail, but it was almost.  You know? It was really like wow, really, really bad, bad..
[L]
[L] (I've been there?)
[S] I didn't no fail, but it was almost.  You know? It was really like wow, really, really bad, bad..
[S] Yes, It was really ridiculous.
[L] (I've been there?)
[L]
[S] Yes, It was really ridiculous.
[S] And  there was a time when I was, I think, in the mid of high school something like that.
[L] Yeah.
[S] And then I had this teacher. Which was actually the only good teacher in the whole school. It was the history teacher.
[S] He was very nice guy, he was very cool guy. You know? very calm.
[S] Very relax, different from other teachers. The other teachers always stressful, always like you have to do that, you have to do that . Stupid people.
[L]
[S] But this guy was different. He was really nice. He teaches history, he kind of love history, and the way that he teaches was really nice.
[S] My problem is that I didn't like history as a course, as a subject, it was really boring for me
[S] It was a lot dates, a lot of names to remember, a lot of... It was like  why should I do that? wow, It's not for me.
[L] Yes.
[S] Uh.. Yeah, but he really make it like.. ok, it was actually not that bad to attend to his class. Then I started to like it or so, and then we had the first exam.
[L] Um.
[S] I fail miserably. I was super super bad, I was really like awful.
[L]
[S] But, after the exams.. after the results come out he came talk to me.
[L] Yeah.
[S] And then he came and said: - Yeah, what happen?.  And then he started to talk to me in a different way. None of the other teach did this with me before.
[S] And I don't know he was trying to help. You know? He was really trying to be a good guy. And then I kind of connected with him me and it  kind of  yeah..
[S] The problem is not the subject. The problem was me. I the one who made this harder than it should be. You know?
[S] And yeah, It was not so nice. them I started to study a bit more, pay a bit more attention to class. And then I did the second test. I pass on this test.
[L] Uh-huh.
[S] So, It was like Wow I actually can do that! This is interesting.
[S] Er.. I mean.. I barely passed, it was like marginal board the line, but yeah I'd passed. And then came to the final exam.
[L] Uh-huh
[S] And I was so nervous, so so so nervous. I had to past in this exam to prove do this teacher that he actually did something.
[S] Ah.. But I was complete non confident on myself. No self confidence at all.
[L] Yeah.
[S] And then what I did, I made a plan to cheat the exam.
[L] Uh-huh. Yeah..
[S] Er.. yeah I made some papers and put then on my sleeve, you know? With dates and numbers and names and so on.
[L]
[S] And then I went to the exam. And as son as I finished the exam. It was like wow I fell really bad.
[S] I felt so guilt, so so guilt for doing that. For breaking the trust of that guy, that one person I could connect.
[L] Um
[S] I'm handing the exam.
[L] Um.
[S] And the teach was very happy. Very "yeah, It's great you did it, very !". Inside I was felling so destroyed.
[L] Uh-huh.
[S] I was felling so so so bad. Really like wow how can I do that?  I'm the worst person on earth, you know?
[S] And then I passed the exam.
[L] Yeah.
[S] Er.. I don't know.. I've never recovered. After that I never cheated anymore
[S] It felt really bad and every time I think about it wow that was just a bad move.
[L] Uh-huh.
[S] Really really bad, you know?
[S]  weird  yeah.
[L] Uh-huh.
[S] That's