[S] So where were we before we were interrupted er..
[S] Okay so I told you about my friend and she had moved essentially um..
[S] Shortly after she had moved
[S] And I actually.. I haven't told you about this, I'm actually the vocalist in a band
[S] Did you know that?
[L] No.
[S]  Interesting fact um.. there's actually a story behing that because
[S] Er shortly after she had moved, I started to get a lot more into music, kind of
[S] So I got a lot more into like
[S] I kept listening to all of these kind of nerdy videos
[S] About like people playing guitars and kind of showing you how to do different chords and stuff um
[S] So I got really interested in that kind of and I started to like tell my parents look I wanna play an instrument, buy me an instrument kind of
[S] Ah they didn't take it too seriously kind of
[S] They just kind of take it as um.. kind of a passing flight of fancy for me essentially
[S] So they didn't really agree to buy me anything too exciting
[S] Um the best I could do is kind of when I was transferring into essentially high school
[S] Is like convince them to send me to a kind of a special like half music kind of specialty high school
[S] As long as they had all the other like subjects there, they had the maths and they had the chemistry and they had the stuff
[S] So it was like, I could go there as long as I did some real subjects you know, on the side  [L] Yeah, yeah
[S] Um.. so yeah, so basically I went there
[S] And I, when I started there it was really great, like I learned a lot kind of
[S] School was great, it was really nice campus, really nice atmosphere essentially [L] Uh-huh
[S] Aside from the  in here  [L] That sucks
[S] But er yeah so.. yeah I really enjoyed it there
[S] And the only thing a had one problem with was this one mandatory class called classical music theory
[S] And I really hated that class, and I really hated that class cause I really hated the teacher in that class
[S] I'm pretty sure she was some kind of a demon in the skin of a human you know, it was pretty bad
[S] Um so I really, cause she was really just a mean and cruel person
[S] Like she used to drag kids around by the ears kind of, almost a bit pseudo-abusive, not great um
[S] So I really hated that class kind of, it was very boring
[S] I actually met some friends who like, at that school,  friends
[S] That we bonded over essentially just hating this one teacher kind of, it was
[S] Um yeah so it was pretty  pretty dramatic to do that but we, I learned a lot and I had a great, some great fun there
[S] Um.. that continued well for a while kind of, until a couple of months
[S] So a couple of, it was two, one year down the line or something
[S] Like we were suppose give this presentation in front of the entire class on like classical music theory with this harpy of a teacher right
[S] Um  so I started to, I was very nervous for, before this presentation
[S] Because like I had to, first I had to go up and present it in front of everyone, I was still a bit introverted
[S] This time has kind of subsided, I don't know if you noticed  [L] I did
[S] But um I was partially scared cause I had to give the presentation in front of everyone
[S] And partially because I had to do it in front of this teacher who I was terrified of essentially
[S] So I studied very hard for this, and I made a very good presentation, what I thought was a very good presentation
[S] And I eventually went up and gave the presentation in front of the class, I thought I'd done very well
[S] But then I started to get feedback from this teacher like, no this is ridiculous, you should've done this, this wasn't good enough, this was awful like
[S] So I really  ah that was really heavy for me
[S] I really inflicted a blow on my self esteem kind of
[S] So I like went back to my parents in shambles and I cried and like  [L] Ah
[S] I told them basically look we couldn't, I couldn't like keep going and being at the school and having to deal with this teacher kind of
[S] Cause I had to have her for another two years or something, it was ridiculous [L] Hmm
[S] We talked with the school about this teacher before, they said that look she's basically there to stay, we can't do anything about it
[S] So like uh it was pretty bad
[S] So what we did arrange eventually is that I could actually transfer back to the normal high school kind of
[S] Where they had, because they shared a lot of courses with this music school [L] Uh-huh
[S] So I could kind of complete the rest of my education at this normal high school kind of, so I  [L] Yeah
[S] Transferred over there, which was a shame kind of, cause I did enjoy being at this kind of special music school
[S] Cause I had to have her like several times a week and she was awful kind of, so yeah [L]  yeah
[S] So I did eventually keep going to this high school and I graduated in all the stuff, kind of the most technical subjects
[S] Ah eventually when I went to college essentially
[S] I actually met up with these four guys from, that I'd met from high school
[S] From this kind of musical high school kind of
[S] Ah and I was chatting with them kind of and we were catching up on old times er
[S] And then one of them said hey we're still playing kind of, you should join us. I was like wow me?
[S] Yeah you used to be pretty good at singing. I was like uh I mean okay
[S] Ah so we tried out a bit and we practiced a bit and it was really fun er
[S] Actually a couple of months after I met them we then we actually had a concert kind of
[S] I felt really grat during that concert it was amazing kind of  [L] Uh-huh nice
[S] I felt really like liberated to be able to do this kind of
[S] It was really a nice experience for me to just kind of, to let go and kind of really express myself so [L] Ah great
[S] Yeah, yeah so I keep in touch with them and
[S] We jam out from time to time
[L] I see, that's good [S] Yeah, yeah that's how I did that so
[S] Now you know  [L] Good