[S] so things are good how's your weekend being?
[L] um.. it's actually being really nice uh
[S] cool cool cool yeah yeah    yeah so.. I'm gonna tell you two stories today.. stories about me growing up stuff like that uh..
[L]
[S] uh.. first off would say that you're an introvert?
[L] more or like an introvert yeah
[S] yeah you kind of have to be  computer science right so? yeah I was also kinda introvert as a kid essentially uh.. I spent a lot of time
[S] playing video games essentially just being by myself I wouldn't say I hated I did kind of enjoy like being on my own , alone some kind of.. it wasn't that hard in South Africa
[S] where you kinda live on this  communities kind of so it's very difficult to kinda meet people essentially  without your parents driving you somewhere uh.. yeas so I did
[L]
[S] kind of enjoy being a lot on my own when I was young ant that's  persisted  most of my youth I did at some point in time move to Sweden when was? when I was
[S] eleven twelve something like that uh.. and I didn't like I obviously was a bit more even lonelier then kind of 'cause I moved and kinda didn't know the language and
[S]  all a bit strange uh.. that last for a while took me a while to meet a friend but eventually I did meet a friends my first friend was actually someone who I
[S] started school essentially low middle school and one of the first friends I met was this girl kind of and she was pretty amazing and fascinating to me kinda she was very outgoing she was very
[S] independent and brave kinda so that was really cool for me who was obviously very shy and introvert uh.. it was very nice to meet someone of that kinda and we did become
[L] yeah
[S] pretty close friends I'd say 'cause we watched a lot of cartoons we played video games we used to  all the kinds of mischief kinda.. yeah it's good to meet someone like that
[L] that's nice
[S] specially if you're new 'cause she's like a kind of an anchor also she spoke English which was a good plus kinda uh.. yeah so we spent a lot of time together kinda we really get to.. get up to quite a lot of stuff
[L]
[S] one of the things notable things that I do remember of this time with her was that we had this like lumbered processing area where they had like store the planks for making furniture kinda so this big
[S] area where they store a bunch of planks kinda and what me and her would do is like sneak into this area and like take some planks essentially we'd sneak off some planks  nothing that
[L] uh ok
[S] we were kids you do stupid stuff but what we'd do with this planks was that we made thins kind of a like go kart so we would kinda hammer the planks together to make this go kart
[S] thing we'd put some wheels on it.. yeah yeah it's.. was a death trap in the making but anyway we'll get to that later uh.. but we did kind trick it out a bit over the weekend
[L] oh with the wheels and all the stuff?
[L]
[S] thing we'd put some wheels on it.. yeah yeah it's.. was a death trap in the making but anyway we'll get to that later uh.. but we did kind trick it out a bit over the weekend
[S]  kinda over the weekend kind we'd put some like yeah  we had a seat we'd put a trunk on it or a trunkish thing um.. we'd put uh.. I'd
[S] put some (spoils?) to make it go faster it wasn't it wasn't very safe  as you can imagine what we'd do is take it this.. uh like.. an asphalted hill
[L]
[S] that was next to my house essentially and we'd take it to the top and then someone would sit in it essentially and we'd roll it down the hill.. I know this doesn't sound like a very good idea  it's..
[L] were any of you wearing a hat or something?
[S] no no no  we were young not   um.. yeah as you can probably imagine this didn't always end up so well kind of there was actually
[L] oh my god
[S] one time I got pretty hurt doing this.. and so what we did is we roll this thing up the hill essentially right? and I was sitting in it and she was behind me normally we'd just let me roll it down and kind of (not too bad at?) speed
[S] and what happened is one time is that she kinda gave me a  push kinda I was sitting she'd really pushed me down the hill and it was like the thing was very
[S] fast kinda so I was stuck in this go kart and I was going very fast and I was trying to control it but then it kind of (curved?) and it flipped over kinda now the problem with this is I was still in this (track?) so like my legs were still stuck in the go kart essentially so the only way I
[S] could really like brace myself I had to brace with the right side of my body so what happened is I eventually had to like ski for a couple of feet on the pavement kinda to stop.. and I like ripped of a lot o skin there was a lot
[L] uh-huh
[L] oh that hurts
[S] could really like brace myself I had to brace with the right side of my body so what happened is I eventually had to like ski for a couple of feet on the pavement kinda to stop.. and I like ripped of a lot o skin there was a lot
[S] of blood I was.. I was crying and screaming and she was crying and screaming it was pretty bad   something so she had to run off and get my dad essentially because this was just a disaster
[S] 'cause I was like out and it took quite a lot of time to recover I have to get a bit of stitches and so it was pretty bad  uh.. yeah no
[S] it was not great but it kind of yeah it's.. I don't really regret it too much it was a stupid thing to do but it's like it's the kind of stuff you remember kinds of stuff
[L] did you try it again?
[S] no no no we'd put it aside I think actually my parents told me not to do it again kinda  that thing needs to go away now like I threw it in the dump or in the trash in
[L]
[L]  wondering why?
[S] no no no we'd put it aside I think actually my parents told me not to do it again kinda  that thing needs to go away now like I threw it in the dump or in the trash in
[S] somewhere so yeah.. uh, yeah.. but that's the kind of stuff that you remember kinda and she was really like we made thesse all the stupid stupid stuff and that was one of the most traumatic
[S] experiences essentially.. uh.. this is.. also.. like sadly like our friendship didn't really last for that long I think I'd known her for about six
[L]  hm
[S] or seven months kinda and eventually told me that her dad had gotten a job in Asia and then she had to move and this was pretty ass for me kinda it wasn't great
[S] and I was very..  I was very depressed kinda she.. this new friend I made would be leaving kind of uh.. and I was like
[L] uh-huh
[S] scared of being all alone kind of essentially again which is like it took me a while to get over that uh.. we exchanged phone numbers kinda 'cause this was back before  social media
[S] so we exchanged phone numbers and had plans of calling each other  but when she did move I called her and I didn't get any kind of response like apparently like Swedish sim cards don't work in Asia
[L] uh-huh
[S]  so we did lose contact for a while kind of made me a bit sad I did get over this as time went on kinda it took a while I did hear from hear a while later
[S] like five years later or something she did get in contact with me again uh.. she messages me on Facebook like.. and I was like wow you still exist that's amazing
[S]  uh.. so we talked for while kind of  about the old times um.. there she was really like  we both kinda of changed as people
[S] 'cause obviously it's been five years I've changed quite a lot as a person
[L]  can change a lot in five
[S] yeah five years is a.. specially when you're a kid you go through a lot of changes very quickly and then.. um.. so yeah we talked a bit but as we  got
[L] yeah yeah
[S] less and less and eventually we just stopped talking and 'cause we just at.. we're to different as people to kinda get along in that way if that makes sense uh.. that's a shame
[S] and now it's been quite a long time must have been about like.. I haven't heard from her since essentially since then it's like yeah since five years after that
[L] sorry to hear about that
[S] uh.. life is..
[L] that's life huh?