[S] How was your weekend?
[L] Was good, was good
[S] Was good ?
[L] Yeah..
[S] Yeah, mine too, I went to Norway to visit a friend
[S] Yeah, the city Tromsø, have you heard ? Tromsø?
[L]
[S] It's really, you know, north Norway
[S] It's really nice
[S] It's kind of could in this period
[S] It's not probably the best period to go to Norway
[S] but anyways, it was was nice
[S] Um.. which is, you know, I went out
[S] for dinner, beers..
[S] It's really expensive by the way
[S]  So it's not the kind of city that you'd like to to live
[S]
[S] 'cause.. you know it's a scandinavian country
[S] prices are really high
[S] It was fine, which is, had fun actually was, um, his birthday
[S] it's why we have the
[S]
[S] party
[S] Um..
[S] then the next day he um..
[S]
[s] try this kind of you know, smelly fish thing?
[L] uh.. smoked one? or..
[S] it's, you know, it's just, it it's
[S] thought to be the smelliest food in the world
[S] it's just kind of (harrowing?) , you know? fermented with salt
[L] ah..
[S] and.. I mean kinda raw fish
[S]
[S] and it's really really really smelly
[S] actually so smelly that they discourage to to eat that indoors
[S] so you should be outdoors otherwise you know your house would
[S]
[S] sting like hell
[S] um..
[S] I didn't know it
[S] and he told me that it tastes great
[S] (really?) it's like how something smell so bad
[S] taste great
[S] and they would made a bet
[S] and we should eat one
[S] and you know, the one who eats faster wins
[S] was kind of simbolic bet so there was not a lot of money involved
[S] was just, you know, one euro but anyway
[S] so ok so we went to supermarket and got this kind of
[S] (harrowing?) thing on a can, like a tuna can
[S] but we had to go to uh you know
[S] small garden kinda forest behind his place 'cause you know
[S] he didn't want his place to sting so we went there and uh
[S] yeah, actually was
[S] you know
[S] the can was nice
[S] but as soon as we opened it that was like wow
[S] was such a
[S] strong smell something really really strong like
[S] i remember in
[S] 2016 i had the smelly
[S] which was wow but this was man
[S] i don't know i can't you know
[S] explain how strong this thing was so
[S] and we just opened the whole can was kinda
[S] you know, really painful but
[S] you know and then we have
[S] you know this thing like this fish and is kind of
[S] water and (staff?) and jello
[S] really disgusting
[S] um..
[S] also his
[S] face
[S] was disgusting something like
[S] he was like
[S] ew
[S] so I thought it'd be uh..
[S] it's not true it's gonna taste good so, you know, i lost
[S] my hope but anyway
[S] so yeah now I have to try it
[S] were there, it took me like five minutes to
[S] psychologically prepare
[S] to taste that 'cause
[S] it smelled (terrible?), it looked (terrible?)
[S] so for sure it's gonna taste really bad
[S] so yeah so
[S] actually I don't even like fish in general so that was
[S] to my disadvantage 'cause I think
[S] maybe if you like tuna or
[S] raw fish but wow
[S] I was overwhelmed by this but
[S] you know it was (kinda?) experience
[S] I hate losing bets so it was just like
[S] what the hell just do it
[S] um..
[S] so we just took the can
[S] and then bum there you go you just grab this with your hands
[S] you know texture of this thing is is gluey
[S] fishy thing it's really disgusting
[S] um..
[S] wow so yeah
[S] I really couldn't bite it
[S] like that
[S] I really had to you know do that with my nose 'cause
[S] wow what a smell what a thing
[S] uh.. and when I looked at him he was literally crying
[S] he was you could see he was
[S] he was crying you know dropping tears
[S] 'cause he was like oh my god it's so disgusting
[S] but we just did it and
[S] it was probably the most disgusting thing I ever
[S] tasted in my life
[S] it's really like
[S] I don't know that thing should not be
[S] edible I don't know why there's such tradition there
[S]
[S] but yeah it was disgusting and
[S] well of course he won
[S] I couldn't finish it actually I
[S] just ate something like
[S] this like this huge and yeah
[S] wow was amazing
[S] he didn't finish it either but he
[S] won and then we went back to his place yeah he showed me some videos
[S] on youtube you know reaction videos of this thing and yeah
[S] everybody was like just like myself so
[S] anyway that that's basically what we did this weekend