[S] Hey!
[L] Hey!
[S] How are you?
[L] Good!
[S] Yeah?
[L] Yeah. I hope that you too!
[S] That's great!
[S] Yeah, I'm too.. I'm too, quite nice.. quite nice
[L] Nice!
[S] Yeah!
[S] I was thinking about some stuff this weekend..
[L] Ok..
[S] Um..
[S] How was your high school time?
[L]  Um..
[S] Did you like it?
[L] It was..
[L] Ya, I kinda like it, sometimes I miss it..
[S] Yeah?
[S] Ok, really?
[L] Yeah, it was nice.. it is a different life now
[S] Yeah, sure.. sure.. sure.. of course
[L] Yeah, like moved on from.. from.. our lives
[S] Of course, of course
[L] Yeah, but it's.. such a good memory..
[S] Cool, nice.. yeah
[S] Interesting, because everyone I ask.. or they tell me.. it's like fifty-fifty..
[S] Or they tell me that they liked it, they loved it
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Or they tell me they hated because something bad happen, or something like that, you know?
[L] Ah, ok
[L] I see it, ok, yeah, mine was a good one
[S] Yeah
[S] And I'm..
[L] I see it, ok, yeah, mine was a good one
[S] Was a good one, great!
[L] Yeah
[S] I'm in the second round, so I.. Didn't like it much
[L] Ah, ok
[L] I see it
[S] I had some problems
[S] I actually.. Uh.. moved in to  school in the second year of high school
[L] Uh-huh
[L] Oh..
[S] So it was on the time that.. Uh..
[L] Oh.. ok
[S] Yeah, I mean, everyone was already there..
[S] They knew each other, they grow up together in the same school
[L] Ya.. ya.. ya..
[S] Then I came, I was like the outsider
[L] Uh-huh
[S] The new kid, you know?
[S] Then I came, I was like the outsider
[L] Uh
[S] The new kid, you know?
[S] And then I could never connect with them
[L] Ya..
[S] I was always kinda of apart or something, it was ok..
[S] But yeah, I was a teenager, you know.. it's always problematic..
[L] It's quite sad..
[S] It's always problematic.. yeah..
[L] Yeah, yeah, yeah..
[S] But.. and then.. also the school.. it wasn't a cool school, it's a nice school but..
[S] They had this very, very traditional teachers..
[L] Ok..
[S] Yeah, they were very bad on didactic.. they really could not Uh..
[S] They were this.. old traditional way of teaching, you know?
[L] Hmm
[S] They were like.. Ya, here is the.. I write in the.. in the board.. you read and then, stop
[S] They were this.. old traditional way of teaching, you know?
[L] And you were supposed to write..
[S] They were like.. Ya, here is the.. I write in the.. in the board.. you read and then, stop
[S] Exactly, you copy and it.. that's all, and that supposed to  teaching, it was awful
[L] And you were supposed to write..
[L] Ok.. Ok.. Uh-huh
[S] Exactly, you copy and it.. that's all, and that supposed to  teaching, it was awful
[S] So, I was a really bad student.. I always did everything just to pass but.. never more than that.. never was motivated to study..
[L] Uh-huh.. uh-huh
[L] Uh-huh
[S] So, I was a really bad student.. I always did everything just to pass but.. never more than that.. never was motivated to study..
[S] Was really something..
[L] Uh-huh
[S] But everything changed when this new teacher arrived
[L] Ok..
[S]  He was a history teacher.. He was.. he was newer than the other guys.. he was younger..
[L] Nice..
[S] And.. he came with this dynamic way of teaching, you know?
[L] Ok..
[S] Ya, and he taught history and I hated history because always was like memorizing numbers and dates and names etc.
[L]
[L] Yeah.. Yeah..
[S] Ya, and he taught history and I hated history because always was like memorizing numbers and dates and names etc.
[L] Sure
[S] But he made it interesting, he made it fun!
[L] Um..
[S] And I was.. wow.. that's interesting, that's nice
[S] But he made it interesting, he made it fun!
[L] Nice..
[S] Yeah, and I started to get more into the lecture and more into the class.. and it was interesting, was nice..
[S]  But.. then came the first exam..
[L] ok..
[S] And I failed..
[L] Oh.. ok.. ok.. that was unexpected
[S] Yeah, and I was like, wow
[S] Yeah, I was like.. Oh, wow, I was liking this, how this is possible, right?
[L] Oh.. ok.. ok.. that was unexpected
[L] Ok..
[S] Yeah, I was like.. Oh, wow, I was liking this, how this is possible, right?
[S] I was.. ok that's weird.. but the most amazing thing is that this guy came and talked to me..
[S] That was the first time that a teacher actually was.. involved with the well being of the students, you know?
[S] Yeah, is like come one to one and.. Yeah.. Yeah
[S] Exactly is like, wow.. that's interesting.. and then he came and talked to me.. and he was like, what's happening you are always in my class..
[S] Everything was nice, so something..
[S] Should happen there..
[L] Uh-huh
[S] And yeah.. I don't know.. I got unmotivated or something that.. but we talked a lot..
[S] Should happen there..
[S] And he actually motivated me to.. to do.. to do better, you know? To like more the lecture, but also do better..
[S] Then the second exam came.. And.. I failed it again
[L] Uh-huh..
[S] Yeah, I was like that's can not happen.. Come on.. I was finally liking something
[L] Yeah.. Yeah
[S] And then I get really negative reinforcement for failing the exam.. something is wrong with me, and then I became nervous and I became unsure about it, you know?
[L] Yeah
[L] Yeah.. Yeah
[S] And then I get really negative reinforcement for failing the exam.. something is wrong with me, and then I became nervous and I became unsure about it, you know?
[S] And then he came to talk to me again.. and yeah, it's normal, it's ok.. lets study better or try something
[L] Yeah.. Yeah
[S] And then I get really negative reinforcement for failing the exam.. something is wrong with me, and then I became nervous and I became unsure about it, you know?
[S] And then he came to talk to me again.. and yeah, it's normal, it's ok.. lets study better or try something
[S] And the next one would be the final exam so I..
[S]
[L] Oh..
[S] Had to pass this one..
[L] Ya
[S] And.. Yeah.. then..
[S] I started to study like a crazy person, you know? Really, really..
[L] Ok..
[S] Eating my books, yeah completely crazy, and I was..
[L] Yeah!
[L]
[S] Eating my books, yeah completely crazy, and I was..
[S] Very, very nervous..
[S] So nervous that the day before the exam I was having panic attacks..
[L] Oh..
[S] So was.. really, really like.. yeah could not breathe.. could not think properly
[L] Yeah
[L] Yeah.. yeah
[S] So was.. really, really like.. yeah could not breathe.. could not think properly
[S] And.. out of.. Uh.. anxiety.. out of desperation I came out with a idea
[S] Which would be to get some traps of paper write the.. names and dates and put in my sleeves
[L]
[L] Oh, you were planning on cheating
[S] Yeah!
[S] I was planning on cheating
[L] Oh, you were planning on cheating
[L] Ok..
[S] I was planning on cheating
[S] That's awful, right?
[L] Yeah.. Yeah
[S] In the day of the test I went there..
[S] I started doing the test with the.. with the.. with the cheating system
[S] It was working, I was answering the.. the.. all the.. yeah.. the questions properly
[L] Uh-huh.. uh-huh
[S] Probably when this was getting close to the end I started to feeling bad
[L] Oh, yeah.. yeah.. yeah
[S] You know? I started feeling like.. wow that's awful, why am I doing this?
[S] And then this guy came and talked to me.. person to person
[L] Um.. uh-huh
[S] You know? I can not break his trust now.. on that..
[L] Uh-huh.. uh-huh
[S] I started to feel disgusted with my self.. like, wow how can I do this to my self? You know?
[L] Yeah
[S] Then I handed the test, and I passed the lecture, but I kept this with me.. this strong, strong feeling of failure..
[L] Guilt.. Yeah
[S] Of guilt, strong guilt.. And this was the bottom for me, like wow I really did that.. that's awful
[L] Hmm.. Uh-huh
[S] And yeah, I carried this with me, my whole life.. and it was like.. was a milestone, you know? It's like yeah.. I could never do this again..
[L] Ah.. shit
[L] Uh-huh
[S] And yeah, I carried this with me, my whole life.. and it was like.. was a milestone, you know? It's like yeah.. I could never do this again..
[S] And I never did, hopefully.. Uh.. gladly
[L] Uh-huh
[L]
[S] And I never did, hopefully.. Uh.. gladly
[S] I hope I will never do
[L] Yeah..Yeah
[S]
[S] But yeah, was a really, really strong feeling on that.. on that day..
[L] I see it..