[S] So where were we before we were interrupted er.. rudely [L] Emily
[L]  [S] Emily, yes, Emily, so
[S] Emily moved away and that was a bit unfortunate kind of um.. [L] Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh
[S] I did start start to cope with that eventually after some point in time [L] Yep
[S] Ah.. I started to get very into music actually. Did you know that I, I can, I sing for a band [L] Um.. um
[L] I do know that, no, I do know that, that's cool [S] Well, I can sing at all  yeah
[S] So I did actually sing a bit er.. in a band
[S] I can tell you a bit about that kind of, so as I said, I did actually get quite into music kind of [L] Yeah, sure
[S] It was a kind of a coping mechanism, I guess, I don't know, cause she left [L] Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah
[S] Ah.. and I kind of nagged my parents like I wanted instruments kind of
[S] Had seen all these videos of people like playing instruments
[S] So and showing how to play chords, and I  it looked really cool [L] Okay, yeah
[L] Okay [S] So I nagged my parents for a guitar and stuff
[S] They didn't really fall for it kind of  [L] Uh-huh
[S] They wanted me to focus on other stuff kind of [L]
[S] So they just treated it as like a phase that I was going through and I would get over it eventually [L] Uh-huh, uh-huh, yeah
[S] And.. the best I could do to kind of convince them, was that when I was going to a..
[S] So this was it, when I was transitioning into high school kind of [L] Uh-huh
[S] Is that I convinced them to kind of send me to one of these kind of
[S] Special schools which had a big music like curriculum kind of, so it's like [L] Yeah, okay, yeah, that's nice
[S] They agreed as long as the school had like proper subjects like maths and like [L]  yeah
[S] Chemistry and stuff, so I could still get a proper education while I'm doing this kind of fluffier stuff [L] Yeah, okay.. yeah
[L] Fluffy  [S]  it is a bit fluffy, right?
[S] Uh yeah, so I did convince them to do it, to let me do that eventually, and I went to this school [L] Yeah
[S] I'd say it was a.. very good school kind of
[S] I enjoyed myself quite a lot there, like the teachers were good [L] Yeah
[S] The food was good, better than here  of course [L]  of course
[L] That's a very easy baseline  to beat [S] Yeah it's a low, it's a low bar
[S] It's a low bar  [L]
[S] Um but yeah so.. I had a great time there
[S] Well I really enjoyed school, I really enjoyed
[S] One thing I didn't like on school, is there was this one course
[S] It was called classical music theory [L] Okay
[S] And the reason I didn't like this course, there was this one teacher that we had and she was just..
[S] A really bad person, she was pretty awful
[S] She was like a demon in the shape of a human kind of  [L]
[S] Um and she used to be like, she used to yell a lot at students [L] Yeah
[S] Sometimes she used to like drag students by their ears kind of [L] Hmm.. hmm
[S] Like bordering on like slightly abusive, a bit on the abusive side, which isn't great
[L] Uh that's not good.. yeah, yeah [S] No, it's not good
[L] Yeah [S] Um.. and I actually did, I actually meet friends kind of, we went to the same, we went to the same class
[S] That she was holding kind of, so we kind of bonded over hating this one particular teacher kind of [L]
[S] She was so awful [L] Yeah, yeah
[S] Ah.. so yeah, but otherwise I, yeah I spent a lot of time with them
[S] And I like really enjoyed going to that school um..
[S] I continued for about one year into the school term kind of [L] Uh-huh, uh-huh
[S] Uh and then we were supposed to..
[S] So I wasn't, wasn't at the school for my entire school thing, and I'm gonna tell you why
[S] Because essentially after one year we had to give this presentation in classical music theory
[S] This is a mandatory course, so you know that you get your grade in your final exam [L] Ah, okay.. yeah
[S] You need to do this mandatory like classical music course [L] Okay, yeah, yeah, yea
[S] And there was this big presentation we were supposed to do in front of the class and everyone
[S] And in front of this teacher
[S] And I was terrified of doing this presentation, like it was, it was ah [L]
[S] It was, it was very uncomfortable kind of, partially I'm not, I wasn't a very outgoing person back then [L] Yeah
[S] I've become more outgoing over time, I don't know if you've noticed  um [L]
[S] But uh I wasn't very outgoing back then
[S] But now I'm er well like so it was stressful for me
[S] Ah and also I had to give in front of this teacher kind of [L] Hmm
[S] Who was like my nightmare kind of turned into a real person [L] Yeah. yeah, your, your demon
[S] Yeah, my, my own personal demon in some sense ah.. [L]  yeah
[S] So I prepared a lot for this, and I prepared slides, prepared to the talk and like
[S] Well I, I, when, the day, the day the presentation came, I gave the presentation [L] Uh-huh
[S] I thought I pretty well, I was pretty happy with it, people applauded, but then like [L] Uh-huh, yeah
[S] As soon as I was done like the teacher really started ripping into my presentation, it's like
[S] And this was wrong, this was awful, why did you say this, this was just not right
[S] And like I.. really, it was a really hard blow kind of [L] Sure
[S] Cause I was a little bit, I wasn't such a confident person to start with, kind of [L] Sure, yeah
[S] So it's like the fact that she kind of would rip into something that I'd done made me feel really bad [L] Yeah, yeah
[L]  yeah [S]  so I just went home to my parents and I was like a wreck kind of
[S] Like I told them like, look this is what happened, I'm really unhappy, can I go do something about this [L] Uh-huh, uh-huh
[L] Uh-huh [S] Um.. yeah so my parents came and we talked to the school about it
[L] Uh-huh [S] And then like we saw if we could do something about the teacher
[S] And then the school said no, basically the teacher is here to stay kind of
[S] We can't do anything to get rid of them kind of thing, so I was really uncomfortable [L]  oh, of course she can be (creepy?) that way
[S] Yeah, I mean, sometimes it's like, you need uh, with certain people
[S] Cause she was very important, she was on some boards, or some direction, or something like that, so I was very unfortunate [L] Okay.. okay.. okay
[L] Uh-huh [S] So we couldn't really get rid of her kind of
[S] Uh and this course was mandatory, and I just really didn't want to go this course with this person [L] Oh that's very sad
[S] Uh so we talked a bit and we came to the conclusion that we would still be okay if I kind of
[S] The thing we could do, because the normal high school kind of
[S] Had a lot of courses shared with this music school, so that I could transfer to this normal high school kind of [L] Yeah, okay
[S] And then just keep going.. um and finish my school curriculum there kind of [L] Okay.. wow
[L] Okay [S] Which was I thought like, sure as long as I get to avoid this person
[S] Cause like I don't, I can't handle this kind of [L] Yeah
[L] Cause you are intimidated by, by her [S] Yeah I was a very, I was a very fragile person, I'd say, back then kind of
[S] So it wasn't great for me to have to deal with that kind of
[S] Especially because you look up to people in positions of, in like this kind of, er.. [L] Yeah, yeah
[S] Teaching positions essentially, and so it's like [L] Yeah, sure
[S] When you, any criticism from them becomes very hurtful kind of [L] Uh-huh.. yeah, yeah
[S] Uh so I did eventually swap over to and complete my high school curriculum in this high school kind of
[S] And yeah it was a shame I had to leave but it was a lot less stressful when I transferred over to the normal school kind of
[S] And I, I missed out on some friends, but I made some new friends as well, so that was
[S] A bit of a shame but fine for me kind of er.. [L] But that's good I mean, you have supportive parents
[S] Yeah my parents have been very supportive along the way kind of, so yeah, always [L] Yeah, yeah
[S] So they were also pretty, they were probably pretty happy that I was transferred over to a more technical school as well [L] Yeah
[S] Kind of to be honest but [L]  yeah
[L] But uh in a new environment for you to start
[S] Yeah, new and, new and more stable environment for me kind of er, which was good [L] Yeah.. yeah, yeah
[S] So I did eventually graduate from high school, I went to college er..
[S] In a more, in a technical thing, in a more technical thing kind of [L] Uh-huh, uh-huh
[S] And when I went to this  it was more like a college
[S] I did actually meet up with on campus these other people I'd gone to what's it
[S] Well I met up with one other people, and then I, eventually we go out together for like a drink and kind of
[S] Uh.. and then I like, we talked at I, like college essentially, about like
[S] How it had been, gone, being for them and how much they still hated the teacher to this day kind of thing and um [L]
[L] In college? Okay [S] Yeah in college
[S] So then eventually we talked and chatted a bit and it's like
[S] They told me that they were still playing in this kind of, they'd made some kind of personal band
[S] And they were still playing with each other kind of, like oh that's cool
[S] And they asked hey would you enjoy to like play with us sometimes? What, me?
[S]  I was like, surprised that like they'd even want me like [L] Sure, sure
[S] And even remembered I could do anything kind of ah..
[S] So yeah and we got together and we played a bit to each other, we practiced a bit to each other
[S] And then after a couple of months we decided to eventually have like a
[S] We just had play over like just group of friends kind of um [L] Hmm
[L] That must be fun  [S] Yeah it was really great fun, I felt really like
[S] And I was the vocalist kind of, so I got to sing, and it's like, it was really liberating [L] Yeah
[S] And really cool to kind of just be able to let go and kind of enjoy [L] Yes, yeah, yeah
[S] So I really felt like I was like on the cloud, on clouds, on sky, on cloud nine kind of  [L] Sure
[S] Thing so that was uh was an amazing experience for me [L] Sure
[S] And that's kind of how I got into that, and I still chat with them now, to this day so [L] Nice, nice
[L] Nice, wow, hmm [S]  yeah