[S] So cool, where were we before we got rudely interrupted ah..
[S] Right, I was telling you a little bit about my friend, essentially she moved away
[S] Now, sometime after she moved away, I actually started to get more into music.
[S] Or like I guess I didn't listen a lot to music so I was I guess interested in the idea of playing an instrument cause I thought it was like a really cool thing, like would be a rock star-esque kind of thing
[S] Um.. so I pestered my parents for this
[S] Naturally, I don't really have a musical bone in my body. Are you a musician? Do you play any instruments?
[L] Yeah, I do, some. But not professionally.
[S]  just playing around
[L] Playing around, yeah. [S] Yeah, okay, fair enough.
[S] But uh yeah, I tried to pester them, I wanna try this guitar and stuff, I wanna do this, I wanna do that
[S] They just kind of, they didn't really believe in it much, they just kind of thought it was a phase, it would go over
[S] Hopefully be a bit cheaper if I didn't get into all of this stuff ah..
[S] So I pestered them for it and they didn't really buy me anything too exciting
[S] What they did eventually do for me is I managed to pester them into letting me go to a kind of a musical high school essentially
[S] Like where you could do all the normal subjects
[L] Yeah [S] But then you could like these extra like er musical courses on the side kind of to get deeper into it
[S] And I really enjoyed going to this school, kind of, I leaned a lot um..
[S] Um but there was one course I had a problem with and that was music theory
[S] And the reason I had a problem with was this course in particular is that there was this one teacher
[S] And I'm pretty sure she was some kind of a demon wearing the skin of a human kind of thing [L]
[S] It was pretty bad  like she was pretty evil um
[S] And just mean, and she used to drag kids around by the ears kind of and stuff like that
[S] So it was like really borderline not okay kind of stuff  um..
[S] And I actually did meet some friends when I went to this high school kind of
[S] Just and we all kind of just bonded around hating this particular woman kind of
[S] So it's a bit yeah it's a bit unfortunate but she was really not a great person kind of um
[S] So like we spent some, I spent some time there, I learned a lot kind of
[S] But then there was this one point in time where we had to give this presentation kind of
[S] We had to give this presentation in classical musical theory, given by this woman who was a bit evil um
[S] And I was really nervous because we were supposed to give this presentation around everybody kind of
[S] And I was partially nervous because I wanted to do a good job, get a good grade
[S] And partially because I was terrified of getting yelled at essentially like for being stupid or whatever um..
[S] So I did prepare a lot, I was very nervous. I did manage to give the talk, I gave the presentation.
[S] And I thought I'd done a good job, like everyone was clapping
[S] But then like she really laid into me after the talk like
[S] She really like went for me kind of  it was pretty bad like
[S] She said why did you do this? This wasn't right, this was wrong, you should've said this, you need to speak up more kind of
[S] And I was really like  I was pretty devastated after this
[S] Cause really it was very harsh critique, and a lot of it was mean spirited kind of
[S] So I, like I went home crying kind of
[S] And I told my parents like, look I can't be in this school with doing this teacher anymore
[S] Cause I needed like.. that course to pass and get my grades kind of, well get my exam
[S] But uh I also was gonna start to do things with this teacher
[S] And we had talked to the school about this teacher before, but we couldn't get rid of her kind of
[S] They just said like no there's nothing we can do really like, she's gonna stay is what we were basically told [L] Hmm
[S] So we did eventually manage to organize that I would be able to transfer into the normal schooling system
[S] Which shared some of the courses with this music school um..
[S] And I kind of finished my high school year, well years, while I was there kind of
[S] It was.. not ideal, I would have obviously have preferred to stay at the music school kind of
[S] I wasn't gonna stay there with her  not a chance, not a chance, yeah..
[S] So yeah, eventually I graduated kind of, and more, with a little bit more of technical focus at school um..
[S] Ended up in college and, when I got to college I actually did meet like the people I like eh that I went to music school with
[S] Cause they'd also gone there  um..
[S] And they kind of, I talked to them a bit and like..
[S] They said hey we're starting a band, do you wanna join? And I was like me?
[S] Like, really? Like yeah, we remember you used to be a pretty good vocalist kind of
[S] Wow, wow. Yeah, vocalist. So.. [L] Vocalist.
[S] Yeah eventually I said yeah, sure, I'd love to kind of like
[S] Cause I was really uh I still really liked music
[S] Yeah I just have kind of put it to one side essentially because such traumatic experiences basically  um..
[S] So like eventually not too long after I met them in college kind of we all decided to like go and hold this concert there
[S] So we had our first concert and like it went great I felt like I was on the cloud, walking on clouds kind of
[S] I felt like a god, it was amazing
[S] Yeah so eventually yeah that's what ended up, I eventually ended up as the vocalist in a band
[S] So yeah, pretty good  [S] Yeah, I'm amazed that I actually got there kind of, I thought it was over, but yeah
[S]  Yeah, that was a great experience. [L] Yeah, it was, probably.