[S] how's your weekend being?
[L] pretty good and yours?
[S] hanging in there ..  yeah no everything is alright I'd say uh.. ok so today I'm gonna tell you two stories about myself kind about my past my childhood so
[L]
[S] first of would you say that you're an introvert?
[L] uh.. not really
[S] no? 'cause I am definitely very introverted kinda I've been that way since I was a child uh.. I used to play a lot of video games on my own when I was young
[L] ok
[S] kid uh.. I was a bit lonely but did kinda.. I still kind of enjoyed myself I didn't hate being alone just by playing video games by myself um..
[S] and that was.. I was like that during most of my youth actually this changed a bit when I did eventually move to Sweden when I moved to Sweden? I think I moved to Sweden at the age of
[L] uh-huh
[S] eleven or twelve I moved to Sweden I think  be a bit perhaps more introverted there 'cause I also didn't speak the language when I first got there I moved from South Africa to Sweden
[S] so I only knew English at that time and.. so it did actually take me a while to kinda meet people.. one of the first people I met and who became a very good friend of mine for a while was
[S] this girl uh.. she was going to my class when I started school kinda of in Sweden and then I met this girl she was in my class essentially and I really admired her 'cause she was very like
[L] uh-huh
[S] outgoing and independent and she was very funny and she like.. uh.. she was just very like brave with and I was very shy and like withdrawn kind of
[L]
[S] um.. but yeah so.. we spent uh.. and she also spoke English which was a great help kinda 'cause I didn't speak a word in Swedish at the time
[S] uh.. but yeah so we did spend a lot of time we watched a lot of cartoons played some video games kind of we also used to spend.. got to a bit slightly more mischievous things kind of one thing that we'd do
[L] uh-huh
[S] this um.. do you know these kind of places where they keep planks before they process them for.. to make furniture kinda so they have these big like yards with planks around
[L] yeah..
[S] 'cause me and her lived actually very close to one of these yards kinda so what we'd do is it we kinda of sneak in there and we kinda of steal planks kinda from the place  and what we'd do with these planks is we kind
[L]
[S] and take the planks and build them into like go karts essentially so we kind of nailed it together put some wheels on it kind of like put in..  add things we added an extra seat we added a trunk
[S] kind of uh.. and then we added some (spoils?) to make it go faster or something I don't know we were kids  we just thought it was cool uh.. and what we would do is once we build this thing we had
[L]
[L] yeah
[S] kind of uh.. and then we added some (spoils?) to make it go faster or something I don't know we were kids  we just thought it was cool uh.. and what we would do is once we build this thing we had
[S] we had like this sloping like.. hill next to my house which was asphalted like this asphalted sloping.. slope next to my house
[L] uh-huh
[S] what we'd do is that we'd take this go kart and then put in to the top of a hill and then someone's in the go kart and it would kind of roll down the hill kind of, does it sound like a good idea?
[L] well this is something I would do yes
[S] yes  interesting because what happened was that.. this was very fun right but I did get pretty hurt at some point in time like one day by doing this
[L] oh no
[S] particularly 'cause we got this thing to the top of the hill alright so  we took it to the  top of the hill then I sat in it and then normally we'd just let it roll down but this time she kinda
[S] pushed me down like with the speed so I was like trying to hold down as I'm going down the hill really fast and I was like bobbling and this thing turned and flipped kinda and the thing is I was still in this right? 'cause my leg
[L]
[S] was still inside the go kart and then like the  of my body was outside the kart so what happened was while I was like.. while I it was going down the hill kind of I had.. it kinda flipped and then I had to kinda brace I could only brace with the right side of
[S] my body so I had to brace against the asphalt with the right side of my body and I had to skied a bit kind of and I got.. I really  off my (little?) skin on my arm kind of and I got very bloody
[L] uh-huh
[S] I was like screaming and completely out of it and she was screaming and I was crying and then she had to run off and get my dad kind of because I was just a bloody mess it was pretty bad
[L]
[S] um.. yeah.. it was uh.. I don't regret it kinda 'cause it's like those kinds of experiences that you remember kind
[S] of the stupid things you do when you were a kid right? uh.. but I did like really.. it was a good time kind I did enjoy being with her specially 'cause she really did like help me go out and do all this stupid
[L] yeah
[S] things like.. it sadly didn't last for too long 'cause I had know her for a couple of months like about half a year or so
[L]
[L] uh-huh
[S] things like.. it sadly didn't last for too long 'cause I had know her for a couple of months like about half a year or so
[S] and then she eventually let me know that she.. her dad had gotten a job in Asia essentially so that means that her and her family had to move kinda.. and this
[S] really worried me kind of 'cause I was obviously like still a bit fragile and like.. uh.. so I was a bit scared of losing a friend kind of I was afraid o being lonely uh.. we exchanged phone numbers kinda
[S] kinda so we could call each other when she moved uh.. this didn't really work kinda so I tried to call her and just couldn't like get through I guess Swedish sim cards didn't work too well and this was a bit before
[S] like the whole social media thing so we couldn't really get in touch that way either um.. so we kinda lost contact for a while we lost contact for
[S] quite a long time I think about five years eventually she did contact me again kinda she contact me over Facebook once it had become a thing and we got back in touch and I was like wow
[L] uh-huh
[S] you're still alive that's amazing um.. but yes and we talked a bit kind of we talked about the past, what we're doing currently and stuff like that um..
[L]
[S] and there's one thing I did notice that definitely we both had changed quite a lot kind of while she had changed more than I had she was very.. much more mature at this point in time uh..
[S] so we talked but like these messages got shorter and shorter we were very different people we didn't have that much in common anymore um.. so eventually this conversation just kind of
[L] uh-huh
[S] died out and unfortunately we haven't really talked since then kind of.. so yeah unfortunate hm
[L] I guess it happens
[S] yeah people grow.. people grow and mature
[L] yes