[S] Hey, how are you doing?
[L] Yeah, good.
[S] How has been for you?
[L] Ah everything is great.
[S] Ah, do you like traveling?
[L] Yeah I like traveling.
[S] Yeah I like traveling a lot but ah..
[S] ah.. I have issues with beeing traveling. Do you have that issue as well?
[L] um
[S] I always feel that I'm really scared when I'm boarding a flight.
[L] Yeah, I'm with you.
[S] See, It's safe but It's not safe.
[L] Yeah.
[S] Um.. I've always suspected that things will go wrong and I never had experienced but...
[S] Quite recently as a week before
[S] I actually was traveling to Brussels
[S] Normally what I would do I take a train from Hamburg and then I go there
[S] But ah..
[S] I got this really cheap flight on (company name?) and I thought why not try this..
[L]
[S] One fifth or one sixth of the journey time
[L] uh-huh
[S] So  do It
[S] Funny thing was that I didn't notice that the flight when I was looking for
[S] I didn't pay attention to it that the flight was at the night. It's just fine for me, work fine for me.
[S] Ah.. but as it turned out ah..
[S] It was started at ten. Do you know the airports in Europe closes at ten thirty or ?
[L] Yeah.
[S] It pretty was the last flight. Um..
[L] Hmm
[S] Um.. So I went to the airport Is was pretty much dark everywhere
[S] It pretty was the last flight. Um..
[S] It was.. You know Hamburg weather of rain a bit of a storm was going on
[S] Um..  the airport the was a huge queue for check in
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Uh Apparently there were many flights going at that time because of the storm. There were flight delayed.
[S] Somehow I had to go to the check in process because I had some luggage
[S] Took me a lot of time for that to happen just banished to reach the flight before it actually took off uh..
[S] Before the boarding started of the boarding ended uh..
[L] uh-huh
[S] We boarded an you know
[S] Before the boarding started of the boarding ended uh..
[S] It's not the boarding with the bridge on it, so you have to get down and get into a bus
[L] uh-huh
[L] Yes
[S] And that's... I hate that.
[L] A shuttle bus.
[S] And the bus actually goes to the plane and as we  the plane is a very small plane
[L] Uh-huh
[S] It's a seventy seater
[S] with a propellers fans. I don't like those planes because of the propeller
[S] I'm always really scared of it. I like the  ones. It's pretty more secured.. I think in my head.
[S] So It's a really small plane, the whether is a bit storming, the propellers.. Everything for me went wrong at that point of time.
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Um.. We boarded, we boarded the plane uh..
[S] Seventy of us somehow.. It's a really (glen?) place.. really small
[L]
[S] We boarded the plane and then there was a announcement that the weather is too bad
[S] Did you see that before?
[L]
[S] The weather is bad and then there is a delay
[L] Yeah.
[S] And (didn't know?) when they will be clear to fly.
[L] Uh-huh
[S] It turns that we waited for one hour in the plane sitting at the tarmac.
[S] The plane didn't start because of the bad weather. And in my head I'm like this is the worse experience (already?) .
[L] Yeah.
[S] I was sited in a plane for one hour you know.. They don't even switched on the AC or something, we were just waiting.. It's just bad.
[S] The plane didn't start because of the bad weather. And in my head I'm like this is the worse experience (already?) .
[L]
[S] I was sited in a plane for one hour you know.. They don't even switched on the AC or something, we were just waiting.. It's just bad.
[L] Yeah.
[S] Um.. Then after one hour so you can even decide I don't want to fly anymore and go out, because they won't let you out anymore.
[L]
[S] So somehow I.. We sat through and I thought okay let's see how it goes.
[S] Um.. Then after one hour so you can even decide I don't want to fly anymore and go out, because they won't let you out anymore.
[S] Uh.. After one hour as said they announced that we could fly now.
[S] Um.. So the plane somehow went to the runway and took off. The took off was too shaky because of the wind.
[S] As soon as we (reached?) a bit higher they never switched off the seat belt sign, so you would always had to keep it
[S] As soon as we (reached?) a bit higher uh..
[S] It started tumbling  I was at the window I could see that there was lightning at our site there was flashes.
[S] Pretty scary that experience.
[S] And then with the thumbing and with the turbulence happening suddenly the lights went off the airplane
[L] Uh
[S] Uh.. All the emergency lights went on and we were told that we should not panic that it happens
[L]
[S] But in my head things are going crazy because I'm thinking I'm going to die now um..
[S] It's really scary, isn't it?
[S] What happened (eventually?) was that uh..
[S] after five minutes of the lights off and people talking  and telling as to be calm and everything will be calm
[L]
[S] The oxygen masks drop off because the plane actually had this three hundred feet fall or something suddenly
[L] Uh-huh
[S] The oxygen masks fall down and panicking
[S] The oxygen masks drop off because the plane actually had this three hundred feet fall or something suddenly
[S] Because the first thing that happened to me.. you think you are prepared for that but when it actually  happen you are really scared
[S] So I'm not able to put the mask on my face and I can't breath because the plane kind of had a (deep?)
[S] And It's getting really troubling for me so the guy sitting next to me actually helped me to put on the mask so I could breath un..
[L] Yeah.
[L]
[S] And It's getting really troubling for me so the guy sitting next to me actually helped me to put on the mask so I could breath un..
[S] But then again after the mask was on the lights was still off and
[S] The.. the flashes outside the lightning outside you see this flashes of lightning coming in
[S] With all of us with the mask and this propeller plane doing
[S] This was so scary I mean this was a scariest experience. After like twenty minutes of this happening and with the masks on suddenly if became smother
[S] (when we was?) closer to our destination it started to became... they would probably flying in a different altitude or something to do that um..
[L]
[S] Yeah, so then we turned off the mask  we took it off and we had lading
[S] Lading was bumping It was not  lading and everything
[L]
[S] Uh.. Probably one of the worst flights experiences of my life
[S] Um.. Something that I've always believed that something like that would happen um..
[L] Yeah.
[S] That feeling  and the pane was falling I felt it really low
[S] Um.. Something that I've always believed that something like that would happen um..
[S] because it fells like you are dying and you can't breath because the oxygen is getting low pretty much we are falling
[L] Yeah.
[S] Ah.. It was scary. I appreciate the pilot was able to manager all of that
[S] but for me I would probably never (fly this flight?)
[L] Um..
[S] I would check which flight is (used to tell?) is it a propeller plane or something? I think  I hated
[S] but for me I would probably never (fly this flight?)
[S] On my way back I'd booked a flight already but i canceled the flight, I didn't take the flight
[L]
[S] I took this long train because, well at least that's a train
[S] The chances of we dying is significantly less perhaps or something
[L]
[S] Uh Really even a  I have this goosebumps because of this crazy experience.
[L] Uh-huh
[S] It probably scared me for life for flights
[S] I may be scared with the flights for now on.
[S] Yeah that's so scary scary experience.
[L]