[S] So we meet again [L] Uh-huh
[L] Yeah, meet again
[S]  how are you?
[L] I'm great
[S] Have a good week so far?
[L] Yes hmm [S] Yeah, fantastic
[S]  Yeah so today I'm gonna tell you a bit more about myself
[S] You got to hear a bit about more, uh you got to hear a bit about me before
[S] But now you're gonna get uh a bit more
[S] And you know that I'm in a band?
[L] Yes, I know
[S] You did know that I'm in a band  impressive um  [L] Yeah, I know
[S] Yeah so actually a big fan of music, do you like music? [L] Uh-huh
[L] Yeah, I like music
[S] Okay, cool cool [L] Very much
[S] Uh.. cause I actually do like music quite a lot [L] Uh-huh
[S] And actually after I moved to Sweden, I really got into it
[S] Kind of really got into this whole like aesthetic line of stuff kind of and.. [L] Uh-huh
[S] I did actually nag my parents like I want to get a guitar, kind of want to get all this stuff [L] Uh-huh
[S] And um they.. don't take it very seriously  [L] Yeah
[S] Um what happened kind of was like I wanted to get this guitar and stuff [L] Hmm
[S] So they no they said it was just a phase and it would go over
[L] Uh-huh
[S] But I never really gave up kind of I kept trying to convince them to get me things
[S] The the best I could do kind of is that eventually when we were going to chose like um.. [L] Uh-huh
[S] Kind of upper high school, then I'm I wanted to go to music school kind of [L] Uh-huh
[S] Um so I nagged them and eventually they said that okay fine
[S] Sure you can go to this music school as long as you can read all this other subjects kind of [L] Uh-huh
[S] Uh eventually I  I kind of uh essentially did kind of give up on this point [L] Uh-huh
[S] So I'd go where I wanted  [L]
[S] Uh so I was really excited to go to this school kind of and the school was really amazing
[S] I learned a lot while I was there
[S] The only problem I had really was with the classical theory, classical like music theory [L] Uh-huh
[S] Which is like learning about different uh kind of  uh to play different things [L] Yeah.. uh-huh
[S] And like how the history of music is also is a big part of that [L] Uh-huh
[S] Um so I had a little trouble with that cause, mostly because of the teacher
[S] And the teacher was a really like.. I was pretty sure  she was a demon in the shape of a person [L] Uh-huh
[S] Kind of she was just an awful human being um.. and uh she was really bad [L]
[S] I did manage to make friends because of that though because what happened was that  [L] Uh-huh
[S] I met four other guys who kind of also hated  we kind of developed a friendship over hating her together kind of [L] Uh-huh  yeah
[S] which was great um.. yeah so that went on I went on like really enjoying like [L] Uh-huh
[S] Learning how to play music and learning a lot about musical theory as well as doing other courses
[S] Uh.. while still hating this one teacher because she was really an awful human being kind of
[S] Er.. and yeah so that kept going on and eventually at some point in time what happened was that we had to give this..
[S] Presentation in classical music theory.. and I was, like and it was supposed to be a presentation around the entire class [L] Uh-huh
[S] And I was.. really stressing out about this like  [L] Uh-huh
[S] I studied a lot, I was very nervous cause, partially because I wanted to good and do alright [L] Uh-huh
[S] And.. but then also because like I was so scared of this teacher and what she would say cause she was obviously judging me [L] Uh-huh, yeah
[S] Um.. so I went up and I gave my presentation and for a moment  a really good job
[S] People applauded but then she really like tore into my work
[S] Like everything I presented she said that this was wrong, why did you say this [L] Uh-huh
[S] You need to speak up more, you didn't due well. And like her criticism was really like harsh and mean [L] Uh-huh
[S] It was really like bitter criticism so like
[S] I really  couldn't handle it, I started to cry a bit when she  [L]
[S] When she started to be like be so cruel to me and I, I just..
[S] I got home, I cried a lot, I talked to my parents and I said look
[L] Like this isn't going to work, I can't go to a school where I have to be with this teacher and she's really just an awful person [L] Uh-huh
[S] Cause we talked to the school about this teacher before and like really they said that basically she's there to stay [L] Uh-huh
[S] So we couldn't do anything about it
[S] So like I.. we basically just, eventually I had to just swap schools
[S] Kind of because like we, I couldn't stay there, I needed that class to pass  [L] Uh-huh
[S] What happened was because the school shared some courses with the main school, I could swap over to the main school kind of [L] Uh-huh
[S] And ontinue my education there and that kind of worked, and it was okay [L] Yeah.. that's right
[S]  I would've preferred to stay at the main than where I was you know [L]  yeah
[S] The music well, but with that teacher it just didn't work
[S] So time goes on kind of, I go to college  [L] Uh-huh
[S] And lo and behold like the people, I er.. I go to college and then I meet these kind of four people I was friends with during this school, music school  [L] Uh-huh.. hmm
[S] I didn't keep in contact with, that much with them after that, which is cool I got to meet them again [L] Yeah, that's right.. uh-huh, yeah.. uh-huh
[S] Um, but the prob, it was good to  meet them again
[S] We just talked a bit and like.. they were still really into music [L] Hmm
[S] And I was like, I was listening to music, I hadn't played or done anything serious with music for a while [L] Uh-huh
[S]  we eventually decided like yeah we should start a band  [L] Uh-huh
[S] Or like they suggested it to me that I should join the band  kind of cause they were already playing with each other  [L]
[S] So I joined as the vocalist and they kind of all, they were drums er.. [L] Uh-huh
[S] Bass guitar, guitar, yeah stuff like that
[S] Um.. yeah so actually we played a bit
[S] And then eventually we had our first show and it was like, it was really amazing
[S] And like when we were performing, I felt so free and so happy kind of  [L] Yeah
[S] It was really a great experience
[L] Uh-huh [S] And er it was really nice I could meet these guys and do that stuff with them
[S] So yeah.. glad to have you back, see you around [L] Yeah, that's cool
[S]  that's how it happened  [L] Yeah.. nice