[S] Okay, great where were we before we were interrupted..uh..hmm..
[S] Okay  so after my friend left for Asia..just a week after she had left I was bit down in the dumps kind of I didn’t really..I..
[S] it’s just  I was friend and he has a kind of way to distract myself in some sense ah..so I started to get a little into music..kind of, ah..do you like music?
[L] Yeah, I love music.
[S] ah, very good  cause, i got really into music, kinda and I really wanted my parents to buy me an instrument kind of like a guitar or something
[S] so it kind of ah..kind of  get my..get it out..kinda get it out of my system
[S] ah..my parents viewed it more as a kind of phase essentially which is something I was going for, so they did kind of ignore me in then some regard to a large extent
[S] kind of they just thought it would pass but  but I just kept nagging them so it was like.. it became a bit of a balance there
[S] The closest I could get was eventually I convinced them to send me to a music oriented high school kind of once I had graduated from middle school essentially
[S] so essentially they allowed me to go to this kind of more..with ah..a high school with a more emphasis on music, if I..could also go and attend like normal, real classes there kinda
[S] and not just these weird musical classes. And that worked great kind of. This was very nice.
[S] I had a lot of fun there, the food was good, a bit  uh  uh..so..yeah I know really enjoyed going to school there.
[S] but there was a one thing I..one problem..one major problem I had with that school, there was this one mandatory course, called ah classical music theory
[L]
[S] and, the problem with this course was I ..I am pretty sure the teacher was like a kind of demon in the shape of a human kind of.
[S] She was pretty awful. She used to really yell at students and belittle them like drag students around by the ear and stuff, it was pretty bad.
[L]
[S] Ah..and I really did..did not like this teacher . She was pretty awful.
[S] Ah the good thing was that..I actually met a couple of people like me and some more students who took her class and I essentially bonded with these four guys kind of
[S] We just hating this particular teacher because she was just such an awful human being, kind of . Ah..which was interesting .
[S] But, yeah, and that continued on for about a year, I went to this school, kind of I really enjoyed myself.
[S] After one year essentially we had to give this presentation on Classical music theory in front of the entire class and I was very nervous about this.
[S] Cause I was still very shy and uh shy kind of as a person at that point and so partially just having to present in front of the entire class was a problem
[S] and then the fact that I had to present in front of this teacher was which I was just terrified of ..she was just evil .
[S] Ah..so I did spend a lot of time like practicing and preparing for this and I rehearsed and I kind of..
[L]
[S] Well I felt fairly confident so I went up and I gave the presentation and people laughed and they, you know, applauded once I was done.
[S] I thought I had done a really good job and uh..but once I done the teacher really like laid in to my presentation like
[S] “No, this was wrong! Why did you say this? You can’t mean this. Why did you do this?  Can you just speak louder?” it’s like
[S] and I was really like distraught after this kind of cause I was a very fragile person so I actually had to go like  I basically cried essentially
[S] and I went back home and told my parents like - “Look I can’t deal with this..kind of..this is too much for me.”
[S] Um..so we had to go have a talk with the school kind of and see if we could do anything about it.
[S] But like the school said that basically - “she’s on a bunch of boards. We can’t get rid of her. So she’s basically there to stay”.
[S] Uh..and I couldn’t just deal with her anymore because like it was a mandatory course, sure, but I couldn’t handle her for another two years..
[S] uh..so eventually we discussed..like um..we decided to send me to..like this musical high school shared a lot of courses with a normal high school essentially
[S] so i could transfer over to the normal high school, without like it impacting my studies too much.
[S] And my parents were also happy I was back to a more technical  subject as well so uh..yeah
[S] I eventually went to the normal high school and finished my curriculum there. It was a shame I couldn’t finish at the musical school, but  . Life .
[S] Yeah um I did actually meet up with one of the guys that I went to the musical school when I went to college essentially
[S] so once I went to college I met up with..I..all five of them. It went quite well. The guys were in the corridor..I said “hey, how are you doing?”
[S] And we talked a bit  said “Ah, we’re still playing in this band kind of..uh..with these other four guys”..I had  to earlier on.
[S] And then he said like “ah you should join us sometime. It would be fun!”  it’s like “ah..yeah, yeah. I remember you are good at singing ”. Like really? um, okay .
[S] So I actually uh..sing for them essentially as a vocalist. I did sing, and we played there and we practiced a bit kind of and eventually we arranged to have a bit of a like concert for..um
[S] some of our friends..and um..close friends and stuff and it’s like..no, it was a really good experience.
[S] Cause like when we had that concert I really felt like I was alive kinda I really felt like I was on cloud nine. It was a great experience.
[S] Ah..yeah so that was..yeah..so that’s how I kind of got to sing in the band and still keep in touch with them .