[S] everything good how's your holiday been?.. weekend been sorry
[L] uh.. I think it was fine.. I traveled a lot
[S] ok ok yeah I'm..
[S] just hanging around here  oh yeah you traveled yeah makes sense uh.. ok so today I'm gonna tell you two stories uh.. about me and my past
[L]
[L] yeah
[S] just hanging around here  oh yeah you traveled yeah makes sense uh.. ok so today I'm gonna tell you two stories uh.. about me and my past
[L] uh-huh
[S] uh.. so first of.. would you say you're an introvert?
[L] ok
[L] no, I don't think so
[S] yeah? ok 'cause I'm very introverted  believe it or not uh.. I was a lot more  when I was young essentially uh.. specially when I was growing up in South Africa
[L]  ok ok
[L] ok
[S] yeah? ok 'cause I'm very introverted  believe it or not uh.. I was a lot more  when I was young essentially uh.. specially when I was growing up in South Africa
[S] I spent a lot of time on my own kind I played a lot of PC games on my on I wouldn't say I was sad about this I kind of enjoyed being on my on
[L] uh-huh.. ok
[L] uh-huh
[S] I spent a lot of time on my own kind I played a lot of PC games on my on I wouldn't say I was sad about this I kind of enjoyed being on my on
[S] quite a lot essentially I was kinda comfortable with my own company so to speak uh.. that was kind of.. that was kind of very nice for me.. make me see (my?) very (repeat?) was mainly
[L] uh ok.. uh-huh
[S] very reclusive kind of.. didn't always want be with other people 'cause I just enjoyed being on my own kinda  and this remained constant throughout most of my childhood actually uh..
[L] ok.. ok.. uh-huh
[S] it did sorta change once I moved to Sweden which I did at the age of eleven.. twelve I think it's when I moved to Sweden  (as if?) you would know
[L] yeah
[L]  yeah
[S] it did sorta change once I moved to Sweden which I did at the age of eleven.. twelve I think it's when I moved to Sweden  (as if?) you would know
[S]  uh.. but I moved to Sweden at the age of around eleven or twelve I was still very like I was even more reclusive right? 'cause we moved to a new country  language kind of I didn't really
[L]  yeah
[L] yeah that's true.. yeah I can understand that
[S]  uh.. but I moved to Sweden at the age of around eleven or twelve I was still very like I was even more reclusive right? 'cause we moved to a new country  language kind of I didn't really
[S] have any contact with anyone I used to know from South Africa so.. It took me a while to meet new friends essentially one of the first friends I met was actually a girl
[L] uh-huh yeah
[S] so I started of in middle in uh.. low to middle school kind and I met this one girl and she was very different.. from me quite a lot 'cause she was very
[L] middle? ok uh-huh
[S] very outgoing kinda very independent very friendly and she spoke English which helped quite a lot right?
[L] ok uh-huh
[L] yeah but that's opposite
[S] yeah it's kinda the opposite of me opposites attract or something  yeah but uh.. she.. I really liked her kinda she was kinda I really admired her kind of for
[L] ok  ok
[L] uh-huh
[S] yeah it's kinda the opposite of me opposites attract or something  yeah but uh.. she.. I really liked her kinda she was kinda I really admired her kind of for
[S] being so like brave and outgoing kinda I thought that was amazing uh.. and we spent a lot of time together so we watched a lot of like cartoons together and we played a lot of video games together and stuff uh..
[L] ok.. uh-huh
[L] oh ok.. uh-huh
[S] being so like brave and outgoing kinda I thought that was amazing uh.. and we spent a lot of time together so we watched a lot of like cartoons together and we played a lot of video games together and stuff uh..
[S] and it was really cool to get to hang around someone like that and we got on to a lot of mischief there was actually this one thing that we did both of us lived very close to this
[L] ok.. uh-huh
[S] kind of lumbered mill processing place it's where they kept all the planks before they made like furniture essentially so they stored all the planks there so me and her would actually sneak in there and steal some planks kinda
[L] uh ok ok.. what?
[S]  uh.. and what we would do is we would kind of build a go kart we were building this go kart essentially so in the weekends we would kind of like build it together and put some wheels on it we added seats
[L] ok
[L] ok.. oh ok.. uh-huh
[S]  uh.. and what we would do is we would kind of build a go kart we were building this go kart essentially so in the weekends we would kind of like build it together and put some wheels on it we added seats
[S] kind of a trunk and then we had some (spoilers?) on the back to make it go faster I don't know what we were thinking we were kids so  bit of  yeah  but what
[L] ok.. oh ok.. uh-huh
[L] ok.. uh-huh.. yeah ok
[S] kind of a trunk and then we had some (spoilers?) on the back to make it go faster I don't know what we were thinking we were kids so  bit of  yeah  but what
[L] ok
[S] we did with this we would roll it down this.. next to my house there was this kind of asphalted hill essentially so there was this kind of hill  to my house and we would take
[L] uh ok
[S] the go kart to the top of this hill and I'd sit in the go kart and we would roll down
[L]
[L] ok so (they're?) Jack and Jill
[S] something like that perhaps a bit less safe than Jack and Jill perhaps 'cause this didn't sound like a very good idea right to sit in this thing and roll it down the hill
[L]  ok  ok yeah..
[L] it can (tilt?)
[S] didn't have a seat belt
[L] yeah
[S] (after?) all the features we added  uh.. but uh.. so one day I did actually get pretty hurt like uh.. riding this thing so what we were doing was  say we took it to the top of the hill someone sit
[L] ok uh-huh
[L] ok.. ok
[S] (after?) all the features we added  uh.. but uh.. so one day I did actually get pretty hurt like uh.. riding this thing so what we were doing was  say we took it to the top of the hill someone sit
[S] and we let it roll it down kinda and one day we took it to the top of the hill I sat in the go kart and then what would happen is she actually
[L] ok.. ok
[L] uh-huh
[S] and we let it roll it down kinda and one day we took it to the top of the hill I sat in the go kart and then what would happen is she actually
[S] my friend actually she really pushed me very hard down the hill and then it was going down the hill like really fast
[L] pushed you too hard! uh..
[S] and stuff
[L] ok and then it tilted or?
[S] yeah it tilted, curved and then tilted kind of over and I was still in the track 'cause my leg was still in the.. in the kart I couldn't really get my legs out kinda so I had to brace with the right side of my body
[L] ok
[L] ok.. oh shit
[S] yeah it tilted, curved and then tilted kind of over and I was still in the track 'cause my leg was still in the.. in the kart I couldn't really get my legs out kinda so I had to brace with the right side of my body
[S] essentially so I landed on like the asphalt and I kinda of skied the couple of feet I really tore up my arm kind there was a lot of skin there was a lot of blood it was pretty.. it was
[L] oh my god.. oh shit.. ok
[S] pretty bad um.. I was just screaming I was a mess kind of  I was screaming and crying and bleeding and she was screaming and crying and she had to run off
[L]
[S] and get my dad kind of like pick me up 'cause he was (out?) in the backyard working uh..  it was a traumatic experience and needless to say the go kart got
[L] oh my god.. ok ok
[L] wow
[S] and get my dad kind of like pick me up 'cause he was (out?) in the backyard working uh..  it was a traumatic experience and needless to say the go kart got
[S] thrown out after that
[L] yeah of course and your parent must've been  out of that
[S] yeah they didn't enjoy.. they didn't think it was a good.. they weren't happy with me doing that uh.. but I don't really regret it was obviously a very stupid idea but that's the
[L] yeah.. yeah ok
[S] kind of stuff that you remember as you get older
[S] yeah that's true we do stupid sh.. stuff
[S] yeah it's the kind of
[S] kind of stuff that you remember as you get older
[S] yeah that's true we do stupid sh.. stuff
[S] yeah it's the kind of
[S] yeah  stupid stuff uh..
[L] as we're growing up.. yeah it's funny  not doing that
[S] yeah .. exactly.. something you can tell your grand kinds kind of thing  yeah but uh.. yeah so that was some of the stuff that we got up to and I really enjoyed spending time with this girl
[L] yeah.. exactly
[L] uh-huh
[S] yeah .. exactly.. something you can tell your grand kinds kind of thing  yeah but uh.. yeah so that was some of the stuff that we got up to and I really enjoyed spending time with this girl
[L] uh-huh..
[S] uh.. it sadly didn't last for that long unfortunately because after about.. I'd know her for about six or seven months at that point in time
[L] uh-huh.. uh-huh
[S] uh.. she told me that her family was moving away to Asia her dad had gotten a job essentially so she was going to move and this was a bit of a shock for me obviously
[L] oh.. ok
[S] because I just met this uh.. new friend kind it's very  it makes you very.. yeah you're with a low self esteem right? you're already a bit scared and fragile right?
[L] yeah of course
[L] yeah .. yeah.. yeah that's true and then?
[S] because I just met this uh.. new friend kind it's very  it makes you very.. yeah you're with a low self esteem right? you're already a bit scared and fragile right?
[S] and then someone like that was very important kind of just disappears this anchor in this new place it's kinda this rock that you've clung to it like disappeared
[L] yeah .. yeah.. yeah that's true and then?
[L] yeah that's true uh-huh
[S] and then someone like that was very important kind of just disappears this anchor in this new place it's kinda this rock that you've clung to it like disappeared
[S] and you have to kinda deal with that, that was very difficult for me as a child kind of I felt like very alone and a bit abandoned maybe we did exchange phone numbers to try to keep in touch 'cause
[L] yeah that's true uh-huh
[L] yeah.. uh-huh
[S] and you have to kinda deal with that, that was very difficult for me as a child kind of I felt like very alone and a bit abandoned maybe we did exchange phone numbers to try to keep in touch 'cause
[S] this was bit before social media and stuff uh.. but when I tried to call her when she got in there she didn't like apparently she couldn't answer apparently Swedish SIM cards didn't work that well in
[L] uh ok.. yeah
[S] Asia kind of thing um.. so we lost contact for a while kind of uh.. for about five years I think.. eventually yeah
[L] uh ok.. yeah.. hm
[L] uh-huh.. wow that's a long time
[S] Asia kind of thing um.. so we lost contact for a while kind of uh.. for about five years I think.. eventually yeah
[S] it's a pretty long time she did get in contact five years later via Facebook I was pretty surprised.. Yeah I was pretty surprised when she showed up  because uh..
[L] ok.. uh that's nice
[L] five years is a long time
[S] it's a pretty long time she did get in contact five years later via Facebook I was pretty surprised.. Yeah I was pretty surprised when she showed up  because uh..
[S] yeah.. I mean I think it's just kind of a whim kinda she was connecting to people and she saw me as a suggestion like ah this guy and I was pretty surprised when I got a message from her it was like wow you still exist
[L] five years is a long time
[L] .. ok
[S] yeah.. I mean I think it's just kind of a whim kinda she was connecting to people and she saw me as a suggestion like ah this guy and I was pretty surprised when I got a message from her it was like wow you still exist
[S] it's amazing kind of thing uh.. so we chatted for a while we talked about who we were what we were doing at the moment like old stuff
[L] .. ok
[L] uh ok.. uh-huh
[S] it's amazing kind of thing uh.. so we chatted for a while we talked about who we were what we were doing at the moment like old stuff
[S] we talked for a while but I eventually (realized?) she changed quite a lot as a person and I guess so did I right it's been five years
[L] uh ok.. uh-huh
[L] yeah of course and she traveled and stuff
[S] yeah she traveled and stuff so she obviously been.. she changed a lot and I changed a lot so the conversation it started of like fairly enthusiastic but as time went on It kind of like  out
[L] uh-huh.. uh ok
[S] and then towards the end it really like.. there were very short responses and like she wasn't very enthusiastic uh.. and after while we just kind of stopped talking which is a shame
[S] and I haven't really heard from her since then but I guess it's part of growing up and people change essentially is that people change and you..
[L] yeah.. hm
[L] I think so too I think separate sections of life have separate relationships and as you're evolving then the relationships are also evolving with you so.. so it makes
[S] lose touch with them
[S] yeah.. yeah yeah precisely
[L] I think so too I think separate sections of life have separate relationships and as you're evolving then the relationships are also evolving with you so.. so it makes
[L] kind of sense  I think only really really close friends really stick by but really less numbered
[S]
[S] hm ..yeah definitely definitely
[L] kind of sense  I think only really really close friends really stick by but really less numbered
[S] yeah
[S] hm ..yeah definitely definitely