[S] Hey man, how are you doing?
[L] Hey, good
[S] I had this terrible, terrible experience a couple weeks back when I..
[S] You know, I'm already scared for taking flights.. Um.. And I..
[S] I don't know, something about it just scares me a lot..
[S] And a couple weeks ago I was traveling to Zurich as a tourist and I..
[S]  I found this really cheap flight, online, and lonely I booked it  once, so that's not a problem but I..
[S] Was not sure about my plan so..
[S] I had to take this flight uh..
[S] Uh.. really in the last minute, I found this cheap one.. and this all.. this, you know? This last minute deals websites?
[S] So, I took that.. Uh..
[S] Was really cheap so.. At least was an one hour flight or one hour and fifteen minutes, how bad could it be?
[S] So it was a evening flight, pretty much the last flight of the day, it was at nine pm or nine thirty pm or something
[S] So maybe I just reached the airport two hours before the time.. Um..
[S] Also.. the weather was not that.. was a bit rainy, and a bit windy, so I thought maybe I just worried guessing something was wrong
[S] And.. And to my.. not to my surprise but probably to my plan, as soon I entered in the airport there was a huge queue for check-in
[S] Apparently all the flights.. flights before were delayed because of the bad weather there
[S] And.. So.. The airport was like  to people completely like..
[S] The check-in was full..
[L] Locked-down
[S] Security was completely filled up and..
[S] And kinda even more much in the whole thing
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Somehow.. I barely managed to reach the board and get it before it closed, like five minutes before it closed
[S] Could running my bags through check-in to security and somehow making it through
[S] This guy was not happy with me, because I was kinda of just on time.. and Uh..
[S] So they just let me in but they were not that.. visibly weren't pleased with that
[S] And you know.. Some of these flight where hasn't these bridge connections to the plane, so you have to go down and take the bus
[L] Uh-huh
[S] That's one of the most annoying things that I hate..
[S] Because you.. I was just packed into the small bus looking a lot cheap and then taking you to somewhere and drop-out
[S] So we took the bus and as soon as we reached the airplane
[S] I see this really small propeller plane like the  a really small one
[L]
[S] I hate the propeller plane because I'm always scared flying in them, I don't know why, it's just a bug
[S] I don't trust that plane so much.. I like the jet planes I think they are the most evolved of this ones
[S] And the noise that they made when they flying is just scary for me
[S] And then.. there wasn't much I could do right? I just boarded in the plane.. they were rushing us, I think they were delayed or something..
[S] They were forcing us to get in there as soon as possible  so they could take off
[S] They were a bit rude to be honest not that.. not that pleasant, just pushed us in and.. we settled on.. to the..
[S] Um.. my seat.. I settled to my seat and I just packed my self in..
[S] And then they announce that the traffic control was not that clear because of the bad weather and they might wait till the tower back
[S] Or sometime, I was like why in the hell are you are you pushing us into the bus if we have to seat here for another few minutes
[S] Thus, we settled and waited the tarmac for one hour waiting for the flight take off
[S] And these guys aren't turning on the air conditioning so.. it was a crappy place for one hour almost no oxygen to breathe.. Uh.. I mean that was just..
[S] Too annoying for me, small place.. I a little bit claustrophobic, I was just getting paranoic all the time but.. this flight I was getting done with it
[S] Um.. At least we did take off, not the smoother, but we took off, I think that was a really strong wind, we were just like drifting along side, just shaky
[S] Um.. Somehow we reached the cruiser altitude.. Um..
[S] I thought I could remove the seat belt maybe go to the restroom, but they didn't switch of the seat belt sign
[S] And the lavatory was not allowed to be used because there was too much turbulence the plance was going from left to right and they said.. well..
[S] You can't move you should be back to your seat.. Uh.. people were having issues, because they weren't using the restroom or something..
[S] There were no services no water, nothing was served in the flight
[L] And you were sitting there for one hour,..
[S] Yeah, exactly I mean, they should give something, right? A bag of peanuts at least I guess or some free cold drink or something, nothing it's just weird
[L] Yeah.. Yeah
[S] And then things get even worst, suddenly the lights go off, of the plane
[S] And we see lighting outside, so these flashes of light was coming in like a horror movie, you watching a scene from a horror movie
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Completely dark and Uh.. flight with lights coming from outside
[S] And I feel like something is falling, sometimes in these turbulences the plane com up and down
[L] Uh-huh
[S] And I feel this fall, and it's not like this instant one second two seconds things, it's like fifteen twenty seconds of constant fall it's like the plane drop four hundred feets or something
[S] And I feel like something is falling, sometimes in these turbulences the plane com up and down
[S] And I panicking at this point of time because this is something my worst nightmare are made of, like planes crashing and things like that..
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Um.. And to my horror after some few seconds of this dropping the oxygen masks drop off
[S] And I've never had this experience before in my life, I've never used this things, and I got.. I mean we all see the guy telling us about it, but you never think this gonna happen
[L] Uh-huh
[S] So I can't put it on, the guy next to me kinda of.. helped me to put this on to my.. so I could breathe again
[S] And I've never had this experience before in my life, I've never used this things, and I got.. I mean we all see the guy telling us about it, but you never think this gonna happen
[S] And we had to go to this harrowing experience of these oxygen masks and jumping up and down for the next twenty minutes or so of the flight
[S] And the flight will go up for few seconds and then suddenly it will drop and few go up and then suddenly it will drop and this continued for the next twenty, thirty minutes
[S] Finally I think we were getting close of our destination and we were reaching to Zurich, the flight kinda of stabilized a bit, the weather cleared.. Um..
[S] And then we are.. we could remove our masks, lights came back on again, we could use the lavatories, and by the time  so shaky and annoyed with the whole experience that I didn't want to do anything
[L] Uh-huh
[S] And this landed..
[S] Even the landing for the matter was not that smooth we bumped around the airrun twice before we actually landed down
[S] So, one of the worst worst experiences in my life.. Uh..
[S] As soon as I got in the airport I canceled my flight of the way back
[S] And booked my train, so I could back by train, I didn't want to the same experience again
[S] Because it probably would be the same flight in the way back
[S] I don't think I can travel back in these propeller plane flights again
[S] Specially in the night so.. I gonna make sure that I'm taking the flight timing and I..
[S] And I pretty sure about that's not a propeller plane, it's a big plane that..
[S] I'm flying on and never have this experience again, I hope it doesn't happen to the big planes
[S] But this was one of the worsts things that I had to come through in my life