[S] Hi [L] Hi
[S] How are you? [L] Fine, and you?
[S] Yeah, cool, cool, cool, cool, I mean, standard
[S] I was remembering some things that happened
[L] Okay [S] In the past uh hmm..
[S] You had good experiences on your high school?
[L] Yeah, some [S] Yeah, some?
[L] Yeah [S] So this was yeah kind of divided
[L] Yeah [S] Yeah, every time I ask someone, I always, I mean, it's
[S] Very, it's really 50 50, some people really love it and enjoy it
[S] And some people really not like it much, it was a bad time [L] Hmm
[S] For me it was a different time, I was moving from school to school, so
[S] On my second year of high school I..
[S] I moved to a new, new school, and then you know it's hard to again, with a lot of people that you don't know
[S] No one knows you, and you are the new guy, and
[S] I never could connect with there people, they're there since ever, since their kindergarten, doing together, you know and
[L] True, yeah, hmm [S] You're kind of the outsider
[S] And this  teachers, they're very
[S] Uh this old didactic style, you know
[S] This authoritarianism in the school [L] Hmm
[S] That they don't know how to pass the, the, the, the subject properly
[S] They just yeah right something in the board and then that's all [L] Okay
[S] And.. and I was not the best student
[S] I was always average, you know, I was doing everything I could just to pass [L] Hmm hmm
[S] You know but never yeah, I never liked it, I never liked the subjects also
[S] Er but everything changed when there was a new teacher coming
[S] And he was younger than the other guys, he was more dynamic, he was more light [L] Hmm
[S] So he made this very good didactic, didactic when he was teaching
[S] And explaining things better, and making things interesting, he was teaching history [L] Hmm
[S] So.. history for me was never the best subject
[S] Because I just had to memorize a lot of dates, a lot names, a lot of things like that
[S] But.. he make a difference, he make it more life, more interesting to study, you know [L] Hmm
[S] Then I start to pay attention more, and attend more his lectures
[S] Uh.. yeah uh then came the first test, the first exam, I fail
[L] Uh [S] Yeah, really bad, and that is like yeah, wow
[S] That's bad, I was starting to get used to it and to like it
[S] Uh but then he came talk to me, this teacher came talk to me
[S] Is the first time that a teacher comes and shows interest on the grades of the student for me
[S] Wow okay, but he was a very nice guy [L] Hmm
[S] And he was asking me yeah I saw that you were very interested on the lecture and
[S] Why you fail? What's happening?
[S] We talked a lot and he gave me some hints of how to study and [L] Hmm
[S] More than everything he gives me motivation of how to go on, you know
[S] Um then things happen, paying attention more in the class, attending more
[S] Second exam came, I failed again [L] Uh, no
[S] And that's like, wow, come on, that's really like [L] Yeah
[S] How this can be possible, right?
[S] I start to feel bad for myself
[S] Er.. then it's yeah no I, there was a third exam
[S] And I had to pass it, so I say you know I have to pass this third exam
[S] So I will make for it and.. I studied like crazy
[S] Really first time in my life that I was really, really studying
[S] And reading the books, and really, really trying to understand it and stuff, and writing [L] Hmm
[S] Er.. but the day before the exam
[S] I was so nervous, so anxious, that I had some panic attacks
[L] Uh [S] And say yeah, I cannot do that, I cannot do that, I cannot do that
[S] And the only solution I could find to, to calm me down
[S] Was to get some strips of paper and write the answers on it
[S] And then put on my sleeves, so I kind of made some cheating papers on it [L] Uh uh
[S] Then I went to the test, to do the test with these papers on my sleeves,
[S] And.. I start to answer the test and
[S] Taking the, yeah the notes I made
[S] But in the end when I was finishing the test, I started to feel so bad
[L] Okay [S] So guilty, you know, I was wow
[S] That's really awful, I'm betraying the trust of this guy on me [L] Hmm
[S] And.. I studied so hard, and that's how I do it
[S] And wow I really felt like the worst person on earth
[S] And then, and then I hand the test, I pass
[S] I never talk to this professor, this teacher anymore
[S] But I always carry this with me, this guilt
[S] This heavy, heavy feeling, of wow this was low bottom you'll ever achieve [L] Hmm
[S] It was a milestone for me, I never did this anymore [L] Okay
[S] Er.. but I will always carry this guilt with me, it was really, really something [L] Uh