[L]  you doing good? [S] Yeah, yeah um
[S] Uh I was traveling over the weekend it was really annoying. Uh do you like traveling?
[L] Yeah [S] Do you like air travel? [L] Yeah
[S] Um well air travel for me is like really annoying and er really scary ah and
[S] It's always like this thing where you are in the mid of air and there's
[S] Literally something goes wrong there's literally no chance for your survival right?
[S] And um over the weekend, on Friday evening actually, I was traveling to Brussels
[S] I found this cheap flight so I took it
[S] Only for that day they had a special flight with some special offer
[S] And I went to the er, it was in the night so it was like the last flight of the day
[S] You know in Europe how they close airports for the night and there's no night flights per se [L] Uh-huh
[S] So this is the last, I think the last flight of the day or something
[S] Yeah, I reached the airport two hours early um
[S] Just.. because I knew it might be delayed or something
[S] Ah it was a windy, stormy night, it was rain happening like
[S] And as soon as I reach the airport, I see this like huge cue of people for check in
[S] Because apparantly all the flights below, uh before that were delayed
[S] Um because of the weather and there was this huge cue and
[S] Even with the two hours that I had before the boarding actually started
[S] I still just barely managed to get to board the plane
[S] Because I was, the whole check in cue I had this big bag, I shouldn't have carried a big bag, which I had to check in
[S] After this long cue of check in
[S] This, again this long cue of security
[S] It took me like almost two hours to finish all of that
[S] And I just barely managed the boarding
[S] And they were like closing the boarding when I actually reached it
[S] You know how in some airports or in some place, they don't have the bridge to the plane
[S] And you have to get down and take the bus, and the bus goes. I hate that, I hate going to the bus.
[S] Just so annoying, on the  going with the bus yeah [L] Uh-huh
[S] And um.. so we board the bus, and with the bus we reach the plane
[S] And, and what I see is a really small plane
[S] You know one of those propeller planes, like 60, 70-seater planes
[S] And I hate those propeller planes, I feel really insecure flying in those propeller planes
[S] I like jets a lot, because well you have better chance of survival for the weather, right?
[S] Propellers are just so annoying. Strong wind and the propeller stops, it's just annoying.
[S] So better than I thought it was, they kind of, they were getting late because of the delays before
[S] So they just pushed us in literally, they just hurried us to our seats
[S] And said you should  as soon as possible like
[S] Not even giving us our time to you know settle down
[S] Just forcing us to get in, it was a bit rude as well
[S] Um to be sat down in the plane, and um..
[S] Then there was announcement saying that well the air traffic control won't let us fly because of the weather
[S] So we were waiting for a clearance
[L] I see. [S] And I was like why, why the hell were you just pushing us in in the first place if this was the case?
[S] Can you imagine we spent one hour on the tarmac waiting for clearance to fly [L]
[S] Just sitting there, and they don't even switch on the air conditioning, it's
[S] You can't breathe after some point of time, there's I mean it's not like you can open a window or something
[S] It's nothing, and it's a cramped, small plane
It's just so annoying um..
[S] Then after an hour or something, they actually er.. we actually went to the er.. were allowed to take off
[S] The take off happened, it was not the best of the take off, you know
[S] Pretty wavering  and uh it was okay
[S] Um we reached to some cruising height and then suddenly um
[S] There's announcement that well you should not take off your seat belt
[S] Because there's turbulence and bla bla and
[S] The lavatories were not allowed to be used, we can't go to the lavatories
[S] And we had to just sit in this place because the plane was going from left to right because of the er turbulence
[S] Um.. then at one point of time, suddenly I felt like this plane was falling
[S] Like having a free fall, you know how in turbulence sometimes it falls down?
[S] And it, it's not like a small one, it just fell down for like 300, 400 feet I believe and
[S] And suddenly the lights went off, off the plane and
[S] It was just free falling, there was lightning outside
[S] Through the seat, these flashes of light coming in, it was just really from a horror movie or something, it's really scary
[S] And then all of the sudden these oxygen masks drop off
[S] And we're asked to put them on, and I've never experienced this before in my life
[S] These oxygen masks coming down, so I'm just, I was not able to do it
[S] Uh so the guy next to me was able to help me
[S] And I was put the oxygen mask, and I could breathe again
[S] But I could still feel like it was trying to climb up and then fall, climb up and fall, it went on for some time, I felt really sick
[S] Um and scared at the same time, I thought that this is the end, I'm gonna die
[S] And then um it went on for like 10, 15 minutes
[S] Of this terrible um turbulence, and then eventually it kind of smoothed out
[S] Probably climbed up to a good altitude, and we were asked to remove the masks, and the lights came on again
[S] But it was like this harrowing and uh scary experience I had um
[S] I'm already scared about the air travel and the propeller planes
[S] And this was like my worst nightmare coming to life
[S] Um and then we were about to reach the destination and then even the landing was bumpy
[S] We just jumped twice on, on the, on the runway
[S] Um it was such a scary, annoying experience of my life
[S] That I'm scared to travel using airlines again
[S] On my way back, I canceled my flight, I took a train
[S] It took me long but fine at least I knew I was, I was safer than that
[S] There was no, no gush of air would make me die
[S] Or something, it was just uh, and I'm scared to take the plane anymore
[S] I'm pretty sure I'm gonna check if it's a jet plane or a propeller plane
[S] How many people, never gonna take the night flights out
[S] Uh it was just so scary, so, so scary for me
[L] Um it must be very terrible to have that experience
[S] It was just