[L] I'm fine
[S] how was your weekend?
[L] my week.. my weekend was good
[L] yeah..
[S] was good ?
[L] was was fine
[S] great
[L] yeah
[S] I went to um Norway
[L] wow
[S] to visit a friend
[L] ok
[S] yeah the city of Tromsø have you heard of it
[L] no no I have not
[S] up north um
[S] not such a huge city
[L] ok
[S] he's doing his Erasmus there so
[L] uh..
[S] um it's been a while since I wanted to you know last time I saw him so I just just decided to go there
[S] he's doing his Erasmus there so
[L] uh-huh
[S] it's really cold in this period but that's you know the
[L] ok yeah..
[S] Scandinavian experience to get some cold and um
[S] it's really cold in this period but that's you know the
[L] uh-huh
[S] Scandinavian experience to get some cold and um
[S] just went around a bit um it's really expensive there by the way
[L] ok
[S] so just to have some decent meal and a beer you know you pay around twenty five euros or so
[S] which is kind of a lot um but yeah we just went around you know
[L]
[L] yeah..
[S] which is kind of a lot um but yeah we just went around you know
[S] you know enjoy the good weather the cold it's kind of dark all the time anyway I met some interesting people at some point um we were with some of his friends and um
[L] uh-huh
[L] yeah
[S] you know enjoy the good weather the cold it's kind of dark all the time anyway I met some interesting people at some point um we were with some of his friends and um
[L] oh ok
[S] um have you ever heard of this really really smelly fish thing which is supposed to be smelliest..
[L] yeah yeah yeah yeah
[S] I forgot the name
[L] did you try it
[S] yeah well that's the thing um..
[S] we were talking about it and
[L] uh-huh
[S] um my friend is like oh you haven't tried I was like no I never tried so
[L]
[L] ok
[S] um my friend is like oh you haven't tried I was like no I never tried so
[S] so yeah so I said ok let's try it
[L] ok
[S] the thing is I don't really like fish in general like whatever is fishy like tuna or salmon it's kind of uh..
[S] so yeah so I said ok let's try it
[L] uh-huh uh-huh
[S] the thing is I don't really like fish in general like whatever is fishy like tuna or salmon it's kind of uh..
[L] uh-huh
[S] but it's like ok we just made a bet and the idea is that um
[L] yeah..
[S]
[S] we had to try it so we went to the supermarket and we just got it um you know this kind of a can
[L] uh-huh
[S] um and he was like yeah don't worry I mean it smells really powerful and strong
[S] but the taste is not so bad which is ok
[L] uh-huh
[L] ok
[S] you know I wasn't really trusting him but anyway let's give it a try
[L]
[L] uh-huh yeah
[S] you know I wasn't really trusting him but anyway let's give it a try
[S] um so then we went back home and you're not supposed to eat this thing indoors
[L] ok
[S] 'cause it's really smelly they yeah advise you to be outdoors somewhere in the nature
[L]
[S] 'cause you house.. your house can sting for days
[L] it's that smelly
[L]
[S] 'cause you house.. your house can sting for days
[S] so what we did is yeah we just went to uh kind of park behind his place
[S] you know 'cause he didn't want his house to smell that
[L] uh-huh
[L]
[S] you know 'cause he didn't want his house to smell that
[L] smell
[S] but uh yeah we went to the park and um yeah I was really hoping this thing could you know taste
[S] not so bad 'cause I had a really bad experience in Beijing in China when I tried the smelly tofu
[L] hm..
[S] have you heard of the smelly tofu ? well it's really smelly it's really.. it's more smelly than tofu it's really disgusting so I couldn't finish that one
[L] uh.. that one yeah I've heard of that
[L] ok
[S] have you heard of the smelly tofu ? well it's really smelly it's really.. it's more smelly than tofu it's really disgusting so I couldn't finish that one
[L] oh my god oh my god
[L] ok
[S] have you heard of the smelly tofu ? well it's really smelly it's really.. it's more smelly than tofu it's really disgusting so I couldn't finish that one
[S] so you know it's like ok you know maybe it's better than that um
[L] uh-huh
[S] so yeah so started opening the can and as soon as you know I opened a bit of the can I felt this
[L]
[S] smelly wave coming to my face an amazing experience in the negative sense was like
[L] ok yeah yeah
[L]
[S] smelly wave coming to my face an amazing experience in the negative sense was like
[S] wow so strong and it's like oh my god this is not edible it's impossible to eat this thing and I told you I hate fish so
[L] ok
[S] for me was you know double challenge just to stand the smell of this fishy thing which is kinda raw and uh..
[S] yeah yeah yeah
[S] yeah I mean he was like well doesn't smell that bad but of course smell bad it you know 'cause it was really disgusting so
[L]
[L] uh-huh
[S] yeah I mean he was like well doesn't smell that bad but of course smell bad it you know 'cause it was really disgusting so
[S] yeah but now was the time to taste it yeah so I opened it and uh you know they had these slices of
[S] raw fish in this kind of water and jello you know this thing kind of oil a mixture of whatever substance
[L] ew..
[L] ok
[S] raw fish in this kind of water and jello you know this thing kind of oil a mixture of whatever substance
[S] that was I don't care I just you know I was almost crying because of the strong smell
[L] ok
[L]
[S] that was I don't care I just you know I was almost crying because of the strong smell
[L] uh-huh
[S] and I guess like this should not be edible and yeah but you know um it was also impossible to get used of that smell
[S] so it's just a game just go for it so the bet was on let's just eat it um yeah so I tried to approach it to my you know
[L]
[L] ok
[S] so it's just a game just go for it so the bet was on let's just eat it um yeah so I tried to approach it to my you know
[S] I grabbed a slice of it whatever that was pushed to my mouth and I couldn't just like ok then I looked at my friend he was like
[L]
[S] chewing but kind of crying like uh.. uh-huh ok so I just decided to take it as a medicine you know just like
[L]  ok
[L]
[S] chewing but kind of crying like uh.. uh-huh ok so I just decided to take it as a medicine you know just like
[S] hardcore like without trying to we just did it so I just you know did like this I put it in my mouth but I just
[L] hm hm..
[S] spit it was too strong I just threw the whole thing to the floor I couldn't stand it um..
[L] ew.. ok
[L] ok
[S] spit it was too strong I just threw the whole thing to the floor I couldn't stand it um..
[S] it was just really so strong and then I look at my friend he was like biting like it's not so bad
[L]  yeah
[S] but it was terrible it was really you could see he was crying you could see what a bad idea it was
[L] oh yeah
[L] uh-huh
[S] but it was terrible it was really you could see he was crying you could see what a bad idea it was
[S] yeah was really really disgusting and I don't think like I don't think that there's anybody who really likes that but
[S] apparently they produce it it's kind of you know  yeah so that's probably the one of the memories that I will never forget about Norway
[L] yeah ew yeah