[L] Yeah.
[S] What's up?
[L] What's down?
[L]
[S] Mean..
[S] (Almost I had this?)
[L]
[S] You known.. I couple of weeks.. week week ago.. last week actually I was traveling to Brussels
[S] So, have you been to Brussels ever?
[L] Ah, ok.
[L] No, not yet.
[S] Yes, so I.. It was the second time I was going there and I was meeting a friend over there.
[L] Ok.
[S] So, I found this cheap flight online, you know this websites you can find this last minute deals or something.
[L] Yeah.
[S] And there was one which was flying the last Friday evening.
[L] Ok.
[S] So, ok, It was a one hour flight or something and I thought It was really cheap so I thought I'd take it.
[L] Yeah.
[S] Um.. It was an evening flight uh.. starting of ten in the night just one hour to we reach there.
[L] Ok.
[S] I was meeting with a friend in the next day.
[L] Uh-huh.
[S] So I took the flight. I was actually.. I reached the airport a couple of hours early, you know.. I tend to reach early to  stuff early.
[S] I was meeting with a friend in the next day.
[L]  OK. Yeah..
[S] So I took the flight. I was actually.. I reached the airport a couple of hours early, you know.. I tend to reach early to  stuff early.
[S] It was this raining typical night (there?). It was raining and stormy a bit.
[L] Um.
[S] So, I reached early so I was expecting maybe a delay or something because of the weather. As I reached the airport I see this huge huge queue for the check in.
[L] Yeah.
[S] Because all the flights before mine were delayed because of the weather.
[L] Oh.
[S] (And it was?) crazy rush at the airport. Ah.. So, despite keeping two hours before boarding I just manage, barely managed to board the flight.
[L] Yeah. Yeah.
[L] Ok.
[S] 'Cause It took me a lot of time to do check in then a lot of time for security. And I forgot this clipper in my bag so they had to send me to another screening. It was crazy.
[L] Yeah, yeah.
[L] Oh, ok.
[S] 'Cause It took me a lot of time to do check in then a lot of time for security. And I forgot this clipper in my bag so they had to send me to another screening. It was crazy.
[S] I just forgot it was in my bag.
[L] Oh, ok.
[L] Ok.
[S] I just forgot it was in my bag.
[S] And then I reached the boarding place, the boarding gate, just like a couple of minutes before they were closing it and they let me in ah..
[S] (Badly?)
[L] Ok, yeah. It happened to me.
[S] Uh.. Yeah, it was crazy.
[S] You know, some of this flights they don't have the bridges to the flight so you have get down and to take the bus. It's the worse. I hate to taking the bus there.
[L] Yeah .
[L] Yeah.
[S] So, they just put us in this bus and then they took us to the airplane and then I realize that It was this really small plane. You know those propeller planes  with sixty seater or seventy seater?
[L] Um..
[L] Yeah .
[S] So, they just put us in this bus and then they took us to the airplane and then I realize that It was this really small plane. You know those propeller planes  with sixty seater or seventy seater?
[L] Yeah.
[S] So, It is a really crammed airplane. And I don't like propeller planes. I just don't fell very secure. I like the jet ones, which is bit big you have more space and this is a really small propeller one.
[L] Ok.
[L] Yeah.
[S] So, It is a really crammed airplane. And I don't like propeller planes. I just don't fell very secure. I like the jet ones, which is bit big you have more space and this is a really small propeller one.
[L] Uh..
[S] And they just rush because they were getting late. They just rushed us in. They were just a bit kind of rude as well as we were supposed to get in as soon as possible and sit down.
[L] Yeah yeah.
[L] Ok.
[S] And they just rush because they were getting late. They just rushed us in. They were just a bit kind of rude as well as we were supposed to get in as soon as possible and sit down.
[S] This (certain?) because because they wanna to fly and everything.
[L] It's not good.
[L] Yeah.
[S] This (certain?) because because they wanna to fly and everything.
[S] And as we settle, there was an announcement saying that, well, we can't fly right now because the air traffic control has said that the weather is not good. So, we have to to wait for some time before we take off.
[L] Ok. Yeah, (bad?).
[S] We waited for one hour at the tarmac inside the plane before we actually could take off.
[L] Ok.
[S] And they don't switched on the air conditioning. They didn't let as move around much.
[L] Ah.
[S] It was this cramped small place. It was just so annoying. It was already not going well for me.
[L] Yeah, yeah.
[L] Ok.
[S] After one hour they said ok, now we can fly. Ah, so.. the take off was also not very smooth. It was  uh..
[L] Yeah.
[L] Yeah, ok.
[S] After one hour they said ok, now we can fly. Ah, so.. the take off was also not very smooth. It was  uh..
[S] Because of bad weather, right? It was just bad weather and a bit stormy.
[L] Uh-huh.
[S] As we reached cruising altitude.. few minutes (has pass?), so normally what you do is you lose your seat belt and go to the restroom or something.
[L] Yeah.
[S] They didn't switch off the lights. They said: no you should keep your seat belts.
[L]
[S] Ah.. The lavatory was not allowed to be used. We could not you lavatory because there was turbulence. The plane was going from left to right all the time. I hate propeller plane.
[L] Uh-huh.
[L] It fells you had the worse experience ever.
[S] It gets worse wait.
[L] Yeah
[S] So It was going on and on left and right.
[S] After some time uh.. The lights go off at the plane
[L] What?
[S] Because of the turbulence I experienced like, you know some times in a turbulence you fells like the airplane is falling?
[L] Yeah.
[S] But it is like for one second or something, but this continued for like few seconds.
[L] Uh-huh.
[S] It was just like the plane falling, having a free fall.
[L] Oh my god.
[S] And then.. That was the first time I ever experienced this. I didn't know how to put on the masks.
[L] Ok.
[L] Yeah, yeah.
[S] And then.. That was the first time I ever experienced this. I didn't know how to put on the masks.
[S] I was struggling. I couldn't breath. The guy next to me actually helped me and then I could actually breathe then.
[L] Yeah, yeah.
[L] Yeah.
[S] I was struggling. I couldn't breath. The guy next to me actually helped me and then I could actually breathe then.
[S] And then.. and then the plane would climb a bit and then fall a bit, climb a bit and fall a bit. It was this next twenty minutes was the worse time ever.
[L] Oh my got, You were dying .
[L]  .
[S] In my head I was like this is the day I'm dying. This is done. I couldn't even talk to my parents before I could die. It was just the worse thing.
[L] (Ouch?) ok.
[L] Yeah.
[S] In my head I was like this is the day I'm dying. This is done. I couldn't even talk to my parents before I could die. It was just the worse thing.
[L] Oh.
[S] And then after like twenty minutes (or well?) of this happening. It kind of stabilize. The plane climbed up to an altitude. We were asked to remove our masks. The light came on in again.
[S] Uh.. The  were apologizing for it. They couldn't do anything because of the weather was just that bad.
[L] That sure, but they can provide better service.
[S] They could be less rude at least. Yeah. That could be something.
[L]  Yeah .
[S] And then even the landing was not really smooth. We bumped in the airport.. in the the air.. in the runaway twice before we actually landed.
[L] Oh my god.
[S] The worse experience. Literally the worse experience of in my life flying.
[L] But you were glad that you made it, right?
[S] I was glad that I was alive, but I was so scary to take the flight back. I canceled the flight back. I took the train.
[L] .
[L] Ok.
[S] It took longer of course but then at least I was safer then I was.
[L] Yeah.
[S] Ans I think I will never and never take the propeller planes again. Before I book a flight I'll see which plane It is.
[L] Um.
[L] Yeah.
[S] Never take a night flight, that hour at least, when I know the weather is not good.
[L] Yeah, yeah.
[S] And never never take the propeller plane, always the jet ones.
[L] Yeah, yeah, but..
[S] It was like the worse experience.
[S] And never never take the propeller plane, always the jet ones.
[L] Yeah, yeah, but..
[S] It was like the worse experience.
[L] Yeah, but the weather you can not judge it.
[S] Yeah, but this one ..
[S] See It's my flying experience for life. I'll be very cautious flying again.
[L] .
[L] Yeah, and..
[S] See It's my flying experience for life. I'll be very cautious flying again.