[L] Hi [S] How are you?
[L] I'm doing good [S] Yeah?
[L] Yeah [S] Great
[S] How was high school? How was your high school time?
[S] Ah, it was fun, I was a nerd, so quite a lot of studying  [L] Yeah?
[L] Yes [S] But you like it?
[L] Yes, it was fun [S] Yeah? I asked a lot of people now
[L] Uh-huh hmm [S] They got always like 50 50 answer
[S] Someone really love it love it, someone is like yeah, it was awful [L] Uh-huh and yeah uh-huh okay
[S] Yeah, for me it was on the second part, so I was not that good [L] Ah okay
[S] Yeah, I changed, in the middle of high school I changed school [L] Uh-huh
[S] So I went to a new school, and then I was always the outsider guy, you know [L] Okay, okay
[S] Everyone study there, and grew up there, they were together in this, and I just arrive [L] Ah okay, yeah, uh-huh
[S] In the middle of high school you know, finish times, and it's not the best option I guess [L] Uh-huh, yeah
[S] But yeah I also never was a good student [S] Okay
[S] I was always averaging, so I was always the minimal to pass [L] Okay, okay
[S] Right that was something yeah  [L] Uh-huh, yeah that doesn't
[S] And I mean aggregated the feeling that I was alone there [L] Yeah
[S] And er.. the teachers were so bad [L] Yeah, hmm
[S] They're really this um.. [L] Okay, uh-huh
[S] Old style teaching, without much didactic [L] Okay
[S] Just this autocrat thing, that I teach, you learn, that's all [L] Okay, uh-huh, uh-huh
[S] So I write here, you copy in your notebook, and that's all [L] Okay, okay
[S] And this was not the best idea, I think [L] Okay, uh-huh
[S] Ah but everything changed when the new teacher came [L] Okay
[S] He was a history teacher, yes [L] History, okay
[S] And I was never fond of history because for me with history, it was always [L] Uh-huh
[S] Memorizing dates, and numbers, and places and stuff like that, for me this was not fun [L] All the time, yeah, uh-huh
[S] But he came with a different way of uh.. teaching, yes [L] Okay, teaching, okay
[S] He came with a new didactic, he was a new guy, and younger than the other guys [L] Uh-huh
[S] And he came with this dynamic way of teaching, and making the lecture more interesting [L] Uh-huh, okay, okay
[S] And I started to get used to it, you know ah that's actually interesting [L] Ah uh-huh
[S] And then started to get attracted to this kind of lecture [L] Uh-huh, uh-huh, okay
[S] And I was pretty motivated to go to the lectures and to pay attention and so on [L] Yeah, uh-huh
[S] Then came the first exam, but I failed [L] Uh-huh
[L] You failed? Oh shit, okay [S] Really bad, completely, really bad
[S] And then I was feeling a bit embarrassed, okay I started to get to like this kind of thing, but then I failed, is something wrong? [L] Okay
[S] Er.. but then the teacher came talk to me [L] Yeah
[S] And it was the first time the teacher approached the students like one to one conversation [L] Okay, oh
[S] And see how, exactly, see how things are going [L] Okay, like personal, okay, uh-huh
[S] And it was nice, I mean he talked to me and said yeah I see you here all the time [L] Uh-huh
[S] You are very motivated, you are always here asking questions [L] Yeah, uh-huh
[S] What happened? Why you fail? And then he was also motivating me to study more [L] Uh-huh
[S] To pay more attention, to study more efficiently, right [L] Yeah, of course, uh-huh, okay, uh-huh
[S] Then I study more, and more, more, second exam came, I failed again [L] Uh-huh, oh shit
[S] Yeah, this was like no, not again [L] Yeah, okay
[S] And then, I then start to feel very very bad
[S] Because of that right? And I say okay that's getting weird [L] Okay, uh-huh
[S] And then the teacher came again, and talk again, and try to motivate me again [L] Yeah
[S] But then I was already feeling very very down [L] Yeah, of course
[S] And then there was the final exam and I had to pass the final exam, otherwise I would fail the class
[L] Oh shit, uh-huh [S] And then I started to study like crazy, really eating my books
[S] Really memorizing and trying to learn everything [L] Uh-huh
[S] But then I start to become very nervous
[S] Very very nervous, and having, one day before the exam I was having some panic attacks [L] Okay, yeah, oh shit
[S] So it was really, really like wow, I cannot do that, I really will fail tomorrow [L] Uh-huh, okay
[L] Yeah, that's rough [S] And then on top of my panic attack
[S] Is what a decision I made to calm me down and to guarantee that I would pass [L] Uh-huh
[S] That I would make some stripes of papers [L] Uh-huh, okay
[S] Put some names and dates on it, and put on my sleeve [L] Hmm, ah okay
[S] So I would cheat on the exam, I decided to do that [L] Oh shit
[L] Oh that's so bad hmm [S] Yeah, it was really really bad, right
[S] And then on the day of the exam, I started the exam
[S] And I started the test, and everything was fine and I was doing my my my cheating [L] Yeah
[S] Um.. I answer all the questions [L] Okay
[S] And then I went to hand in the test
[S] Uh before I hand the test I started to feel so bad about it [L] Yeah
[S] I started to feel so guilty, you know?
[S] Came this guy, this teacher, he was super nice, he was trusting in me, and he was motivating me [L] Uh-huh
[S] And then I break his trust doing something like that [L] Yeah that's true
[S] I felt so, the worst person on earth, really really disgusted with myself [L] Uh-huh
[S] Really really bad for doing that, I mean to have to do that you know [L] Okay, uh-huh, yeah
[S] And then I hand in the exam, I passed the test, I never spoke to the teacher anymore
[S] But I carry this with me, this feeling of of failure [L] Okay, oh shit, uh-huh
[S] This really, really bad feeling, I think it's shaped me on my future [L] Yeah, that's bad, uh-huh
[S] But yeah, this was really, really strong to me at that time [L] Uh-huh, oh that's not good
[S] No, no, not at all