[S] hey how was your weekend ?
[L] yeah was great
[S] was great ?
[S] I traveled I visited my friend he's living um.. in Norway
[S] actually Tromsø you know Norway.. have you ever been there ?
[L] no
[S] it's a really cold place you know this
[S] typical Scandinavian city
[S] um he's studying there so I just went
[S] there for a weekend and you know have some fun
[S] um.. not really a lot to do
[S] except for just you know going to some
[S] national parks and everything there is so expensive actually you know
[S] just wanted to have some dinner and beer an that's like
[S] wow around thirty euros but anyway it was really nice and then
[S] um.. he told me about these um really
[S] smelly food they had this kind of
[S] um fermented fish
[S] with salt you know it's supposed to be the smelliest food in the world
[S] have you ever heard that
[L] yeah
[S] yeah so this really smelly fish thing and he said look
[S] um doesn't matter what you say smells bad but it tastes great
[S] and I was like really does it taste great ?
[S] so yeah why don't we try it
[S] and I was a little kind of skeptical about it 'cause once I had the smelly tofu in Beijing
[S] and it was honestly the most disgusting experience
[S]
[S] of you know this mix of that smell
[S] that taste but on the other hand I mean I was like yeah let's just do it
[S] and you know we made a bet
[S] so like we had to finish it
[S] I was like ok um so we went to supermarket we got it was kind of this you know kind of tuna cans
[S] which had this thing already the can looked kinda disgusting and oh my god
[S] um you're not supposed to eat this
[S] you know indoors so inside your home 'cause this kind of smell forever so we had to go
[L] hmm
[S] somewhere else so we went to this small park close to his place
[S] um.. it was cold so you know for the smell that's good 'cause you know
[S] when it's really really cold the smell doesn't sting so hard but anyway so we went there
[S] um..
[S] and yeah so the thing is I don't like fish in general
[L] uh-huh
[S] and then I also the smelly one so I really had a lot of
[S] I needed a lot of psychological preparation so ok I'm about to eat this kinda
[S] raw smelly fish
[S] that I know will smell a lot but anyway I just did it
[S] and as soon as I opened this can I was like wow it's really
[S] was not only the smell also the look you know when you saw
[S] when I saw that fish with that oil there was like oh my god
[S] and I saw his face and his face was so disgusted as well so I knew that it would not
[S] taste good at all so he was lying to me of course I kind of knew it from the beginning
[S] but yeah but I wanted to win the bet um..
[S] so you know was the
[S] moment of truth in which I had to really
[S] take that gluey thing
[S] out of the can and put it in my mouth
[S] such a disgusting moment
[S] and I mean I did the first try but I couldn't was kind of ok stop and then I looked at my friend and he was like literally crying
[S] he was like you know and he's from that place and was like oh my god
[S] it smelled so bad so I had to you know do this with my nose
[S] and I just had it and wow
[S] was probably the most disgusting
[S] taste I ever tried so the full thing like
[S] the smell the taste the texture of this thing
[S] so I just gave a bite
[S] and that was it I just
[S] um.. left it there my friend was just trying to finish it but he couldn't he was really like
[S] crying saying I won I won the bet yeah you won but
[S] you know it was a really disgusting experience but I'm sure I'm gonna remember that forever
[L] I see..