[S] doing ?
[L] fine and you ?
[S] good how was your weekend ?
[L] it was nice
[S] nice ? I went to Norway to visit a friend
[L] cool
[S] he's living in Tromsø
[L] uh-huh
[S] have you ever been there or heard anything ?
[L] no
[S] it's a nice small city up north
[S] the country really cold
[L] uh-huh
[S] um.. not a lot to do there but
[S] the country really cold
[S] he's doing his
[S]
[S] so I just went there to visit him
[S] everything is so expensive so
[L] uh-huh
[S] just to get out you know a food and a beer
[S] must be like twenty five euros so it's not a place for a student but anyway
[S] um we had some fun there it's kinda cold in this period I mean it's kind of cold the whole year but you know
[S] it's also getting dark
[S] it's kinda dark all the time
[L] hmm
[S] nice experience and then he um asked me
[S] if I ever tried this kind of super smelly fish thing have you ever heard of it are you familiar with this thing
[L] I heard of it but
[S] that should be the smelliest food
[S] if I ever tried this kind of super smelly fish thing have you ever heard of it are you familiar with this thing
[S] in the world
[L] hmm
[S] just I mean I think I saw something like this but I was not sure so
[S] but then he told that it's really smelly but it doesn't taste so bad
[L] uh..
[S] and then it's like ok let's try it you know he's like you wanna try it
[S] and I hate fish in general so whatever even tuna I really
[S] don't stand but yeah so we made a bet like
[S] the one you know person just uh finishing this thing wins was like ok you know
[S] whatever so we went to supermarket got these cans I mean already the cans looks kind of suspicious like you know this kind of cheap can
[L] uh-huh
[L] hmm
[S] whatever so we went to supermarket got these cans I mean already the cans looks kind of suspicious like you know this kind of cheap can
[S]
[S] um you're not supposed to eat these indoors
[S] 'cause this is really smelly so if you open this at your place your place is gonna smell
[L] ok
[S] like fish you know this kind of I don't know I don't I can't even explain
[S] that smell you know whatever so we ad to go outdoors I mean to this park um
[S] behind his place yeah so we went there which is you know I had to prepare.. prepare a lot psychologically
[S] 'cause I hate fish 'cause this thing is kinda raw you know fermented with salt
[S] and because this is really really smelly and
[L] hmm
[S] I started to think about my experience in Beijing trying smelly tofu
[S] and.. have you ever tried ?
[L] no
[S] uh wow just you're missing nothing it's
[S] so disgusting so it's really you know I was kinda torturing myself thinking oh man this is gonna
[S] it's gonna be be.. worse but he said no man don't worry it's really smelly but it tastes good alright so we went there we just opened it and
[S] and you could see like the first you know wave
[S] of smell like
[S]
[L]
[S] it's like a mixture of emotions like oh my god
[S] what the hell is this um yeah you could see you know the slices of raw fish
[S] swimming in this kinda of watery jello thing you it's kind of
[S] wow also his face was like wow so then I knew this wouldn't taste good was like oh yeah he was kidding
[L]
[S] but yeah we were there so I had to try it
[S] wow also his face was like wow so then I knew this wouldn't taste good was like oh yeah he was kidding
[S] so I just opened the can a bit more so even more smell came to me so I was like
[L] uh-huh
[S] you know having this kind of almond shaped eye like oh my god
[S] yeah and we had to try it so I just you know
[S] crusted this slice of fishy
[S] gluey thingy so you know so oh my god
[L] uh-huh
[S]
[S] I just turned around to my friend and he was
[S] he was literally crying you could see he was
[S] biting this thing like uh-huh it's not so bad
[L]
[S] but it was terrible so
[S] I was not sure but a bet is a bet so I just tried it
[S] um.. so I had to do like this 'cause um it was too much
[L]
[S] but anyway it was too much I just remembered I tried to give this more bite and I couldn't stand it I just dropped the can everything
[S] but the smell was everywhere so not like just drop the can so I have this
[S] taste in my mouth and then I looked at him he was like crying saying it's not that bad
[L]
[S] but it was terrible so yeah I told him man you won the bet it's ok I
[S] you know I just wanted to forget this experience you know yeah so
[S] that's basically what I will always remember from Norway