[S] Hey, how are you doing?
[L]
[S] Ah Long time, yeah?
[L] A little time...
[S] Ah um..
[S] Have you been traveling recently?
[S] Did you travel somewhere recently?
[L]
[S] So, the last week so so?
[L] Three weeks ago or something.
[S] Ah ok. Had any trouble?
[L] No.
[S] Ah ok. That's great.
[S] Um.. I was traveling last week uh..
[S] I had to go to Brussels, which is not that far away, so I could technically take a train
[S] But I've found this deal online on (company name?) and It was a really cheap flight, so I could fly to there.
[S] So i took it. I didn't realize.. I mean I did see that it was in the night, so a night flight
[S] But I didn't realize It was that late, so It was at ten and most of the flights in Europe from airports don't fly at night or (something?)
[S] That was like the last flight or so.
[S] At ten ten PM
[S] Ah.. So I reached the airport and It was dark already and It was.. ah.. pretty stormy because the I think the rain were forecasted or something
[S] And I reached there and there is a huge queue for check in, because apparently a lot of flights were delayed and everything.
[S] Um.. So It took me like almost one hour to get through the check in and everything
[S] (I arrived?) early for the flight but then I realized that I.. while I was checking in there were fifteen to going minutes for me to do the check in, do the security  and actually finishing my boarding.
[S] By the time I managed to reach the boarding, they were kind of closing It down, but they let me in.
[S] And we boarded the plane.  Um.. So you known Uh.. When you board in some of the airports don`t have the bridges, so you have to get down and the bus takes you to the plane.
[S] It was one of those um..
[S] Which already.. I was already started do fell a bit grumpy about it because I don't like that ah..
[S] But when we reached the plane we realized.. or I realized there was a really small plane, you know this propeller small plane with seventy seats or something
[S] And I hate those.
[S] Because of these propellers I never fell safe on it. I like the jet planes or something a little more secure in my head at least.
[S] Well, It was this propeller plane and at that point I had no option but to just board the plane. so I boarded it and um..
[S] They were hurrying up.. hurrying us up, because the the flight was kind of late  we seat on our places  as well.
[S] And then we find out that ah.. the air traffic control didn't allow us..
[S] the plane to take off because of the storm and everything
[S] And the other flights waiting to take off before us. So we stand on the tarmac for one hour waiting for a plane to (actually?) stopped
[S] Already going pretty well, It gets worse I tell you.
[L] Uh
[S] Um.. After waiting for one hour they don't give us water and they don't switch the air conditioner on the tarmac.
[S] Already going pretty well, It gets worse I tell you.
[S] It was terrible. We could hardly..
[S] There was not much oxygen left in the plane.
[L] Uh.
[S] And suddenly they said ok, now we can go to the take off
[S] Ah.. we took off ah.. It was a bit shaky the take off as well, the plane was going all over the place and..
[S] Once we reached this cruising altitude um..
[S] Shortly after that, It this.. there was too much turbulence because there was a storm forecasted.
[S] It was too much turbulence, It was raining heavily, the plane was going from left to right, It was really shaky
[L] Uh.
[S] And the seat belt signs were never switched of we had to keep our seat belts on all the time.
[S] We couldn't use [inaudible] our seat uh..
[S] And the things get even worse then.
[S] Suddenly we fell like the air plane is having a fall of one hundred feet or something then
[S] Ah.. You know that feeling when the plane falls and it is just kind of..
[S] I was scared like hell at that part of time because i though I was going to die.
[S] And then suddenly the lights completely goes off at the plane.
[S] Ah.. To my misery, for the fist time in my life I experienced this oxygen masks dropping of. I've never used it before, i never had this experience, so..
[S] And the plane is sort of like free falling almost and I can't breath at that point of time
[S] And I can't even put the mask on. I was just shaking with panic at that point. This guy sitting next to me actually helped me to put the mask on.
[S] Then I could breath again, but uh..
[S] For another couple of ten seconds or so we actually felt the plane going down and down.
[S] It just felt so.. ah.. scary at that point of time.
[S] And because the lights in the plane were completely switched off we could see the lightning flashing outside
[S] This flashes of light coming inside were so scaring like the horror movies or something.
[S] Uh.. A few minutes later It kind of stabilize, the lights came on again. We were told to remove our masks and the plane went to the cruse altitude again. I think there was pretty much we were nearing the destination.
[S] Uh.. But It was really a tough time.  We stand fifteen minutes really (horrifying?). I was completely shaking ah..
[S] Even the landing at that point.. The landing was bumping as well, We just bumped twice before we stabilize on the runway.
[S] Ah.. It was like the most (horrifying?) experience in my life having that flight.
[S] I mean.. I'm glad the pilot was able to hand it, but..
[L] Uh.
[S] I'm never gonna take that flight again. On my way back I've canceled my flight, and I took the train back uh..
[S] It took me more time but I was at least safe, in my head.
[S] Probably I'm never gonna take a flight for a short distance again, at least if I know the plane is a small plane, then I'll never take.