[S] Hi, how are you doing?
[L] Hi! Good.
[S] How was your weekend?
[L] Ah, nice weekend.
[S] Nice weekend for you?
[L] Yeah..
[S] I've been, I've..we've known each other for some time now right? Almost, almost a year now
[L] Yeah, almost a  year.
[S] Yeah..I actually wanted to share something with you.
[L] Okay
[S] Do you like, do you like pets? Do you like animals in general?
[L] Yes I love (animals?)
[S] Yeah, even I..I love..I love animals. I love dogs essentially.
[L] Uh-huh.
[S] Um, uh, it's probably because when I grew up, I grew up with a dog. So my parents already had a dog, a Golden Retriever.
[S] Ah we called..we called her Pepper
[L] Uh-huh.
[S] So we had this dog even before I was born. My parents had this dog and they loved this dog I think.
[S]  I think they loved it even more than they loved me
[L]
[S] I have felt that jealousy growing up little bit.
[S] Ah, and it was amazing growing up with that dog because you always had somebody to play with
[S] and it is always pulling your leg or always trying to gather attention and then you focus on it and take it out for walks.
[S] Long walks I used to take it out and we used to play almost everyday because when growing up we don't have anything to do, you just play with your dog right?
[L]
[S] Yaa, but um, when I was seven..I remember when I was seven, it started to get really sick, uh, you know, dogs live really short you know, just one through seven kind of age
[S] and..and my parents had already had it for about two years before I was born so when I was seven or eight it started to get sick a lot, it barely walked and eventually it died off
[L] Hmm.
[S] Um, it was really tough, ah it was really sad times when the dog died, more for my parents than for me because well they were, they had this strange attachment to that dog
[S] Um, don't get me wrong, I also loved it a lot and I felt really sad but their sadness was like at another level, they were completely destroyed emotionally
[S] and they decided that they would never ever keep a dog again, they would never have a pet..pet again
[L] Yeah..
[S] Um, which was a bit weird for me because I wanted to have a dog, uh but I could understand like..partially like
[S] Fine, I mean, they..you always knew that dogs don't live that long and if it passes away
[S] I think..in my view the best  is to get another one and get another life and  help it and grow with it
[S] but, they decided not to have a dog and this went on till about eight, nine years, till the time I was at home
[S] and during my school and everything and then I moved out of my place, and I went to another city, doing my graduation there
[S] And I had a flat, small flat there and so I had enough space for me to actually get a dog so I..without my parents even knowing about it I actually bought a small pup
[S] I bought this..uh..uh..what do you call this dog, a Beagle, you know a Beagle?
[S] Uh, and I named it soldier because I wanted it to be a really strong dog and everything. Um and I had this dog for like ten..ten years now.
[L]
[S] I had this dog for ten years, uh all that I imagined I could do with a dog when I couldn't do when my parents didn't have one
[S] we used to hang around everyday, uh take him out for walks and he loved ice cream although I know it's not good for it
[S] But I used to feed him ice cream every now and then like a treat. I even..that time social media was new
[S] and I even opened a Facebook page on his name and um there were a lot of likes coming in everyday, so it was a really nice happy place
[S] But then again, uh ten years later uh the dog died.
[S] Uh and at that point I realized what my parents must have felt because I was devastated when the dog died.
[L]
[S] I mean..it was..the dog was my everything growing up, it was like my best friend, almost like a brother to me in a way that it always knew if I was feeling low or sad
[S] always would come and sit by me through the toughest of times, uh it was my only companion.
[S] And, um, when it died, um, I just felt hollow. I almost went in a depression, wouldn't talk to people for days.
[S] I remember the day when he passed away, um he was sick for sometime and then he..I was talking care of him and he died in my arms.
[L]
[S] It was like really even..even uh worse feeling for me because it died in my arms and I..I couldn't wake up..wake him up
[S] I pet him but he didn't wake up. Um the weirdest feeling was to bury him..uh.
[S] You know this dog was always jumping around, happy and always playing with you and now it doesn't move and I have to put it away
[S] and that day I realized that uh..what my parents must have gone through ah with..with Pepper for example.
[L]
[S] and..and I decided that day as well that I..it is very tough for me as well now to have another dog
[S] because well whenever I see a dog all what I can see in my head is images of Soldier going around and how we used to play and how we used to be companions.
[S] um..it was..yeah..uh..so I..I get my parents now. Why they didn't have a dog and probably it will be very difficult for me to have another dog
[S] although I will have these cherished memories with Soldier all my life because it's ten years of companionship
[S] It's very difficult to even explain people who haven't had a pet ever that what it feels like having ten years..ten years of this companion suddenly gone and you can't do anything about it
[L]
[S] Uh..but I still have the Facebook page, so I uh but I..I made it private now, nobody can see it but whenever I'm feeling low..I..
[S] Cause I used to post a lot of pictures and videos there..I..once every few months when I'm feeling low I go there and I see those videos again
[S] And kind of uh brings me up again, it makes me feel..remember those days again and feel happy about it
[S] Um..yeah..so..all in all I would say happy memories.
[S] One should experience this, have..have a pet and although there is sadness also sometimes that comes with it
[S] but I think it is worth the experience, the whole journey..itself.