[L] Hi
[S] How you doing?
[L] Good
[S] Do you like traveling?
[L] Yeah, I do
[S] Do you like air traveling?
[L] Depends
[L]
[S] If it's a long travel or a short one?
[L] No it depends on the weather where we are landing..
[L] Hamburg is not good usually
[L] Landing here is not so fun
[L]
[S] Ok
[S] I had a similar experience, but not landing, but going away
[S] Um, couple weeks ago I had to go to Brussels for a holiday and..
[S] I was looking a train and it takes a lot o time to go by train so..
[S] I thought I might take a fly that's normally expensive
[S]
[L] Uh-huh
[S] At the website I found this really cheap flight
[S] That I could use
[S] So I took that one, and I booked that flight and I went to the airport, I was taking it at the end of the evening this kinda of flight is almost the last one of the day
[S] So when I reached the airport, was a bit rainy and a bit windy, so I thought that it might be delayed  early..
[S] Took a lot of hours, actually
[S] And at last there was a huge huge queue for check-in
[S] Apparently, Uh, all the flights before ours were delayed because weather
[S] And there was a huge check-in queue and..
[S] Just at the airport.. I was waiting to many people at airport that normally doesn't have those many people there
[S] Um, this flight was reaching two hours early, I could barely manage to get to the boarding
[S] Because of the check-in, the security, it's just..
[S] Too many people
[S] And there were no systems do handle this many people
[L] Uh-huh
[S] So I reached at the gate at like..
[S] Two minutes or five minutes before the boarding closes
[S] They allowed me in but they were not very happy with that
[S]
[S] Um.. and you know that somehow these flights don't have these bridges to the plane then you have to go down and take the bus
[L] Yes
[S] I hate that
[S] I hate taking buses to the plane Um..
[S] It's just.. cramp there, it's like hurts getting into a..
[S] A vessel and then transporting to somewhere else
[S] So it's weird
[S] So we took the bus Uh..
[S] And went around the airport, eventually reached our plane
[S] And then I realized that is not a regular plane, was that a smaller propeller ones, like these really small ones  or something
[L] Yeah
[S] And I hate those planes, I had.. my worst plane experiences  with propeller planes
[S] I think they were not equipped to handle bad weather for starters and they just don't work very well with that weather it's not ideal for them
[S]
[S] Bad then it was a little bit to late to me to say, I don't wanna travel
[L]
[S] So I said, let's see how it goes
[S] Bad then it was a little bit to late to me to say, I don't wanna travel
[S] These guys were really pushing us because we were late or something..
[S] And they were just heading us to our seats, and them just said sit down we gonna start soon and everything..
[L] Uh-huh
[S] And they were a bit rude, not very pleasant to
[S] And they were just heading us to our seats, and them just said sit down we gonna start soon and everything..
[S] Um..
[S] So we were in ours seats, we were ready to fly and then this announcement that says, Hey we can not fly right now because well the flight control says..
[S] The weather is bad for take-off or something and then we are grounded for now..
[L] Uh-huh
[S] And we don't know how long it will take
[S] And at part of time I thought what the heck, why they hiding it from us in that point of time then..
[S] You must know this for some time given the other flights that
[S] And..
[S]  We were the tarmac, waiting to take-off for one hour
[S] And this.. they don't even switch on the air conditioning or something in this plane, so we were just sitting there almost no oxygen then..
[S] Just crowded up in this really small place
[S] It was just Uh..  just too frustrating experience just..
[S] Even before the flight took-off..
[S] i admit it did take-off, we have a.. we.. we went to the runway and took-off, the took-off was a bit shaky wasn't the most ideal one
[S] Probably was too windy for then, to handle such a light plane
[S] Um, we climb up to this Uh.. cruising altitude and..
[S] Like all, what we do is lose a belt  people want to use the lavatories
[S] Apparently they told us not we could do that..
[S] We can take off ours sit belts, because was turbulence all the time
[S] The plane started moving from left to right because it was to shaky
[S] They stopped the use of the lavatories  after some time
[S] Um, as we were stuck in our sit, the plane just shaking and.. Um..
[S] In my head I'm thinking what in the heck do I take this plane? I could've..
[S] Spend a little more money and actually save my life or.. and not having this experience
[L]
[S] Just when I was crossing my mind, it gets worst
[S] The lights go off, of the plane
[S] Apparently there was too much turbulence and then some systems just got damaged or flawed or something.. the lights go off..
[S] And.. it's lighting outside so we had these flashes of light coming in for us, seeming like a horror movie where..
[S] We were in a plane thousands of feet in the air and suddenly there is..
[S] There is no light there, there is light outside and..
[L]
[S] We started felling like the.. you know.. when the turbulence goes up the plane and forces
[S] At the end of this free falling (speed?) I feel like that
[S] Not just for momentary but for like.. Twenty seconds
[S] It's like it felt three hundred, for hundred feet
[S] And.. I have.. I had big issues with this claustrophobia.. the place already crowded up..
[S] I'm not feeling well anyway
[S] And now this happens
[S] And it doesn't stop it just keep going up and then falling really fast
[S] And going up and falling really fast, and in one point of time the oxygen masks dropped
[S] At that time.. I'm.. I'm gonna die it's my last flight ever
[L]
[S] And it's not gonna go well
[S] And I don't know how to use these masks
[S] We never had this experience so the guys next to me kinda help me to put this on
[S]  but then for the next fifteen, twenty minutes we were just doing this
[S] They will try to climb up the altitude and then fall again and do this again
[S] Terrible, terrible having a experience like we had, shaky plane Uh.. If I only think about that night, just so scared about it
[S] After go fifteen, twenty minutes, it kinda stabilized Uh.. Probably we were reaching our destination so they started to..
[S] The lights came on again.. We took off our masks and started the descent
[S] Um..
[S] Even the landing was bumping..  twice before it landed
[S] At that part I decided to myself, I will never gonna fly again
[S] At least not in  I'm gonna make sure it's not a small plane, not a propeller one for sure no way I'm doing that
[S] I canceled my flight back because it probably would be the same plane
[S] Um.. I took the train, took me twice the time or three times of the time but at least I was safer
[S] Even now I think I would never Uh.. take night flight out of this place and..
[S] Especially if it's a propeller plane
[S] The first think I will know before to book any flight it's what plane it is, what time it's flying
[S] Before I can even think what is the price I've to pay for it
[S] It was just a annoying, annoying experience and a scary one