[S] How you doing?
[L] Hey, I'm good
[S] Great, how was your weekend?
[L] Pretty good.
[S] Nice, I went to Norway to Tromsø, have you heard of Tromsø?
[L] No
[S] Sitting up north of the country
[L] Um
[S] It's really nice.. um.. I have a friend.. um, I have a friend.. um he is doing his  there so I decided to visit him
[S] Sitting up north of the country
[S]
[S] Hmm, yeah it's really cold.. in this period, actually very really cold and there is not a lot to do there, so it's some  small city
[S] Really expensive so, for a decent meal and a beer you will pay something like 25 euros which is..
[S] Well, you know, for students that's kinda of expensive
[S] But yeah, we had some fun  going around to some (parties?) Um..
[S] And had a lot of, you know, shopping with skin dolls, because it's really cold Um..
[S] Was dark most part of the time, but anyway
[S]
[L]
[S] It was a nice experience
[S] Um.. yeah at some point he ask me if I would try this.. Um, have you heard of this really smelly fish, which is supposed to be the smelliest food in the world?
[L] No truly
[S] No? So I don't remember the name in scandinavian it's like a herring.. so can fish fermented with salt which is supposed to be a thing that's.. I mean, the smelliest thing in the world
[S] There are.. I mean in the  in some youtube videos some.. you know.. reaction videos  people react to that, smelling and tasting
[S] Um, he told me that actually even it smells bad, it doesn't taste so bad
[S] I has been thinking if you wanna try. And I was like.. ok, I mean, we made a bet.. ok, let's try it
[S] Um, the thing is, I don't like fish, in general. So all this thing like tuna and stuff, you know, it's kinda of.. I don't like it.. so was kinda of double challenge for me because I'm already disgusted  by this fishy thing.
[S] But yeah, we just went to the supermarket.. got this.. can, you know, container can, Um..
[S] And I was really, all the time thinking, oh my god, this gonna taste so bad, and he was saying no, don't worry, I mean, the texture , but the smell is terrible bad, but it doesn't taste so bad
[S] Alright, so, we just Um.. went back from the supermarket, so we are not supposed to eat this indoors, because it smells so bad, alright, so strong, that they tell you, that you should, you know, consume this outdoors
[L] Ok
[S] Otherwise your house is gonna stink for, I mean, for days, weeks, whatever
[S]
[S] I was really suffering, because I had a similar experience in China, when I went to the (gym?)  we had this smelly tofu, have you heard smelly tofu?
[L] No
[S] So smelly tofu is like a really smelly version of tofu, it's just, you know, a piece of tofu which smells terrible, and I couldn't eat it, actually I just had a bite and I was felling can not say because..
[S] Uh, some people like it, you could see all the chinese people just eating that and saying it's actually good so..
[S] I was really scared about this thing, anyway, I just went for it, so..
[S] Um, we went outside the house to the park behind this place and Um.. yeah, that was the moment the we had to do it, you know, so we were just side by side with this can..
[L] Uh-huh
[S] And as soon as I opened the can is like, you know, the first way the fish smelled, just hit my face like a bomb, I was like, oh my god, this is really disgusting
[L]
[S]  like that yeah, smelly but not so much, but you could see, isn't only the smell, so the thing is, this was with kinda of slices of raw fish..
[S] Inside this, you know,  kinda of oil, jello, like tuna things, like really disgusting thing at least for me so..
[S] Um,  well, then I opened the can, and it took me like a couple of minutes to can of.. be able to (restand?) that, that smell
[S] And then I, well, you know, had to try it, he said, come on just do it, you will see, it's not so disgusting actually, I think
[S] So I, just took one of the slices and, also the texture was, you know,  sticky.. not sticky, but just like you know, oh my god, you know, so disgusting
[S] Um, yeah, I tried to give a bite, but I couldn't, so in the first time I just put it back
[S] And then I looked back to him, and he was actually biting that, but he was literally crying, you could see tears from his..  it's not that bad
[S] But it's terrible, he was like, oh my god, man you are lying to me, actually this thing tastes terrible, but it was a bet, I didn't want to say no, so yeah, I just, you know, it's ok I'll take it like a medicine
[L]
[S]  and I had some
[S] I don't know, I just, wow, it was so intense, I just, I mean, threw this thing to the floor, it was horrible, it was, you know this..
[S] Fishy, disgusting thing,  rotting.. this flavor of rotting things
[S] I couldn't make it, and my friend actually, he was, still crying, and he just had some more bites, and well, you know, he won the bet
[L]
[S] Um, but it took some time to just go back to normal, this thing was incredibly smelly, and I had this smell in my hands, it's a thing, you know, it's a psychological thing for days
[S] So my holiday to, I mean, in Norway was nice, but that is a thing that I won't fortunately not forget so easy