[S] Hey, how, how you doing? [L] Hello
[L] Fine, great, never better [S] Okay
[S] Um do you like traveling?
[L] Yeah, it's so nice
[S] Yeah, do you like traveling in the airplanes, do you like air travel much?
[L] Yeah, as well, like cause, I mean [S] Yeah?
[L] Even though I know that it's really nice to enjoy also the..
[L] Traveling part, but also good [S] The train, yeah
[L] Reaching the place  [S] Reach it fast, yeah, yeah, I have the same opinion, but
[S] I'm scared of airplane travel actually
[S] And most of it because well um, um, you know?
[S] Back where I come from, like it's really small airports
[S] So it doesn't have like huge planes going, so we have these really small planes
[S] And I don't like those planes anymore.. yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah [L] Some noisy airplane
[S] I had a recent experience, like couple of weeks back, I had to travel to uh Brussels
[S] And took this uh cheap flight I found online on the last minute deals or something [L]
[S] And this was like the night flight or something, like the last flight of the day
[S] Like 9:30 pm or 10 pm in the night [L] Uh-huh
[S] It was really cheap, I thought well it's one hour, shouldn't be that much of a problem
[L] Yeah.. uh-huh [S] So I took the flight, I reach the airport a couple of hours before the boarding time
[S] Uh it was like a rainy night, like a regular raining, windy kind of an evening
[S] Uh and when I reach the airport I see, well, it's, it's
[S] Fully packed, it's like jam packed of people, and there's a huge queue for check in
[L] Hmm.. Uh-huh [S] Um apparently all the flights before mine were delayed because of the weather
[S] So there were these so many people at the airport, the check in lines
[S] The security queue, everything was completely full and there were so many people there
[S] Somehow I barely managed to reach the boarding gate
[S] In time so that I could board before they closed [L] Uh-huh
[S] I mean even though I reached two, two, two hours before I, before I had to do this but
[S] The whole rush was just too much for me to manage one time
[S] And I reach the boarding, they were not too happy to let me in
[S] Because I was just on time, and a bit, I mean a bit late
[S] Uh but they allowed me to board
[S] You know er some of these flights don't have this bridge to the, to the flight
[S] And you have to go down and take that bus [L] Yeah
[S] Uh to the flight, I don't like that bus, like [L]
[S] Putting sheep in, in a bus and just letting them go
[S] So [L] Right so they didn't pay enough to go the right to the airplane
[S] Yeah, yeah, exactly, right? So they would take in a specially car [L]
[S] Something no, you have to take this bus and go there [L]
[S] So I boarded the bus and the bus took some time
[S] To go and reach to the plane, and then I see that this is
[S] The small plane with these propeller blades there [L]
[S] And I was like oh god, this is not gonna go well.. um [L]
[S] This really small plane, like 60 seater or 70 seater, really cramped
[L] Uh-huh, I'm so tall have to uh walk down [S] Yeah, it's really small
[S] How does fit so many people in it. And they just forced us in.
[S] Because I think they were getting late or something, so these just rushed us into our seats [L] Uh-huh
[S] The crew were also not very polite, they were a bit rude
[S] Uh so we were forced to our seats, we sat down
[S] Um and we were suddenly told that um
[S] The, the traffic control has told us that they can't fly right now
[S] Because of the weather, and we have to wait for some time [L] Hmm
[S] We, we were stuck at the tarmac for one hour
[S] Waiting for the flight to take off hmm
[S] And at that time you know, they don't even switch on the air conditioning
[S] It's cramped and it's like, it's really annoying
[S] And for me, I'm claustrophobic, I'm getting like really annoyed
[S] And scared at that point in time, I couldn't breathe [L] Uh-huh
[S] Just so annoying for me
[S] Anyway after one hour we go to the runway and we take off
[S] When we take off is a bit shaky
[S] I mean there's too much wind, the weather is just too bad for, for the flight
[S] And the propeller blades are not, they're not even strong to handle that now, that weather
[L] They shake a lot because of the weather [S] Way too much, way too much
[S] We reach this cruising altitude, and
[S] The plane was literally shaking left to right and
[S] They didn't um switch off the seat belt sign
[S] The, the lavatories were not allowed to be used, we couldn't go [L]
[S] Because well the plane was shaking that much [L] Yeah
[S] And all of a sudden we see that the lights go off
[S] The plane lights went off
[S] And there was lightning outside so we could see these flashes of light coming in
[S] Is like a scene from a horror movie or something
[S] You're in the flight and suddenly there's no light [L] Hmm
[S] And you see these flashes of uh lightning
[S] And everybody was scared because well it was moving too much
[S] And there's no light now suddenly, the, the emergency lights are on
[S] Um [L] No information to you?
[S] No the guy there was, there's too much turbulence we can't do anything
[S] We should keep calm and everything but.. well at that point in time everybody was just too scared
[L] Do nothing actually  [S] Yeah, we can't do anything, right?
[S] And, and then you know how in turbulence sometimes the plane goes up and down
[S] And it feels like it's falling er
[S] So I felt this fall like not just for one second
[S] But like 20, 30 seconds of this fall [L]
[S] It felt like the plane fell like, 300, 400 feet down
[S] And I was scared, I was scared as hell, I was already really, really scared
[S] Because there was too many people in this small place and, and
[S] The propeller blades going with that sound
[S] And the plane then falls and all my, it's like all my nightmares are coming true now
[S] That we're gonna die or something [L] Was anyone screaming like?
[L]  [S] Uh not yet, but, but people were on the edge of the seat
[S] They were, they were not very comfortable with what happening [L] Just holding it hard
[L] The seat  [S] They, they were, you could see people are scared and a bit frightened
[S] And the worst happened, the oxygen masks fall down
[S] Which has never happened to me before [L]
[S] Like you think about when they're telling this, during this, during take off
[S] That these will help you, but you never think this, this gonna happen [L] Yeah
[S] And these fall off and I don't have any experience working with the oxygen mask so I, I
[S] So I'm struggling with it, so the guy sitting next to me actually help me put my mask on [L] Hmm
[S] So I could breathe properly, meanwhile we still fell that the plane is falling
[S] And is going up, and then falling again, then going up, and falling again
[S] And everybody is scared at this point in time [L] Just waiting for your death
[S] It's like this is gonna be the last flight and we're doomed [L] Uh-huh
[S] And everybody is scared now, you know, kids are crying on the plane
[S] Because they can't take this uh fluctuation
[S] This goes on for next 15, 20 minutes, with the masks on, flight goes up, flight goes down
[S] And after 20 minutes or so it kind of stabilized
[S] Probably we, we cleared the area from, from the bad weather
[S] We reached uh closer to our destination
[S] Um and we start the descent, so we were told to turn off our masks
[S] Uh the lights came on again, it was a bit uh a bit stabilized
[S] People allowed to go to the lavatory, so it kind of became normal
[S] And then er we landed, even the landing was bumpy
[S] We jumped onto the runway twice before we actually landed [L]
[S] Worst harrowing experience of my life [L] Yeah
[S] Of flying, I'm already scared while I'm flying
[S] And this was like my, all my nightmares coming true
[S] I canceled my flight on the way back, I took the train
[S] Although it took like three times the more time, but I was, I felt much safer [L] Yeah
[S] I think from now on I'll be really scared traveling
[L] In any kind of airplane [S] In a small plane.. in any plane, sure
[S] And, and I'll make sure that when I'm booking a flight, it's not a night flight
[S] It's a day flight and it's not a small plane
[S] It's a big plane, even though I have to pay more money, that's fine [L] Yeah, that's terrible
[S] But I just can't go through the whole thing again [L] Yeah
[S] I just