[L] good and you ?
[S] good good how was your weekend ?
[L] great as always
[S]
[S] it's great I went to Norway had a trip to Norway
[L] uh I've always wanted to go there
[S] yeah to visit a friend actually well no to I mean
[S] to the capital just Tromsø you know have you ever heard of Tromsø ?
[L] yeah
[S] up north um I have a friend there he's doing his
[S]
[S] study since so long so I've always wanted to you know see the area although in this period it's really cold
[S] but we had some fun just went around the thing is it's really expensive there
[S] such as for kinda piece of meal and a beer you end up paying twenty five euros that's not great for a student
[L] yeah always
[S] but was nice we just you know went around had some fun some local parties
[S] and then he asked me about this have you ever heard this kind of really smelly fish that is supposed to be the smelliest
food in the world ?
[L] yeah uh-huh
[S] yeah well I was not so familiar with that and he told me and um apparently it's a big thing in these Scandinavian countries so
food in the world ?
[S] he wanted me to try it and he said that even if it's really smelly the taste is not that bad
[S] I was like uh ok you know I was not so sure if he's was telling the truth but anyway
[S] we made a bet and we should try it and he I mean he hasn't he has never tried it either so
[S] we decided  just to you know have this thing and try it together um..
[S] the thing is I don't like fish in general so this fishy smell or taste is something I hate in general so even tuna or salmon so
[S] for me it was kinda of a double challenge but I don't like losing bets so  I just went for it
[S] so I went to the supermarket we got these you know kind of really I don't know bad looking cans so
[S] and I in my mind I was already just feeling the disgust but I just went for it so you're not supposed to eat this thing indoors 'cause you're house is gonna
[S] smell like hell for the next day so
[S] they advised to eat outdoors so we just went to a forest behind his place (plenty?) of place you know um
[S] so yeah so we went there um I was preparing myself psychologically for.. for this
[S] um I was really suffering actually it was like a torture the whole time like
[L]
[S] I.. we hadn't even opened the can and I was already suffering and imagining how this thing could be and I started to think about my experience in Beijing in China when I tried the smelly tofu
[S] yeah have you tried the smelly tofu ?
[L] I haven't
[L]
[S] they call it smelly tofu because it's really smelly tofu so it's a strong smell and taste was terrible
[S] and you know well but my friend told me don't worry doesn't taste that bad it's just a smell once you try it it's gonna be alright I didn't believe him
[S] so we just you know started opening the can and as soon as I just you know opened a part of the can was like wow way
[S] a fishy smell right in my face you know something really disgusting um not only the smell but also the you know the look
[S] you know just kind of raw slices of
[L]
[L] rotten or ?
[S] yeah it's like fermented with salt this kind of you know the slices of raw fish with the jello like water and oil and
[L] hmm
[L] yummy
[S] yeah it's like fermented with salt this kind of you know the slices of raw fish with the jello like water and oil and
[S] puff yeah it was really disgusting actually it's like there's no way that this thing is gonna taste good um..
[S] and then you know I just really my friend just brought it to his face to smell it better and he literally started to cry you know I could see the tears yeah this doesn't smell that bad
[L]
[S] then I realized yeah this is it was a really bad idea but just you know I'll just do it I don't care so um
[S] and then you know I just really my friend just brought it to his face to smell it better and he literally started to cry you know I could see the tears yeah this doesn't smell that bad
[S] I let's say tried to grasp one slice of this sticky gluey thing in my hands
[S] and the whole thing was disgusting so not only the smell also the texture of that thing was disgusting but anyway I just tried to give it a bite but I couldn't I was just literally
[S] rejecting that whole thing I look at my friend he was crying he was trying to
[S] not that bad but it actually was terrible right ? so he was crying and yeah at some point I just took the thing um you know just do like this
[S] got a bite
[L]
[S] yeah like a medicine but I couldn't man I just spit it I just threw it to the ground I couldn't it was just
[S] too much was really disgusting my friend just gave it a bite he couldn't finish it but um he won the bet
[L]
[S] um and that taste kind of stayed in my mouth for weeks so that's kind of the let's say the worst
[S] and also the most interesting experience that I had in Norway