[S] How has your weekend been? [L] Weekend? Was nice.
[L] I guess I'm most of the time at home, relaxing.. yeah [S] Yeah, yeah, I know, I know that feeling
[S] Yeah, I guess. Today I'm gonna tell you two stories about myself um..
[S] First off, would you think you.. would you say that you're an introvert?
[L] Um.. I would say so
[S] Yeah.. I guess you kind of have to to be a computer scientist right? It's hard to avoid  [L] Yeah.. yeah
[S] Cause I'd say I'm also pretty introverted obviously um..
[S] Especially when I was younger, that was a big thing, I grew up in South Africa
[S] And it's very easy to be introverted there cause you spend a lot of time at home essentially [L] Hmm
[S] I spent a lot of times playing video games on my own, I..
[S] It was a bit lonely but I didn't really mind, like I enjoy being by myself kind of
[S] That was good for me.. uh.. [L] Uh-huh cool
[S] I didn't know, I always thought that people in Africa like
[S] Like to enjoy time outside  [L]  ah well I'm, I'm a bit special
[S] Yeah but uh yeah and I was like that for most of my youth
[S] Um and that was fairly
[S] Uh average thing for me until.. it did change a bit when I moved to sweden
[S] So I moved to Sweden at around age of
[S] 11, 12 I think? Uh is when I moved um..
[S] And once again I became a bit, a bit more introverted
[S] Cause I'm now in a new country and I don't speak the language  kind of it's like [L]
[S] Uh yeah so that didn't help um [L] Interesting
[S] And it took me quite a while to find a new friend
[S] One of the first friends I found was actually a girl from class
[S] So I started in like this middle, lower middle school class kind of um..
[S] And I met this girl there, and she was really fascinating to me cause she was very outgoing
[S] Very kind of brave, very independent
[S] Which was like the exact opposite of me cause I was like shy, introverted, and scared of everything.. uh.. [L] Uh-huh
[S] And we spent a lot of time together, because we, I spent time like watching cartoons together
[S] Playing video games, and coming up, like going, going around doing like, yeah, it was pretty great [L] Nice
[S] Ah going around causing mischief and stuff uh
[L] So it helped you a lot like to..  on your life [S] Yeah, she really helped like
[S] Yeah, get going, it really helped me like kind of settle and get into the conf, self confidence you know? Uh.. [L] Uh-huh
[S] Uh one of the things that we did do actually was that we lived very close to like a lumber processing plant
[S] Was where they keep all the wood for like making furniture
[S] So they had a big yard where they had all these wooden planks and stuff [L] Hmm
[S] Uh so what her and me would do is she would sneak in
[S] And we would kind of take planks, and we would steal planks
[S] And we would use these to build like a go cart essentially
[S] So we had this uh box essentially, and then we had wheels on the side
[S] And her and me over the weekends would kind of build this up, so we would like
[S] Nail new boards there, we could add an extra seat
[S] And then we would add like a trunk, and then we would add (spoilers?) to make it go faster or something
[S] I don't know, we were kids, we weren't the smartest people  [L] Uh-huh
[S] Uh and what we did was that we would usually
[S] Take this and then put it on top of a hill, right? So I had this big sloping hill next to my house
[S] And it was asphalted so it was like very, pretty good for speed  eh.. [L] Yeah
[S] And so we.. no, we will get there [L] It's not so safe
[S] Cause I actually did actually injure myself quite a lot, so what we do is we  let it fall down kind of this hill um..
[S] There was this one day where we rolled it, we rolled it top of the hill, I sat in
[S] And then she was gonna like just let me, uh let me go down the hill
[S] But instead she kind of really pushed me, essentially, so she really rocketed me down the hill kind of [L]
[S] And I, I was like holding on for dear life and I was really like sp, spazzing out
[S] And but then the thing started to wobble and it turned to the side, and it flipped kind of
[S] And then but so then I stuck onto the side, but I was still stuck in it, right? So my legs were still stuck in the go cart [L]
[L] Woah [S] Ah so then the only thing I could do was I had to brace with the right side of my body
[S] And so I kind of scraped the asphalt for a couple of feet
[S] And there was like I lost a lot of skin, there was a lot of blood kind of  [L]
[S] I was screaming and crying, she was screaming and crying
[S] And like I was like paralyzed, couldn't do anything like [L]
[S] So she had to run off and fetch my dad, like to come and save me from this mess that I'd put myself in [L]
[S] Uh yeah it was pretty.. it was pretty bad [L] Intense
[S] It was pretty intense yeah, but it's the kind of like
[S] It's the kind of stuff that you remember, right? So this is the kind of
[S] So it's kind of, I didn't really regret it, even though it was very, very stupid
[S] I didn't really regret, cause that was the kind of stuff you remember when you remember when you're a bit older, right?
[S] These things you did as a kid that would probably kill me if I did them now, right? [L] Yeah
[L] And you never played with her again like after this [S] Ah.. I mean
[S] We play for quite eh um
[S] Her and me did play with each other for quite a long time after this
[S] Although it didn't last for that long actually, cause I'd known her for like..
[S] 6 or 7 months I think
[S] And then she let me know that her dad had got a job in Asia [L] Hmm
[S] Ah and her family would be moving, so it's like [L] Hmm
[S] I was very worried about this kind of
[S] Cause I'd just met this new friend, like kind of in this new country  finally>
[L] She became like your best friend and all, she was [S] Yeah, yeah, she became a really good friend
[S] And now like she's moving, it's like fuck, it's like goddammit what am I gonna do now [L] Hmm
[S] Ah we did exchange phone numbers to try and keep in touch kind of, but uh..
[S] When she did move over there, I tried to call her, and it didn't work too well kind of
[S] Cause like apparently Swedish sim cards don't work that well in China, so like [L] Yeah
[S] It didn't like, we had a lot of trouble like, we didn't really get
[S] Weren't able to get in touch with each other, so she just kind of disappeared, which was
[S] Yeah it [L] Especially when you are young, I think
[S] Yeah you're fragile and sensitive when you're that young, it's very dangerous [L] Yeah
[S] Uh so that was.. uh she spoke English to me luckily  [L] She speak our language in that time?
[S] Ah yeah so I did lose contact with her for a while
[S] And this was before like facebook and stuff, so I couldn't really get in touch with her
[S] Uh so it went a couple of years before I heard from her again kind of [L] Hmm
[S] I think it was about five years uh..
[S] And then when she did actually contact me on facebook, like later on, five years later
[S] Right? And it's like when I got the message from her, I was like wow you're still alive that's amazing  [L]
[S] Um.. but.. yeah  [L] Recovering from that incident, right?
[S] It took me that long to recover, it's like, well it was like, it was a pretty long time later kind of
[S] And then we started to chat like about like ah
[S] What her and me had done in the past kind of
[S] Like how we were as people, how we were in life now, like what we were doing
[S] Uh.. and we talked for a while about this, but I realized that like
[S] After she'd moved she'd changed a lot
[S] Then I guess that I'd also changed a lot as well, just kind of because it's like you change a lot when you're a kid, right?
[L] Ah.. also because of the culture that's different in a [S] Ah so we talked
[S] Yeah the culture, and like changing, just finding new friends [L] Yeah
[S] And stuff, you become a different person, you get different hobbies and stuff uh
[S] So she had changed a lot.. yeah, I, I, I got worse, this is yeah [L] Forgot you
[S] Um but yeah, she had changed a lot and I had changed a lot
[S] So we talked for a while, but like the conversation just kind of, the messages kept getting shorter
[S] And we didn't really like talk that much after a while, eventually we just stopped talking [L] Yeah
[S] And I haven't really talked to her ever since, which is a shame but
[S] I guess that's how life is I guess
[S] You live, you learn, you keep growing [L] Yeah
[S] Right?  yeah, yeah [L]  this is true