[S] so you had a good weekend?
[L] yeah it was nice what about yours?
[S] yeah it was alright  yeah just kinda took it easy this weekend
[L] ok
[S] so today I'm gonna tell you two stories about myself about my past and stuff I've done in the past uh..
[L] uh-huh
[S] first of would you say that you're an introvert?
[L] yeah
[S] yeah I'm also a bit introverted I think you have to kinda be to end up as a computer scientist
[S] yeah I've been like this since I was a kid specially when I grew up I grew up in South Africa kinda and so back then I was kinda.. enjoyed spending a little time
[L] uh-huh
[S] or spent a lot of time on my own and I actually kind of enjoyed it even though it was kinda of very lonely yeah it was kind of
[L] oh ok
[S] very relaxing for me and I was like that for quite a long time when I was young I did move to Sweden around the age of
[S] eleven, twelve I think I moved to Sweden
[L] uh-huh how did you find moving to Sweden?
[S] it was an experience obviously since I was.. I was very lonely in the beginning it was a bit of a shock kinda specially when they first told I was gonna move I actually (curled?) up
[S] like (at?) sofa and cried because like I was so scared of moving and leaving my family or even some parts of mt family behind and stuff but moving to Sweden was.. it was an experience I.. it was very
[L] ok
[S] scary in the beginnig I was bit lonely.. kinda you now new kids, I didn't speak the language.. I did eventually start school.. in school kind of I started in like
[L] hm..
[S] (lower?) elementary school uh.. and there I met my first kinda Swedish friend was this one girl she was really like.. it was interesting she was very outgoing and independent which is
[L] hm
[S] very different from who I was as a person 'cause I was very reclusive kinda of and shy and she was always very outgoing very happy very cheerful very like.. it was really.. I really admired her kind of a..
[S] (lower?) elementary school uh.. and there I met my first kinda Swedish friend was this one girl she was really like.. it was interesting she was very outgoing and independent which is
[L] hm
[S] very different from who I was as a person 'cause I was very reclusive kinda of and shy and she was always very outgoing very happy very cheerful very like.. it was really.. I really admired her kind of a..
[S] and.. and she spoke English which was definitely a plus 'cause I did not speak any Swedish at the time uh.. so I spent a lot of time with this girl we used to watch a lot of like
[L] yeah?
[L] ok
[S] and.. and she spoke English which was definitely a plus 'cause I did not speak any Swedish at the time uh.. so I spent a lot of time with this girl we used to watch a lot of like
[S] Saturday.. Saturday morning cartoons kinda we saw a lot of cartoons together and like played video game and  stuff and it was great fun kinda uh.. we used to together get up to a lot of stuff
[S] kind of like out in the world we did this one thing where we uh.. do you know like there are these lumbered processing planks where they
[S] kinda keep all the planks before they make them into furniture yeah we lived close to one of those actually me and her used to sneak in and kind of sneak off certain planks that were like old
[L] ok
[S] and not being used and stuff and what we'd do with this planks is we kind of build a go kart with them so we'd like take some hammer and nails like nail things together we'd put some wheels on it
[L] hm
[L] oh
[S] and not being used and stuff and what we'd do with this planks is we kind of build a go kart with them so we'd like take some hammer and nails like nail things together we'd put some wheels on it
[S] kind of.. yeah.. I mean if you're a kid you've got to limitless creativity right? yeah so it's like we nailed this
[L] very creative
[L]
[S] kind of.. yeah.. I mean if you're a kid you've got to limitless creativity right? yeah so it's like we nailed this
[L] that's true
[S] this thing together we'd put an extra seat in it and we'd put.. we'd put a trunk on it and like (spoils?) to make it go faster or something I don't know.. like I don't know it's kinds in the camp we'd do things just it's nail
[L] yeah?
[S] things to kind that we think that looks cool right.. and this thing kinda of workedish.. like what we did was actually we had this big slope next to my house essentially which is like an asphalted
[L] yeah.. yeah that's true
[S] asphalted slope and then what we'd do is we take we'd take what's it called? go kart to the top of the slope and then we'd.. I'd sit in it and like ride down the hill kinda
[L] uh-huh
[L] oh
[S] asphalted slope and then what we'd do is we take we'd take what's it called? go kart to the top of the slope and then we'd.. I'd sit in it and like ride down the hill kinda
[S] this was not the best idea I'm sure you can imagine like it's unlimited.. it's like.. yeah well I mean it didn't always.. It wasn't.. It was courageous
[L]  very courageous
[S] but it didn't always end that well like because there was this one time when I actually got pretty badly hurt when we were riding this thing so like the thing is what we were doing is the same thing we like took it to the top of this hill essentially
[L] ok
[L] oh
[S] but it didn't always end that well like because there was this one time when I actually got pretty badly hurt when we were riding this thing so like the thing is what we were doing is the same thing we like took it to the top of this hill essentially
[S] and then one of us was sitting in it normally we'd just let it roll down what happened this time was like I was sitting in the kart and then my friend she was behind me she essentially just
[L] uh-huh
[S] gave me gave me a really like push like down the hill and it went really fast and I was like bobbling when I was doing down it kind of like (curved?) like flipped over kind of
[L] oh
[L] oh no
[S] gave me gave me a really like push like down the hill and it went really fast and I was like bobbling when I was doing down it kind of like (curved?) like flipped over kind of
[S] and like the problem was like I was still stuck in the kart right? so like I.. my legs were still in the kart so I couldn't really get out so I hat to like brace with the right of my body on the way down and I really like hit the ground like
[S] and I slid a bit like kind of and really like scraped off a layer of skin and there was a lot of blood and I was like screaming and half out a bit ans she was like
[L]uh.. oh my god
[S] panicking and she had to run of and get my dad kinda 'cause I was just lying there in the blood screaming this was pretty bad but you get up to stupid things as kid you know, as kid you're
[S] pretty like resilient right? you can get away with like a lot of stuff can it probably kill me now? to be honest uh.. yeah so yeah we got to a lot of
[L] yeah.. yeah that's true
[L] that's true that's true
[S] pretty like resilient right? you can get away with like a lot of stuff can it probably kill me now? to be honest uh.. yeah so yeah we got to a lot of
[S] mischief and like weird stuff like that kinda it was for a couple of months at least uh.. sadly this didn't really last 'cause I knew her for a couple of months but actually just after I had moved
[L] oh
[S] and known her for a while  then she actually told me that her dad had gotten a job in Asia.. and that she'd be moving away kind of uh.. and I was
[L] oh..
[L] hm
[S] and known her for a while  then she actually told me that her dad had gotten a job in Asia.. and that she'd be moving away kind of uh.. and I was
[S] pretty shaken up by this 'cause I just made my new friend after moving and now she was moving away kind of uh.. and I was very scared of this kind of uh.. and I was very..
[S] sad and almost afraid of being really lonely again essentially 'cause I got to used to her being around kinda.. so we exchange phone numbers 'cause this was a bit before like when social media really
[S] got on like I guess I  msn or something.. uh.. so we exchanged phone numbers and I tried to call her after she moved but it didn't like work
[L] hm
[S] kind of so.. so I couldn't really get in touch with her essentially
[L] so you've never heard of her anymore?
[S] uh.. not necessarily actually she did contact me a couple of years later I had like a Facebook essentially once it gotten started off five years later or something she actually did like (count the blue?)  from
[L] oh
[S] from someone and she contacted me and said was like hey how's it you going like.. and I was like wow you're still alive  um.. yeah so we chatted for a while and then we talked with each other about what we done in the
[L]
[S] past like nostalgic stuff uh.. I chatted with her but I did actually realize after a while that she had changed quite a lot as a person I guess you do change
[S] like specially when you're a kid you change very quickly and like moving and you grow up kind of I was like.. it's been five years I was seventeen at this point that time so was she so we changed quite a lot as
[L] yeah..
[L] hm
[S] like specially when you're a kid you change very quickly and like moving and you grow up kind of I was like.. it's been five years I was seventeen at this point that time so was she so we changed quite a lot as
[S] people since then so yeah eventually the conversation started to die out a bit kinda it's a bit sad but like I enjoyed it was a fun experience while it lasted kinda
[L] hm
[L] good memories
[S] people since then so yeah eventually the conversation started to die out a bit kinda it's a bit sad but like I enjoyed it was a fun experience while it lasted kinda
[S] yeah eventually we did stop talking and then I sadly didn't hear from her since but yeah.. fun while it lasted at least.. and that..
[L] yeah that's cool