[S] Okay great where were we before we were interrupted um..
[S] Okay so  so after my friend had left
[S] For ages shortly after she had left I was a bit down in the dumps kind of
[S] I didn't really uh I just lost my close friend, I needed a kind of way to distract myself in some sense
[S] Er so I started to get a lot into music kind of
[S] Um.. do you like music? [L]  Yeah, I love music
[S] Oh very good, cause I really got into music kind of
[S] And I really wanted my parents to buy me an instrument kind of
[S] Like a guitar or something, so it kind of er..
[S] Kind of  get out, kind of get out of my system
[S] My parents viewed it more as a kind of phase essentially
[S] Just something I was going through, so they did kind of ignore me in some regard
[S] To a large extent kind of, they just thought it would pass
[S] But I just kept nagging them so it's like  it became a bit of a balance there
[S] The closest I can get was eventually I convinced them to send me to a music oriented high school kind of
[S] Once I graduated from middle school essentially
[S] So essentially they allowed me to go this kind of more, high school with a more emphasis on music
[S] If I could also go and attend normal, real classes there kind of
[S] And not just these weird musical classes
[S] And that went great kind of, the school was very nice
[S] I had a lot of fun there, the food was good, a bit better than here  [L]
[S] Um so yeah no I really enjoyed going to school there
[S] But there was one thing I, one problem, one major problem I had with that school
[S] There was this one mandatory course called er classical music theory [L] Uh-huh
[S] And.. the problem with this course was I really..
[S] I'm pretty sure the teacher was a kind of demon in the shape of a human kind of thing [L]
[S] She was pretty awful, she used to really yell at students
[S] And belittle them, and like drag students around by the ear and stuff, it was pretty bad [L] Hmm
[S] I.. I really did not like this teacher  she was pretty awful
[S] Ah the good thing was that I actually met a couple people like me
[S] And some of those students took her class, and I essentially bonded with these four guys kind of
[S] Over just hating this particular teacher because she was just an awful human being kind of
[S] Ah which was interesting
[S] But yeah and that continued on for about a year, I went to this school kind of, I really enjoyed myself
[S] After one year essentially we had to give this presentation on classical music theory
[S] In front of the entire class, and I was very nervous about this because I was still very shy
[S] And shy kind of as a person at that point in time [L] Uh-huh
[S] So partially just having to present in front of the entire class was a problem
[S] And then the fact that I had to present in front of this teacher which I was just terrified of essentially
[S] Cause she was just evil  um..
[S] So I did spend a lot of time like practicing and preparing for this
[S] And I rehearsed and I kind of, well I felt fairly confident [L] Uh-huh
[S] So I went up and I gave the presentation
[S] And people laughed and they applauded when I was done, I thought I'd done a really good job
[S] Um but once I was done, the teacher really like laid into my presentation
[S] Like no this wrong, why did you say this, you can't mean this, why did you do this
[S] Can you just speak louder? It's like.. and I was really like distraught after this kind of
[S] Cause I was a very fragile person, so I actually had to go like, I basically cried essentially
[S] And I went back home and I told my parents I can't deal with this kind of, this is too much for me um..
[S] So we had to go and with the school kind of, see if we could do anything about it
[S] But like the school said that basically she's on a bunch of boards, we can't get rid of her, so she's basically there to stay
[S] Ah and I couldn't just deal with her anymore like because it was a mandatory course
[S] Sure but like, couldn't handle her for another two years er.. [L] Uh-huh
[S] So eventually we discussed and like we decided to send me to like
[S] This musical high school shared a lot of courses with the normal high school essentially
[S] So I could transfer over to the normal without like impacting my studies too much
[S] And my parents were also happy I was back to a more technical subject as well  [L]
[S] So I, yeah I eventually went to the normal high school and finished my curriculum there
[S] It was a shame I couldn't finish at the musical school but you know  life [L] Yeah
[S] Um.. I did actually meet up with one of the guys that went to the musical school when I went to college
[S] So I went to college, I met up with, I found  in the corridor, said hey how are you doing?
[S] And we talked a bit and it's ah no we're still playing in this band kind of er..
[S] With the other four guys I'd met earlier on
[S] And then he said like ah you should join us some time, it would be fun. I was like me?  [L]
[S] It's like yeah, yeah, I remember you're good at singing. Like really? Oh, okay
[S] So I actually did sing for them as vocalist
[S] I did sing and we played and we practiced a bit kind of
[S] And eventually we arranged to have a bit of a like concert for um.. some of our friends and
[S] Close friends and stuff and it's like that was a really good experience
[S] Cause like when we had that concert, I really felt like I was alive kind of, I really felt like I was on cloud nine, it was a great experience [L] Uh-huh
[S] Er.. so that was yeah so
[S] That's how I got to sing in a band and still keep in touch with them