[S] Hey, how you doing?
[L] I'm great
[S] How was your weekend?
[L] Nice weekend!
[S] Uh, my weekend was nice too.
[S] I'll tell you something, I went to Norway
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Uh, have you been traveling by the way?
[L] No
[S] No? Well, it's kinda of cold this period I wanted to visit a friend he went out to study in Tromsø
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Which is in the north, it's north part of the country
[S]
[S] Uh, it was really nice, so spike of cold temperatures we had a lot of fun
[S] Everything is really expensive there, so really choose maybe having a beer or going out for dinner.
[L] Hmm
[S] It's kinda a lot for a student
[S] Everything is really expensive there, so really choose maybe having a beer or going out for dinner.
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Uh, but we had fun (also point?) he told me you know about this kinda of food they have is a fish called.. I forgot the name
[S] Middle language something like  which is some kinda of  or fish
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Which is supposed to be the smelliest food in the world
[L] Um
[S]  Have you heard it?
[S]  No?
[L] Ah, I have heard it, I have heard it
[S] Yeah? So, yes, is this kinda of, you know..fish fermented with salt which prevents it from..you know rotting they says it's really smelly and..
[L] Hm
[S] But then he told me that is delicious, right? And..it's like..ok, I don't know, so I checked in the internet there were different versions about it  some people saying it's great, some people saying it's bad
[S]
[S] So then we'd meal that and then, hmm she said ok the guy who can finish, you know, this fish wins..
[L] Yeah
[L] Uh-huh
[S] So then we'd meal that and then, hmm she said ok the guy who can finish, you know, this fish wins..
[S]  ok let's do it I was curious, I really like trying different things, I tried the smelly tofu in China for example, and it was really smelly and really disgusting
[L]
[S] Um, so we went to this place and got it and this thing is so smelly that you should eat outdoors
[L] Yeah
[S]  whenever you offer to someone or whenever you order it, you are not supposed to eat indoors because I guess your house can stink for days so..
[S] Just went to the, you know, out to this garden that she got
[L] Uh-huh
[S] So, she got a beautiful house, by the way, so we went there and..alright..so..
[L] Yeah?
[S] Already, it was already challenging to open this can, you know..it's just like.. tuna can
[S] I openned.. oh my god.. that's really.. was really.. intense smell, you know.. this raw..
[S] Fermented fish, it's like.. oh my god.. it's really really  disgusting, but he was like saying come on man if you try it, you will see, you will love it
[S] I was like.. alright
[S]  So we.. what we really decided to also take the whole experience.. you know? Just kinda of.. you know.. to see around the reactions to it
[L] Uh-huh
[S]  Hmm.. the  as soon I saw his face really.. you know.. disgusted.. I realized that he will.. he will like it so.. it wasn't like it was really.. you know.. delicious, supposed to be
[S]  So we.. what we really decided to also take the whole experience.. you know? Just kinda of.. you know.. to see around the reactions to it
[L] Hmm
[S]  Hmm.. the  as soon I saw his face really.. you know.. disgusted.. I realized that he will.. he will like it so.. it wasn't like it was really.. you know.. delicious, supposed to be
[S]  Um.. but then yeah, I didn't want to lose the bet
[L] Hmm
[S] Um.. just said ok, I have to do it
[S] So it was similar like I living in China.. you know it's just supposed to like.. oh my god
[L] Uh-huh
[S] But I went for it  you know.. I don't really like fish, in general, so for me it was double challenge
[S] All this kind of.. you know.. raw fish that they eat for example in the Netherlands
[S]  But yeah.. So I took it, I just.. closed my eyes
[S] And I went for it, and I.. wow.. it's.. I can't due describe how bad that was..
[S] You know.. the.. from the flavor to the texture.. this consistency, you know.. a bit  I really hated it and I couldn't finish it
[S] But he finished it, I don't know how he did it, I.. you know.. could see his face like.. oh my.. crying and all this kinda of weird expressions
[S] But he finished it and then he told me, actually it's not that bad
[S]
[L]
[S] So yeah, I don't think I would have this thing again but it was.. you know, a funny memory from.. from this trip
[S]
[L] Uh-huh