[S] hey how's it going?
[S] uh.. well how are you?
[S] uh.. fine fine how was your weekend?
[S] yeah was perfect
[L]
[S] ok good good
[S] ok so today I'm gonna tell you two stories about me, yeah.. one story about my childhood and one story about uh.. growing up to me essentially
[S] so the first story is about.. before we start, would you say that you're an introvert?
[L] uh-huh
[S] so you are an introvert
[L] yeah
[S] yeah.. I am definitely an introvert I.. when I was young I used to enjoy being by myself a lot you know just kind of staying on my own
[S] so you are an introvert
[S] play video games and.. but I wasn't.. I was a bit lonely but I still kind of enjoyed myself  and.. and that's I was like that for most of my
[S] childhood uh.. eventually.. when was.. at the age of eleven? I moved to Sweden kind of uh.. and when I moved to Sweden I still was a few introverted but I
[S] met this person.. kinda so I started school and like kinda of was it.. middle school essentially um.. (low?) middle school and then I
[S] met this one person I became very friends with she was a girl she was really outgoing kinda she was really funny she was very independent kinda which was very different from me 'cause I was like
[S]  essentially  'cause I moved to this new country I didn't know the language right? uh.. but she was very outgoing and cool and me and her became really good friends kinda of so we used to watch a lot of like
[S] saturday morning cartoons together and we used to like play a lot of video games together and go out and do something together kind of so it was.. so yeah she was my first real friend in Sweden which is pretty
[S] fun kinda.. it was pretty nice um.. one thing that we actually.. I remember very vividly is that we kind of do you know one of these lumbered..  processing mills like these lumbered processing mills
[S] where they make store of the planks and stuff to make furniture kind of we used to live pretty close to one of these so me and her would sneak in and kind of steal planks from this place
[L]
[S] um..  and what we'd do with this planks is kind of we'd try to build em into a (go?) kart.. (go?) kart essentially  um.. so we'd build.. we'd hammer all the pieces we'd get some nails put a hammer and gather all the
[S] pieces together and overtime we'd build up this go kart we would put on and extra seat kind of we would have like a trunk that we put on and we had like a
[S] (spoils?) to make it go faster or something I don't know what we were thinking just looked cool  like that uh.. but we build like this (go?) kart kinda what we would do with this is that right next to my house there was this kind of
[S] sloping asphalted hill kind of so we would take this (go?) kart and take it to the top of this hill and then essentially someone was supposed to be sitting and the other would just kind roll down the hill kind of
[S] uh.. and this was pretty fun we enjoyed  we enjoyed a lot we spent a lot of time doing that actually in the beginning uh.. as you can imagine this probably wasn't
[S] the best idea kind of um.. one day I got actually pretty hurt so what happened is when we were taking this thing up hill right so we put all the stuff on it and like it was.. it was
[S] pretty fun to just roll over down the hill what happened was we took it to the top of the hill I sat in it and then instead of just rolling down instead she pushed me down kind of
[S]  I started to like fly down this hill at the speed but the thing was bobbling a lot and so it kind of  flipped and then it shifted
[L]
[S] and then it started to flip over but the thing is I.. my legs were still stuck on the thing so I couldn't really get out so I was like landing on this side of my body and like going down the hill and I really just like scraped up
[S] the right side of my arm and it was really bloody kind of an awful land and all I heard was like pop cracking sounds which was really sad and so what she had to do is like.. and I was like sitting..
[S] laying there screaming a bloody mess kinda so she.. and she was also screaming so she had to run off and get my dad kind of he was working in the backyard yeah I know  it wasn't fun but
[L] oh..
[S] um.. it's kind of like I still enjoyed kind of the entire experience 'cause it's like it's the stupid stuff you do as kid that you remember for life right? uh..
[S] yeah so that was I had to learn from time that was one of the stupidest things I got up to um.. I was friends with this girl for a couple of months kind of but the thing was that after
[S] after a while I got to know that it was a shame really 'cause she told me that her family was moving to Asia kind of 'cause her family had gotten work a work kind of so her family had to move there
[L] I see
[S] uh.. and this was pretty not great for me kinda 'cause I was still a very lonely person  moved so when she did tell me I got
[S] pretty depressed I mean we gave each other our phone numbers kind of so we could like try to keep in touch but that didn't really work kind like we tried to call
[L] yeah..
[S] each other I tried to call her when she   it just didn't work like apparently cellphone or had to call sim card  notebook in China who knows
[S] right so yeah uh.. I was ashamed so I didn't hear from her for quite a long time actually eventually she did get in touch with me in kind of this one in one of these uncomfortable like
[S] Facebook messages you get five years later kind of it was five years  I received when she got in touch with me again and I was pretty excited to hear from her 'cause she kind of disappeared from the face of the earth and now
[S] she was back uh.. so I started to talk with her about about the way she was kind and then I talked to her about the past and we talked for a while but I could realize that
[L]
[S] I talked quite a lot but she wasn't really into it she did obviously uh.. change quite a lot from having moved I guess that's  kinda happens when you're a kid and you move somewhere  you do change pretty quickly
[S] uh.. so unfortunately the.. our conversations became just kinda shorter and shorter and eventually she just kinda stopped responding to my texts (switches?)
[S] shame you know but this like what you.. what you gonna do about it so yeah um.. so that was the story one of my first friends when I moved to Sweden hm..
[L] hm..
[L] I see
[S] hm
[S] must be difficult like
[S] uh.. I mean it was a good.. nice to meet her but I guess like I changed a lot too as a person overtime so that's
[L] that's right yeah
[S] hm