[S] everything good?
[L] yeah
[S] ok, had a good week so far?
[L] yeah, was.. I think so
[S] yeah that's how I feel as well
[S] ok so I'm gonna tell you a bit about my childhood today kinds of stuff and two stories about my childhood
[S] um.. first off would say that you're an introvert ?
[L] sorry what?
[S] introvert.. kind of you're a bit shy or a bit uh.. kind of you'd like to keep yourself kind of thing you get tired from being around people
[L] that depends on the people that are around me sometimes I am
[S]   uh yeah but I was very introverted and like very reclusive as a kid kinda I enjoyed being on my own a lot and I kind of
[L]
[S] I don't know it was a bit lonely but I didn't mind kinda it was nice.. it was peaceful for me kind of a.. and that continued through most of my childhood
[S] so.. that thing changed when I eventually moved to Sweden which I did around the age of.. was it eleven? eleven.. twelve I think I moved to Sweden kind of
[S] and that  scary experience right? I was a bit lonely at first but I (did?) meet people  starting this new school so I (had?) to meet people there
[S] started a new class uh.. and then I met this one person I spent a lot of time (with?) this girl and she was really nice she was amazing she was really outgoing kinda
[S] she was very independent which I really admired 'cause I was just so shy and reclusive from where I was originally um.. and we spent a lot of time together we watched a lot of
[S] cartoons and we played a lot of video games together and yeah we had great fun and I really enjoyed spending time with her and we got to a lot of mischief and kind of weird
[S] stuff so there was actually this one thing that we build uh.. we had this like lumbered mill do you know where they make like planks a whole bunch of planks and they use this for furniture
[L] uh-huh
[S] where they store the planks we had this kind of thing close to us and me and her used to sneak in and kind of steal like small planks and (after?) the planks from there and what we'd do with these
[S] planks is that we'd kind of (hammering?) these planks to get it to the shape of like a (go?) kart essentially we'd put some wheels on it and her and me would keep like building up this kart overtime so we put in this
[S] seat we'd put in like a  work so we'd put in like small (spoils?) at the back of it trying to make it go faster or something I don't know we were kids we were not the smartest
[S] and what we'd do with this (go?) kart is her and me we would bring it to the top of a hill and we'd kid of sit in it and kind of roll down kind of this hill and it was like this paved uh.. road kinda
[S] paved road hill next to my house essentially right? and as you can imagine this probably wasn't.. wasn't the smartest of ideas right?
[S]  so rickety wooden thing going down of a hill at a certain speed with squishy humans in it is not a.. great  great idea um.. so I did actually get very
[L] yeah
[S] hurt doing this at some point in time like.. 'cause what happened is we rolled this thing to the top of the hill I sat in it and normally we would just let going down kind of a (path?) speed but what happened this time was she really
[S] like I was (in?) and then she pretty pushed it like really hard so then I started to go down with speed I'm like hanging on and the thing is bobbling what happened is the thing eventually curved and flipped over kinda
[S] and I was stuck in it still so it's like my top half was out and bottom was still stuck in the thing kinda so I couldn't get out so what happened was I kinda like landed on my side and I scraped
[S] down the side of my arm and it got very bloody really bad yeah  it it wasn't great it wasn't great let me tell you it was really painful and like
[L] hm.. uh..
[S] so she screamed and there was blood everywhere and she had to run off and get my dad because I was just a bloody mess on the ground kind of so like  uh.. yeah that took me a while to
[S] recover from it was not a great idea I think it's a good experience kinda, it's the kind of stuff that you remember like when you get older kinda, all the stupid things you do as kid
[S] would you say you did stupid stuff as a kid as well?
[L] I've done some but.. uh.. (not a one?) I think I recall but I'm sure there is a lot
[S]
[S] yeah yeah 'cause that's part of (us?) being.. it's.. being kids is about making mistakes and learning from them don't matter how stupid they'd be kinda yeah but I had fun really a lot of fun with this girl in my youth
[S] kind of a.. so but the thing as time went on I got to learn that she was eventually moving away so I'd known her for like couple of months now and she was my
[S] first real friend in Sweden kinda  spoke English to me it was amazing I didn't know any Swedish  time uh.. but I got to know she was moving away I was actually
[S] her family was moving to Asia kinda 'cause her dad had gotten a job there um.. so basically she told me that and I was very upset and
[S] like I was worried about being alone 'cause she was my only real friend it's like.. it wasn't.. it was difficult um..
[S] so we agreed to exchange each others phone numbers kind of 'cause this was in a time before Facebook, (Instagram?) and stuff like that...  which
[S] yeah so we exchange phone numbers and  but it didn't really work kind of for whatever reason we couldn't get in touch with each others nothing worked kind of so yeah was a bit
[S] unfortunate I lost contact with her for a couple of years and I was very sad in the beginning I got over it eventually but it wasn't great for me for a long time
[S] uh.. eventually she did come back to contact with me like I think it was five years later or something like Facebook suddenly like a message like uh.. how you doing you remember me
[S] I was like yeah it was like wow  she's back uh.. so we talked a bit kind of and we uh.. kind started to share.. to talk a bit about our past
[S] so we talked about the stuff we did uh.. and we talked quite a lot about nostalgic things but like as we talked like a realized she was getting less and less interested like she would have shorter and shorter responses
[S] kind of it'd take longer and longer to get a response like I was enthusiastic but she was obviously.. had  changed her thoughts since she moved uh.. so eventually as
[S] time went on we kind of lost contact which is sad like (how?) people grow up  and change
[L] yeah yeah..
[S] and uh.. yeah so overtime we just stopped talking and I haven't really heard of her since hm..
[S] it's a sad story at the end?
[L] yeah it's a bit sad  sorry
[L]
[L] As always  they always go.. something like that
[S] people change right?