[S] Hey, how are you?
[L] Good. And you?
[S] Good, good, good. Do you like to travel?
[L] Yeah, I love traveling
[S] Yeah? Do you like to backpack?
[L] Yeah backpack with a tent and stuff
[S] Yeah? It's amazing right? Such an amazing feeling, it's awesome. I remember once I was traveling over Columbia. You ever went there?
[L] Ah, no.
[S] Awesome place to be, fantastic food, fantastic people. And I was just walking around in the ah.. all the villages and taking the local bars and going around.
[S] It's awesome. And I was in this little village and was in the Amazon forest region in Columbia. Huge forest. You ever went to a tropical forest before?
[L] No
[S] Never? It's an experience
[L] A little in New Zealand but not in Columbia like never on this continent.
[S] Okay. It's an amazing feeling. Ah, the thing is they have the forest, they have some tracks around the forest that you could go and walk around and so.
[S] But it was the rainy season and then they say yeah, don't go there. It's dangerous.
[L] Hmm.
[S] And you know maybe it's raining then you got lost and you..we have to go out and search for you. Something like that. Ah.. but whatever I decided to go.
[S] And I packed some food, packed some water and just went to the..to the..to the track around the..the forest.
[S] And..I don't know, the experience of being inside such a forest is amazing.
[S] The colors, the illumination of the..it's completely dense right but there is this sunlights coming in and illuminating this..
[S] this trees, this plant, this leaves, the flowers.
[L] Hmm.
[S] The sounds. The, the, the sounds of the monkeys, faraway, of the birds, of the, you know, the smell, it's such a..
[S] I don't know it is overwhelming experience. Really, really heavy on you and I was just experiencing this really loving it, walking around.
[S] I think I walked for two three hours, just ah on the forest. Then it started to rain. And then came this tropical rain
[L] Oh..
S] Really, really like the..the sky is falling on your head. The raindrops was like this size
[L]
[S] Was really, really dense. Really, two seconds and I was completely soaked.
[S] So I was like I cannot stay like that I'll get sick. So I was looking..runaway..looking for shelter.
[S] Then I saw a trunk of a tree and I said yeah okay I would stay behind this trunk and protect myself of the rain.
[S] I mean usually they say that the rain lasts one-two hours everyday so
[L]
[S] Wait there for one-two hours and then I go out. Sitted there, waited a bit. Was really experiencing also the rain, it's really heavy.
[S] Really everything changed on the forest, everything is quiet. This very, very heavy ah rain sounds and smell.
[S] And suddenly I hear something moving around me and then I look up and then I saw that the tree was moving around. Like, yeah, what that's weird.
[L] Hmm.
[S] I'm that tired now? That's really strange. While I was wondering, ah behind the tree came a head of a huge anaconda.
[S] Was so, so, so big.
[L] Oh my God!
[S] Completely like, completely scream out loud..I
[L] Yeah
[S] throw myself on the ground, running away from the tree. Completely soaked, but screaming, screaming, screaming.
[S] For some luck, the snake I don't think it saw me, it paid no attention to me. But I was so scared.
[S] I run away in the rain, found the track, run away back to the village
[L]
[S] Lock myself. Lock the door. Lock the windows and was in the bed like shaking like that
[L] Enough nature
[S] Completely enough nature for me. I was completely scared. Completely, completely.
[S] And I never was afraid of snakes but since that moment I..every time I'm on a place with (food?) or so I'm always looking around and wow
[L]
[S] It was such a traumatizing experience. It was really, really something.