[S] um so today we're gonna talk a little bit about like I'm gonna tell you a little bit about my past and kind of my childhood and a bit like a special someone to me when I was a child uh..
[L] yeah
[L] hm
[S] um so today we're gonna talk a little bit about like I'm gonna tell you a little bit about my past and kind of my childhood and a bit like a special someone to me when I was a child uh..
[S] would you say that you're an introvert?
[L] hm
[L] hm.. sorry?
[S] an introvert like are you a bit shy or a bit like withdrawn?
[L] yeah I'm an introvert
[L]
[S]
[S] yeah because I was different I was that and I am still that and I.. specially when I was young like I didn't have that many
[L] uh-huh
[S] friends I was very withdrawn but still kind of happy you know it's.. typical weird
[S] yeah  yeah
[L] uh-huh yeah I can feel that
[S] so like yeah I was like that  for quite a long time the most of my youth I used to just stay on my own um that changed a bit when I moved
[S] to.. Sweden.. when let me think in Sweden I was at the age of eleven I lived in Sweden um
[L] uh-huh
[S] when we moved out I was still a bit like an introvert but then I met this one person in my class she was a girl very cute
[S] uh.. and I kind of she was my friend and I didn't know Swedish  so she really liked me under her wing kind and I really admired her kind of she was..
[L] uh-huh
[S] really great this is really outgoing very independent kind of maybe like would you say you're independent?
[L] yeah
[L] yeah, I'm independent
[S] really great this is really outgoing very independent kind of maybe like would you say you're independent?
[L]  of course
[L] yeah, I'm independent
[S]
[L]  of course
[S] yeah good uh and I really got along great with this girl we spent a lot of time together actually
[L] uh-huh
[S] yeah we use to.. like on weekends we used to like watch movies together we used to play video games we kinda of did all kinds of stuff
[S] actually one of the weirdest things that we did was we had like these lumbered yard where they process planks for furniture you know kind of like when they have these big like all these planks lying about
[L] uh-huh yeah
[L] uh-huh
[S] actually one of the weirdest things that we did was we had like these lumbered yard where they process planks for furniture you know kind of like when they have these big like all these planks lying about
[S] and me and her used to like go there and we used to get these planks and we started to build like this  kart kind of thing where we had.. would put all these planks into like
[L] uh-huh
[L] hm..
[S] and me and her used to like go there and we used to get these planks and we started to build like this  kart kind of thing where we had.. would put all these planks into like
[S] kart shape and the put some wheels on it uh.. and we spent a lot of time just kind of like upgrading this car putting in it a trunk putting in two seats
[L] uh-huh
[S] putting in (spoil?) there to kind make it grow faster or something I mean what we were thing?  um.. but what we would do with this kart? so we take it to the top of this like slope it was like a long asphalted slope that went down
[L]
[L] uh-huh
[S] putting in (spoil?) there to kind make it grow faster or something I mean what we were thing?  um.. but what we would do with this kart? so we take it to the top of this like slope it was like a long asphalted slope that went down
[S] um.. and.. well we just we would take it to the top oh this and we would roll it down does it sound like a bad idea yet?
[L] uh-huh
[L] yeah yeah
[S] yeah  it wasn't a great idea because actually um.. there was this one time when I got pretty badly hurt kind of uh..
[L]
[L] hm
[S] yeah  it wasn't a great idea because actually um.. there was this one time when I got pretty badly hurt kind of uh..
[S] so it was her and me we were taking it so we build this thing together it was kind of a group project um.. we took it to the top of this hill and then we would like let it roll down kind of own it's own
[L] uh-huh
[S] like it  eventually stopped at the bottom and.. but there was this one time where I got really badly hurt like we took this car to the top of the hill and  pushed it
[S] so it was her and me we were taking it so we build this thing together it was kind of a group project um.. we took it to the top of this hill and then we would like let it roll down kind of own it's own
[L] hm
[S] like it  eventually stopped at the bottom and.. but there was this one time where I got really badly hurt like we took this car to the top of the hill and  pushed it
[L] uh-huh
[L] hm..
[S] like it  eventually stopped at the bottom and.. but there was this one time where I got really badly hurt like we took this car to the top of the hill and  pushed it
[S] I (should?) really.. ok  and then we went on super fast but then like I kind of turned a bit in the kart and the kart flipped over like I flipped on the inside so it would flip on to it's side so then I would
[L]
[L] uh-huh
[S] I (should?) really.. ok  and then we went on super fast but then like I kind of turned a bit in the kart and the kart flipped over like I flipped on the inside so it would flip on to it's side so then I would
[L] yeah
[L] uh-huh
[S] I (should?) really.. ok  and then we went on super fast but then like I kind of turned a bit in the kart and the kart flipped over like I flipped on the inside so it would flip on to it's side so then I would
[S] flip over and what happened was kind of I.. I said it was like this long asphalted um.. like hill essentially right?
[L] uh-huh
[S] so it flipped over and then like what happened was since the kart struck me out of balance I was still (sat?) in the kart my legs were still in the kart so I flipped over and just like scraped my entire side all the way down the hill
[S] and like you can imagine that hurts right?  and like all the way down like and I was just like.. it was just this bloody mess and she was screaming kind of
[L] yeah yeah of course
[L] uh-huh
[S] and like you can imagine that hurts right?  and like all the way down like and I was just like.. it was just this bloody mess and she was screaming kind of
[S] and like I really felt like it hurt like I broke something kind of it was really bad  so she actually had to run and
[S] get my step dad we kinda.. he was like nearby at the time and the hill was actually right next to my house so she had to run to get my step dad so was like
[L] uh-huh
[L] yeah
[S] get my step dad we kinda.. he was like nearby at the time and the hill was actually right next to my house so she had to run to get my step dad so was like
[S] and it was just like this bloody mess and.. and it was pretty bad I'm sure you can imagine like so but yeah at the end of the day I thought it was like totally worth it
[S] stuff like that you remember right? do you have like similar (reasons?) other like exciting stuff?
[L] uh-huh
[L] yes.. uh-huh I have.. I have a similar experience
[S]  yeah.. but yeah me and her were great friends and we.. we did a lot of this stuff and she really helped me like she really took care of me it's a friend of mine who I built a kart with
[L] hm..
[S] eventually I did get to know that she would be moving away um.. it came very like suddenly for me I..
[L] uh-huh
[S] and she said that she was moving away 'cause her family.. her dad had gotten a nice position in Asia kind of um..
[S] and.. she like.. we said that we'd keep in touch kind of and we did try but she was moving to Asia and this was back in the time
[L] uh-huh
[S] before most of the social media stuff so we gave each other the phone numbers but I couldn't really.. uh.. it was difficult to me to keep in touch with her 'cause like a phone I couldn't get any answer kind of so..
[L] (help?)
[L] uh-huh
[S] before most of the social media stuff so we gave each other the phone numbers but I couldn't really.. uh.. it was difficult to me to keep in touch with her 'cause like a phone I couldn't get any answer kind of so..
[S] yeah.. and that she was a big pain 'cause that was like one of my first friends that a really made kind of like 'cause I was very introvert even like where I lived before kind of so it was a big pain to lose a friend
[L] uh-huh
[S] like that and um.. I did eventually manage to get back in contact with her like
[S] I think it was about like a couple of years after she had moved I got in touch with her again and we started to talk about like
[L] uh-huh
[S] I think it was kinda maybe about was it.. that was actually quite a long time it was like ten years or something like  I got in contact with her again like with the  of Facebook and stuff
[L] uh-huh yeah
[L] uh-huh
[S] I think it was kinda maybe about was it.. that was actually quite a long time it was like ten years or something like  I got in contact with her again like with the  of Facebook and stuff
[S] but then like I got in contact with her again and um.. she changed a lot from what I remembered like she couldn't contact with me so I was really hoping like
[L] uh-huh
[S] we could talk about the past and I talked about all these nostalgic things but I think she changed a lot do you know when you like that don't see people for a long time and like they change quite a lot and..
[L] yeah.. uh-huh
[S] and I thought that we could have like a bond or this stuff that we did all these stupid things that I mentioned this kart thing right? and but she didn't seem
[L] yeah
[S] that interested in it that was mostly me pushing the conversation kind of and.. and yeah so.. eventually we.. I kept trying to push the
[L] uh-huh
[S] conversation but she answered less and less every time kinda so eventually we just talking kind of and now it's been a while since I heard from her last so..
[S] I think it was about four years maybe so I haven't been in touch with her since then
[L] uh-huh
[L] hm..
[S] I think it was about four years maybe so I haven't been in touch with her since then
[L] it's quite bad..
[S] yeah it's unfortunate
[L] uh-huh
[L] yeah
[S] yeah it's unfortunate