[S] How're you doing?
[L] Fine, great thanks!
[S] How was your weekend?
[L] Yeah, it was nice, relaxing. Just recovering little bit from the PhD
[S] Great, I watched this, um, movie. You know Karate Kid?
[L] Yeah, I know, I know I watched it
[S] Famous movie about Daniel-San and Sensei. It's a nice movie. That reminded me, when I was practicing martial arts
[L] Uh-huh
[S] when I was a child and then a teenager
[S] Started around when I was..I don't know, around five? Just my parents took me there just to play with my friends and have some fun with them
[L] Uh-huh
[S] So it not a lot about techniques or self-defense, we were just about having fun altogether. It was cool.
[S] So I started to practice um more often. Like from twice a week, to up to three or four times a week
[L] Karate?
[S] Yeah
[L] Okay
[S] And then also a bit of Kung-Fu. Um..then I just started..I mean I was going there with my friends.
[S] I started to take it more seriously. Like I was really, you know, into it
[L] Engaging?
[S] I was really like practicing. Um, you know when you get better and then you start to practice, more focus and so on
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Um, then after several years of practice I would say, you know around six or seven years, I had the chance to take part at this national tournament
[S] Of martial arts. Um..I was, yeah, I was really excited. I was not really confident that I could somehow you know, go
[L] What's your level that time? Like, black..
[S] I was yeah..I was almost black belt
[L] Black belt
[S] So, but these tournaments are according to different levels. So..
[L] Yeah
[S] Basically, you can also have um, fights with other..with people with different color and different levels and then my master thought..
[L]
[S] It's kind of you know hard. So master..my master thought actually it would be a good idea to take part of it and then we went to this place
[S] there were around hundred participants from all over the place..I mean all over the country
[L]
[S] Really good ones. I mean I was, you know, thinking about it all the time, like, oh man, I don't know if I'm good enough for these guys
[L] Like, was your first time, right?
[S] Yeah, it was my first time. Like my first martial arts competition, my first competition in general
[L] Uh-huh
[S] So, I never..I never won anything. So, I was like, oh my God, it's gonna be so humiliating. But, no, I was hoping
[L]
[S] for, you know, for winning and my family was there, supporting me. Also, my master was there just asking me, you know, to empty my mind
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Just get focussed. So, empty your mind. Um, so then I had this..
[L] So you had these great supporters screaming for you
[S] Yeah, kind of. You know, my parents and my friends were there. So they were, cheering me up and saying, you know, it's like, you can make it. Yeah, you know the usual things you hear in movies. it's all fake
[L]
[S] But yeah, it came the time for my first fight. Um, and there was this huge, super huge guy, you know with this killer look in his eyes
[S] You can see, he just wanted to hurt me.
[L]
[L] With black clothes, while you are wearing..white one
[S] Yeah, like in the movies. You know where he had this black kimono like, you know, all ready for..Oh my God, so my legs were shaking
[S] I was super nervous. I couldn't really imagine even ah, hurting this guy. I was just so nervous
[S] I was just..I just wanted to protect myself from this huge..I mean he had this huge hands
[L]
[S] But anyway, actually I look at my master, he look at me and I just like remember everything you trained..you know this
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Movie (sentences?) just to
[L] Were you washing the car like this?
S] Yeah. And, yeah then we started. As soon as we started, I felt a bit better. You can see all the adrenaline, you know running through your body.
[S] So, the thing is, this guy was really, was really huge, but he was not so quick, so actually I won the first match. It was really cool.
[S] Um and then I got much more confident. I was like, you know, if I can beat this guy, probably I can do this with other people
[L] Beat everyone?
[S] Well, yeah, not everyone, but I was..oh yeah. So that was two days of fights.
[S] Um, I think I had like ten different fights, well, um, five, five fights each day.
[L] Each day
[S] It was really demanding, cause the thing is, you know, usually um, pain comes afterwards. At the beginning, you're all, you know..
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Full of energy
[L] Yeah, yeah
[S] But then when you just go there and you just sit down and then you start to feel the pain everywhere. Maybe they hit one part of your leg and then it's swollen and it was ah
[S] I was, you know, with some ice and so on. But, yeah, but actually, I made it to the final
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Which was great. I couldn't even..couldn't believe it. Actually it was like, oh my God, I'm going to the final. Also, my master was like, yeah, you made it. I think, he didn't think, I could make it
[L]
[S] But, yeah, we got to the final. Um, at that point I was super tired like also psychologically tired you know with this thing of getting ready for a fight
[L] Also motivated, right? You got to the final, you beat a lot of people.
[S] Yeah, it was a mixed, half motivation, of course when I have to face this last guy, I was super motivated
[S] But you know, you can also feel like my body was not reacting like it was supposed to. I was also a bit nervous, cause there were a lot of expectations, you know like.
[S] It's like in movies, oh the finals, so the guy winning is the winner, big guy and the other guy is just loser, like
[L] Uh-huh
[S] So I was kind of, you know, thinking about the movie. But, then again, just, I empty my mind, just stop thinking about anything. So okay, you're mine.
[S] This guy was even bigger, bigger than the first one I told you. He was really like two meters tall. Such a huge guy.
[S] Ah, he had, you know, he had a scar here, really intimidating
[L]
[S] From movies man.
[S] But anyways like, okay, I go for it. Um, we start a fight. Again, in the beginning he was really aggressive.
[S] so I most mostly protecting myself. But then, yeah as this thing like big guys are not so quick, so I was just like you know waiting for the right moment to hit him and I won
[L] Woah
[S] It was great. I mean, it was a great feeling, like I remember just this guy just fell down to the ground and I was still thinking like is he gonna stand up?
[L]
[S] You know, even angrier than before. But no actually..
[L] You  his face just to confirm
[S] Yeah, no, you can't do that, otherwise they disqualify you. No, but, you know I won and I was so happy. I was like so tired and so happy.
[S] Ah, so the first thing I did was just, you know, go there, celebrate with my family and you know, it was actually the first and actually the only one time that I won something
[L] Nice
[S] Yeah, so I was watching this movie this weekend, remembering those all memories
[L] Uh-huh. Cool, nice.