[S] Hi, how was your weekend?
[L] I'm very good, yeah, it was great
[S] Great
[S] Um, I went to Norway this weekend
[L] Norway?
[S] Ya, to visit a friend
[L] Ok
[S] He is Um.. Living in Tromsø, have you heard the city? Tromsø..
[L] No.. Tromsø..
[S] Up north in the country
[L] Ok
[S] He was doing his Erasmus there so..
[S]  and I was visiting him
[L] Oh, ok, that's nice
[L] Uh-huh
[S] So I went there for the weekend and Uh..
[S] Uh-huh
[S] Yeah, well, it's kinda of a small city, so there is not a lot to do..
[L] Yeah
[S] It's really cold in this period so you know..
[L] Ok
[L] Uh-huh
[S] And really expensive as well
[S] So for a decent meal and some.. you know beer..
[L] Ok
[S] You end up paying twenty five euros or so, it's not that good for students
[S] Really?
[L] What in the hell?
[S] You end up paying twenty five euros or so, it's not that good for students
[S] Yeah, you know, experience, my first time in a.. Scandinavian country
[L] Yeah
[S] So we just went around the city.. Um..
[S] Some pubs and so on.. Then he asked me if I've tried.. Have you heard this.. Um..
[S] This really smelly fish thing.. like.. This should be the smelliest food in the world
[L] Which one?
[S] Um.. I ain't remember the name in this.. well in any scandinavian language, it's like herring
[S] Which is.. you know.. fermented with salt, and it's supposed to be super smelly
[L] Ok
[L] Um.. don't
[S] So there is some reaction videos on youtube of.. you know.. of the people when they smell or when they eat that
[L] Ok
[S] And it's considered the smelliest food in the world
[S] Um.. and then my friend told me that  that thing that smells really bad it doesn't taste so bad
[L] Ok
[S] Which I was like.. Yeah.. I don't believe you so we made a bet that we should try it
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Um, so.. ok
[S] The thing is, I don't like fish in general, so..
[L] Ok
[S] You know, I really think it's like tuna, so I was like.. Ok
[S] So for me was a double challenge
[L] Yeah, of course..
[S] Ok, lets go, just do it, so we went to the supermarket..
[S] We got this can of, you know, this herring which I don't know the name and..
[L] Yeah
[S] They looked really like.. This thing is gonna taste so bad..
[L] Ok, haha..
[S] hm... Then we went back to our place, Um.. the thing is you're not supposed to eat this indoors..
[S] Because it's stinks so much that..
[L] Oh my god
[S] You're advised to open this when you're..
[L] In open air
[S] Yeah
[L] Ok
[S] So  we went to.. this park
[S] Behind this place and Uh..
[S]
[S] Well, you know was the time of the truth to see..
[S] He was like.. He was all the time, don't worry.. it doesn't taste so bad just smells but..
[L] Ok
[S] Once you get used to smell it's not so bad
[S] Ok, so I, just, you know, opened the can and as soon as I opened..
[S] You know..  I just could feel this way off..
[L] Oh my god
[S] Disgusting fish smell into my fac,e almost hitting my face Uh..
[L]
[L] Ok
[S] Disgusting fish smell into my fac,e almost hitting my face Uh..
[S] So I was like, oh my god, I hate this..
[L] Uh-huh
[S]
[S] So I was like, oh my god, I hate this..
[L] Uh-huh
[S]
[S] He was like.. no this smell is not that bad
[L] Ok
[S] It's gonna taste good, it's gonna taste good.. ok..
[S]
[S] So yeah.. so I.. you know, just opened and there is kinda of slices of this raw fish so.. I just..
[S] Took one slice of this..
[S]
[S] You know, was.. that would.. some oil and (wine?) you know.. this kinda of jello that ah.. terrible..
[L] Ah..
[L] Yeah
[S] You know, was.. that would.. some oil and (wine?) you know.. this kinda of jello that ah.. terrible..
[L] Uh-huh
[S] So a terrible also the (hat pick?) experience was so bad..
[L] Ok
[L] Uh-huh
[S] So a terrible also the (hat pick?) experience was so bad..
[L] Yeah, Ok..
[S] Disgusting, so..
[L] Uh-huh
[S]
[S] But you know.. the bet was on.. I hate losing bets..
[L] Hmm
[L] Yeah
[S] So, just went for it
[L] So you.. went for it
[S] Um, I tried to get a bite, but I couldn't, like..
[S] As soon I approached this slice of fish tuna
[L] Yeah
[S] I was like, can I even break?
[S]
[L] Uh-huh
[S] Um, then I looked back at my friend and he was, you know, trying to bite it..
[S] But he was I little bit crying, I could see tears from his eyes like..
[L]
[L] (Shit?)
[S] But he was I little bit crying, I could see tears from his eyes like..
[S] Oh, it's not that bad..
[L] (Shit?)
[L] Ok
[S] Oh, it's not that bad..
[S] I was like, oh my god, it's gonna taste so bad, he was lying to me, this is terrible, but you know, I was like, ok..
[S]
[L] Yeah
[S] Doesn't matter.. and.. well.. the thing is he then..
[S] He gave it a bite, and really you could see it, his face was so much like..
[S] Who was kinda in pain
[S]
[L] Oh my god  Uh..
[S] So I decided to do the only thing that I could do just take that as a medicine so you know I just..
[S]  in my mouth
[L] Oh
[L] Oh shit
[S] But as soon as I could really taste that.. I just..
[S] Threw the whole thing to the ground, was just to much.. I was like..
[L] Oh my god
[S] Was a (mix?)
[L] So the taste was not good at all..
[S] Was terrible
[L] Ok
[S] Was just  since I don't like fish I can't guess if the taste was even worst than the smell was..
[L] Yeah, of course
[S] Everything was bad, the smell, the texture, the taste, was terrible..
[S] And he was like, yeah, it's not that bad, he could just.. had a bite.. actually
[L]
[L] Yeah
[S] And then he stopped,  but seems he actually ate that piece.. And I didn't..
[L] Yes, he won
[S] Which, you know, drove me up, this.. Uh..
[S] Time that I went to Beijing to have this smelly tofu thing..
[L] Oh..
[S] Which was something.. not so bad like this.. smelly tofu in Beijing but..
[S]  almost there.. Yeah, so basically Um..
[S] My holiday in Norway was at all great
[L] Um.. uh-huh
[S] This is the kinda of thing that I will not forget so easily
[L] Yeah