[S] how's it going ?
[L] good
[S] good? everything.. had a good week so far?
[L] yeah.. are we supposed to tell a story?
[S] I'm gonna tell a story you don't need to (talk?)
[L] ok
[S]  so I'm.. as you said basically what we're gonna do today is I'm going to tell you two stories about me  from my childhood uh.. first story is going to be a bit
[S] about when I was younger would you say that you're an introvert?
[L] hm.. yeah sort of
[S] yeah
[S] you kinda have to be   isn't that right?  yeah but I was also  very young believe it or not uh..
[L] hm.. yeah sort of
[L]
[S] you kinda have to be   isn't that right?  yeah but I was also  very young believe it or not uh..
[S] (still?) in a very young age I just stayed by myself played video games kind of thing um.. and yeah I didn't hate it I was a bit lonely but I enjoyed just being by myself
[S] enjoyed my own company and this continued for quite a long time eventually.. and it continued also when I moved I moved to Sweden when I was about.. what was I?
[S] eleven? twelve? so I moved to Sweden uh.. I mean yeah I still was little bit of an introvert (below?) I didn't go to meet.. start in my new class and meet new friend kind of thing
[S] and there was this one girl I became very good friends with I thought  she was amazing she was very outgoing kinda she was a great person she was very friendly and she also spoke
[S] English  I couldn't really say anything in Swedish yet right so I kinda we spent a lot of time together her and me watched cartoons.. played some video games I brought with me kinds of stuff
[S] uh.. that was very like there was great fun I enjoyed the company quite a lot we always talk about  actually um..
[S] lived very close to a kind of lumbered processing (plant?) it's like kind of where they make planks for making furniture stuff like that and she and..
[L] hum
[S] me used to sneak in essentially and like steal some planks what we would do with those planks is we try to build like this kind (go?) kart so like we cut some nails kind of tried to nail it together
[S] put some wheels on it kind of kart we disassembled uh.. tried to put.. and we kind of build.. build up everything we'd add extra seats we'd add like
[S] a trunk kind of thing It (didn't?) work very well we tried to add (spoil?) so that it'd go a little bit faster this kind of wooden wreck we were trying to ride and uh..
[S] and what we would do with this thing is that we would take it to like the top of a hill essentially.. so we took it to the top of a hill and then we would kind of roll it down  this hill and was right next to it it was this kind of asphalted like hill right
[S] right next to my house kind of thing and so we would do this a couple of times doesn't sound very safe does it?  kids (get up?) to stupid things I'm telling you  yeah so yeah
[L[ hm
[S] this time actually like what happened like we played with this thing quite a lot but eventually one day what happened was we walked to the top of this hill and then normally we just kind of let it roll down
[S] but then  time I was sitting in it and she was (right?) behind me she gave me a big push kind of down the hill to make it go faster and this didn't go too well I was kind of holding on for dear life and then kind of I swung it a bit
[L] hm
[S] too far just holding on just with my body weight and then it kind of flipped over and I was still stuck in this thing kind of so like the thing flipped over and I was like stuck in it and then like
[S] so what happens is I landed  on my side right and I scraped my side all the way the like.. before a couple of like feet essentially down this hill kind of and I was just
[L] hm
[S] a big bloody mess during this time it was pretty bad and it got so.. it was.. there was all the blood she was screaming she had to run and get my dad kinda because I was just
[S] lying there like screaming and like crying it was not great yeah it wasn't nice um.. yeah but that was great fun kind of stuff like that you remember the stupid
[S] things you do as kid right? um.. yeah and I had great fun with her kinda she was my first real friend kind of when I got to Sweden which is
[L] yeah
[S] cool to be friends with a cute girl  uh.. yeah so that continued for a while me and her had a lot of fun but eventually I found out
[S] that she would be moving her family or her dad more specifically had gotten a job in Asia kind of and that she had obviously move there for work
[S] kind of because you go where you.. you go where you get paid and so we decided to try to keep in touch kinda we  exchange numbers and stuff but that didn't really work out
[L] yeah
[S] too well 'cause we're kids we're stupid this was a (trip?) before Facebook like way back when the age when we were using messenger and stuff (and that?)
[S]  doesn't always work right when you have to move kind of that far away so eventually we lost touch and like I became really sad I was really lonely again kinda I really reverted
[S] back um.. which is unfortunate.. for me at least and I got over it eventually with quite a long time (perhaps?) but..
[S] but she did get in touch later on kinda of I think it was about when was it five years later I think when she got back in touch with me  she reached out and I was kind of
[S] wow she still exists I was amazed like hm she's back again um.. so we started to chat a bit about stuff we did when we were kids and which in fact
[S] I had to remind her about some of things we did she was into it at first but as we talked more and more she got more distant over time essentially and eventually
[S] I realized that she just really wasn't interested kind of anymore she  and she changed or whatever but she's different than what I remember her being essentially and..
[S] yeah eventually we just stopped talking and I haven't really talked to her (those days?) kind of so  life huh?
[L] sucks
[S] yeah..
[L] hm