[S] Before we were so rudely interrupted er.. right [L] Yeah
[S] So I told you about my friend who moved away essentially um.. [L] Uh-huh
[S] Honestly that left quite a big void in my life kind of, I was a bit lost for a while [L] Uh-huh
[S] So I started to look for kind of a way of filling the gap in some sense
[S] Kinda feeling that.. kind of acting out so to speak like  [L] Okay
[S] Um.. I started to get really interested in music, and kind of becoming a musician
[S] I thought it would be a really, well I need to just vent kind of, some emotions I had piled up [L] Yeah
[L] Yeah that role of artist are quite emotional [S] Hmm
[S] Yeah  good fuel, or so I hear ah.. [L]
[S] So I started to nag my parents a lot, for like I wanna have a guitar
[S]  nag about this [L] Okay
[S] They treated it more as a kind of passing phase
[S] Kind of that they hoped would go over so  [L] Okay
[S] Er it was.. not that seriously no [L] They didn't take you seriously
[S] They thought it was just something I would get over in due time um.. [L] Uh-huh.. okay, uh-huh
[S] And that went on for a while, the closest I could get to kind of convincing them of anything
[S] Is that once I was going to transfer from middle school to high school
[S] I convinced them to let me go to a more like musically oriented high school
[S] As long as the high school had like proper subjects like maths and chemistry  [L] Okay.. ah, okay
[S] So not just music um.. [L] Yeah
[S] So they agreed to do that
[S] And the school was very nice actually ah.. [L] Okay, that's nice.. uh-huh
[S] I really.. like the classes were very.. I learned a lot there [L] Wow
[S] The people very nice, the campus was very nice, the food was better than here  [L]
[L] That's amazing [S] Um.. but yeah
[S] And that, er I had a really great time there, I
[S] Except it lasted for a while at least, there was one thing that I had, I really had a problem with [L] Uh-huh.. uh-huh
[S] And that was there's this one mandatory course we had to take, which was classical music theory [L] Okay
[S] And the big issue with that course was that there was this teacher
[S] And I'm pretty sure that she was some kind of demon in the shape of a human being kind of  [L]
[S] Because she was really just an awful person kind of  [L] Shit
[L] Oh my god [S] She would like er
[S] She would yell at students and drag students around by the ear kind of [L] Oh shit
[L] What the hell [S] If they were misbehaving.. yeah she was not stable
[L] Okay.. wow [S]  ah..
[S] So being the, being in class with this woman was terrifying
[S] And it really like scared me kind of to have to go to her course
[S] Cause everything else was fine, but this is [L] This teacher was a problem
[S] This teacher was a major problem essentially [L] Okay.. uh-huh
[S] I did actually make friends off of those, strangely enough
[S] Cause like, there were these other four guys in the class, who went to the same class weirdly [L] Uh-huh
[S] And we actually bond over hating this teacher  like after the classes [L] Okay  yeah
[S] Difficult and angry all the time and yeah.. [L]  uh-huh.. okay
[S] Yeah so, it went okay like
[S] Cause she made my life really miserable with the classes but the rest of the school stuff was kind of okay [L] Uh-huh
[S] She did have other courses but those were taken the two later years kind of [L] Okay, that's nice.. okay
[S] Er.. everything was kind of fine for the first year kind of [L] Uh-huh.. hmm
[S] Eventually we got to this point where we had to give this big presentation in classical music theory in front of the entire class [L] Okay
[S] I was still fairly shy and fragile at that point in time
[S] So it was difficult, so this was a scary enough prospect, of just presenting in front of the entire class for me [L] Okay
[S] It was a bit spooky [L] How many students were there?
[S] Ah there were about.. 20 something I think so [L] Okay, uh-huh
[S] Ah it was till a sizable crowd for someone so young tho [L] Okay
[S] To present in front of, you know like talking in front of 8 people is a bit errifying like  [L] Okay.. yeah.. yeah, yeah, uh-huh
[S] Ah.. so partially I was scared of presenting in front of the class
[S] But also I had to present for this teacher who I'm fairly sure was very unhinged kind of [L] Ah yes, it's awful
[S] Not a happy person essentially [L] Yeah  okay
[S] So it took me kind of, I prepared a lot for this kind of [L] Uh-huh
[S] I was very nervous, I prepared a lot, I prepared slides [L] Uh-huh
[S] I really rehearsed in front of a mirror kind of, to make sure it would be good um [L] Okay.. uh-huh
[S] Eventually the day came, I gave the presentation, I was fairly happy with it [L] Uh-huh
[S] Like people clapped and the they laughed in between the presentation, that was nice [L] Ah that's nice
[S] Ah but then the teacher started to give feedback and she really like ripped into my what's it called um..
[S] Presentation. So she really said like no this is wrong, this is awful, why you do this kind of [L] Okay
[S]  and why did you say, should've spoken louder kind of
[L] Okay.. uh-huh [S] And really just like mean spirited uh feedback
[S] Not really constructive at all [L] Okay
[S] I had a very tough time handling this kind of ah..
[S] I had a very fragile self esteem at that point in time so I was  [L] Okay
[S] Difficult for me to parse the information, I suppose
[S] So it's like difficult for me to kind of absorb that [L] Yeah, of course, uh-huh
[S] So essentially.. I did kind of just go home to my parents in tears
[S] And I like to tell them like this isn't gonna work, I can't deal with this
[S] Ah we had to go and talk with the school
[S] But they said like, no we can't really get rid of her kind of
[S] She's on a number of boards, like she's essentially there to stay is what they kind of said [L] Oh my god
[L] So you couldn't do anything about it either [S] No she was a, she was a permanent fixture unfortunately
[S] So there was scarcely more we could do, but she also held a bunch of other courses essentially, which was a problem [L] Ah shit, uh-huh
[S] Uh so we discussed with them and we eventually came to a solution [L] Uh-huh
[S] That we could transfer me to kind of, there's a high school which shared a number of courses with this
[S] Uh.. music oriented school, and we [L] Okay
[S] Took to that we could transfer in to me into this normal school program essentially [L] Okay
[S] And so continue my education, so I could avoid these mandatory music courses that were required from and held by this teacher [L] Uh-huh.. ah okay
[S] Um so.. [L] Yeah but that means you losing studying music
[S] Yeah, it was not great, but she made my life singularly miserable
[S] I kind of thought, what's it called, I can get back into it later [L] Okay
[S] My parents thought yeah he's going to study IT stuff, I was like that's fine as well right?  [L] Yes
[S] Um so that's kind of, kind of what happened to me in essence [L] Okay
[S] So I transferred and then finished a normal like more traditional thing, I did kind of put [L] More traditional school and not
[S] Music enthusiasm on ice for quite a long time [L] Okay hmm
[S] Ah when I got to college on the other hand, but it in IT, and cause it's kind of up here
[S] I did actually meet one of the guys who I met there in the corridors of the university ah [L] Okay
[S] And we talked a bit kind of and he said that he still like plays in a band with those other four guys
[S] They still hated the teacher after having been there for he two years they had to to finish off with that teacher [L] Cool
[S] Ah so we talked a bit and he said ah we're playing in this band
[S] He actually said hey you should come and play with us, it's like what me? Really?  [L]
[S] Like I was surprised, like what you remember that I can do anything, he's like yeah you're pretty good vocalist, I remember [L] Okay
[S] So I was like, ah cool, yeah sure  [L] Okay, uh-huh
[S] I can try it, try out, so we played a bit during weekends now and then, it was
[S] Really it was really fun, and eventually we actually organized a bit of a concert for some friends and some other people [L] Ah that's really nice.. uh wow
[S] Yeah it went, it was really fun and I really felt like
[S] Liberated to kind of do it, it really like felt empowering in some sense and it really felt nice so um [L] Yeah, of course
[S] To really.. yeah connect to old friends, and to do something that [L] Connect to old friends
[L] You really liked [L] I kind of had, yeah, and I had kind of a dead passion
[S] To revive a dead passion was a really great experience, so it was [L] Yeah
[S] Great.. yeah [L] That is true, uh-huh