[S] Hey [L] Hi
[S] How you doing? [L] I'm doing good
[S] Um I'm telling you, I'll tell you what this real experience that I had
[S] Do you like traveling by air? [L] Yeah..
[S] Aren't you scared of it? [L] Little bit
[S] I'm terrified of traveling by air and and [L]  okay
[S] I normally I avoid taking flights if I can [L] Okay
[S] Um but a couple of weeks ago we were traveling to Zurich
[S] And um I didn't plan it in advance [L] Uh-huh
[S] And the plane takes way too much time to go there
[S] So I found this really cheap flight on the Zoom last minute deals website [L] Uh-huh, yeah yeah
[S] And took this flight um it was really cheap [L] Uh-huh
[S] To and fro was really less than 100 euros
[L] Uh-huh [S] And I took that flight um..
[S] I didn't realize it was in the evening, so it was fine for me, I would reach then and go in to the hotel directly but
[S] It was like the last flight of the day from here right? [L] Okay
[S] So 9:30, 10pm was the flight from here [L] Okay
[S] Um so I reach the airport, I reach the airport a couple of hours ago, as I normally do [L] Uh-huh, yeah
[S] It was a bit rainy evening, like normally it is [L] Uh-huh, okay
[S] But it was really windy at that night [L] Okay
[S] So I reach the airport and I see this huge cue of people for check in
[S] Apparently all the flights before my flight were delayed because of the weather [L] Okay, ah..
[S] So there was a huge, huge cue for check in, the security was completely packed [L] Uh-huh
[S] Like the whole airport was completely like stuffed with people at that point in time [L] Okay
[S] People with flight canceled, delayed, everything happening that night [L] Oh shit, okay
[S] So even with two hours I just could barely manage to reach the boarding gate in time
[S] They were closing the gate when I entered [L] Hmm, okay
[S] They let me in but they were not very happy about it [L] Yeah
[S] I told them how the check in was really long, and the security was just taking too much time [L] Uh-huh, uh-huh
[S] And I could just barely manage to get in [L] Okay, uh-huh
[S] But they allowed me to board the flight, um.. [L] Okay
[S] You know some of the flights they don't have the bridge to the flight
[S] So you have to go down and take the bus, and the bus goes to the flight [L] Yeah, yeah, yeah, then take the stairs
[S] I hate taking that bus, it feels like you are sheep [L] Uh-huh, okay
[S] And you're being, as a herd of sheep, you're put into this bus [L]
[S] And this bus is gonna take you to the farm and let you go there [L] Yeah  okay
[S] But feel like that for me [L] Yeah, okay
[S] Anyway we took, I took the bus, and then um
[S] As I reach the plane, I see that this is one of those small, really small propel propeller plane plane [L] Ah, okay
[S] A 60, 70 seater or something [L] Uh-huh, yeah
[S] And I really hate those planes, there's something with the [L] A lot of turbulence
[S] A lot of turbulence exactly, and the sound of those blades are basically [L] Yeah, uh-huh
[S] Too scary for me, feels like it's gonna fall at any time the plane right [L] Okay  okay
[S] It's just so scary for me, uh anyway [L] Uh-huh
[S] At that time it was too late for me to go anywhere, so I had to take the flight, I said okay fine it's one hour [L] Yeah
[L] Yeah, uh-huh [S] Whatever, I'll take the flight
[S] Um so they were rushing us in to board because I think they were getting late or something [L] Yeah
[S] They just rushed us in, the cruel also not very politely, a bit rude [L] Okay
[S] And they sort of literally followed us in to go and sit down like [L] That's weird
[S] Because we wanna fly just go quickly and sit down, yeah it was just [L] That's weird, okay
[S] Just really awkward and really really weird what was happening at that point right [L] Yeah, yeah, uh-huh
[S] Anyhow, we sit down [L] Hmm
[S] And then they announce that well the traffic control has told us that we can't fly [L] What?
[S] Because the weather is too bad so we have to wait
[S] They don't know how long, but we have to wait till the time we're cleared off for take off [L] Okay, okay
[S] And that I was thinking why the hell were you forcing us.. exactly, right? [L] Pushing us to get into
[S] If you don't, if you don't, you're not flying there, we're just sitting there for some time [L]  makes..
[L] Yeah, like.. yeah [S] Why were you so rude?
[S] They obviously didn't have any answer to that [L] Yeah, miscommunication probably
[S] Yeah.. but they didn't have to be rude to us right? [L] Lack of management.. yeah that's true
[S] That was just.. awkward [L] Uh-huh.. uh-huh
[S] Turns out we were there for one hour in the tarmac waiting for clearance to take off
[L] Oh my god [S] One hour we were just sitting there doing nothing
[L] Oh my god, that's so annoying
[S] People were cranky, and they don't even switch on the air conditioning or something while you're sitting in [L]
[L] Shit.. oh my god [S] And it was really small, crampy place with 70 people sitting right next to each other
[S] And I'm claustrophobic and I'm really getting really panicky and fidgety with it [L] Okay.. uh-huh.. okay
[S] Um.. [L] Isn't it dangerous as well?
[S] I mean it's there, I mean they had very minimal so it was not much oxygen there but it was still fine [L] Uh-huh.. uh-huh
[S] And the boarding gate was still open, so it was okay but it was still not the perfect situation [L] Yeah, okay.. okay, uh-huh.. yeah, okay, uh-huh
[S] Anyhow, after that one hour, we  and we take off
[S] Take off was also shaky, that means the winds were too strong for the plane, the plane was really small [L] Uh-huh.. okay, uh-huh
[S] So it was just going up and down, and by the time we reached the cruising altitude [L] Uh-huh
[S] We think we can take off the seat belt, go to the lavatory or something, the restroom [L] Uh-huh.. uh-huh
[S] But they said you couldn't take off the seat belts because the plane was going from left to right [L] What the hell
[S] They didn't allow the lavatories to be used, so we didn't, nobody could go to the lavatory [L]  such a crazy experience
[S] It was like everything was going wrong in that experience, right? [L] Okay.. okay.. uh-huh
[S] And then it gets worse, suddenly the lights go off [L] Oh my god.. what?
[S] Apparently there was some turbulence, there was some fall, the light goes off
[S] And we're seeing this lightning outside, because it was raining [L] Oh my god
[S] Flashes of light coming in, like a picture from a horror movie
[S] A scene from a horror movie [L] Oh my good, do you start thinking it's gonna crash
[S] And and you can't move, you've been told not to get up [L] Shit.. uh-huh
[S] You can't go to the lavatory, the plane is just shaking terribly [L] Oh my god
[S] Um you know when sometimes turbulence happens, the plane goes up and then suddenly has a fall [L] Yeah, yeah, yeah
[S] And you feel like it's gonna fall out [L] Yeah, that's true, oh my god
[S] Normally it's like for one or two seconds, right? But this was like 30 seconds of just falling [L] Uh-huh
[S] It felt like the plane fell like 400 feet or something [L] Oh my god
[S] And I'm panicking at that point, right? This is way.. they're like... [L]
[S] Everything worse that I can imagine about this flight experience is getting, is coming true [L] Is going, oh my god, okay
[S] The worst, worst experience [L] Uh-huh
[S] And then the oxygen masks follow [L] Oh my god, shit
[S] You always think that well, this will never happen
[S] They tell you about it when you're boarding but this never happens right? [L] Yeah, but
[S] An that was the first time it actually happened to me [L] Uh-huh.. okay
[S] And I didn't know what to do with it, because I could not put it on er
[S] Because I was panicking, everything was shaking [L] Yeah, exactly
[S] The guy sitting next to me actually helped me put on the mask, so I could breathe again
[S] But then again, this plane was again falling and trying to climb up [L] Uh-huh.. oh my god, shit
[S] Falling, trying to climb up
[S] And I, I was thinking okay this is the last light of my life
[L] Oh my god, shit [S] And I'm gonna die
[S] This is gonna crash and everything is gonna burn to hell now [L] Oh my god
[S] Er this goes on for the next 20 minutes you know?
[S] The, the goes up, falls down, goes up, falls down [L] Oh my god, like, oh shit
[S] By the end of that 20 minutes they kind of stabilized, probably we moved out of the bad weather area [L] Uh-huh
[S] Closing down on where we had to go.. the destination
[S] I went, everybody was annoyed with the crew, so we were told we can take off the mask
[S] The light came back on again [L] Yeah.. okay
[S] They served us some water and everything, and everybody was shouting at the crew [L] Thank god.. uh-huh
[S] But what could they do right? The weather was that bad.. um.. [L] Yeah.. uh-huh
[S] Just, just a harrowing experience, really, really scary [L] Oh my god.. uh-huh
[S] Um then we started to descend for landing, even the landing was weird [L] Really?
[S] Cause we landed and we jumped twice on the runway before we actually landed [L] Oh my god
[S] Um.. I [L] You're lucky the plane didn't explode or something, but
[S] That could be the next thing, the next worse thing would happen, we don't even land, we just burst into flames [L]  yes.. yeah.. uh-huh
[S] I mean people were really annoyed at the pilot, but I think well what could he do? [L] Uh-huh
[S] The, the weather was that bad. Yeah, landing was his fault  [L] Yeah
[L] Yeah, come on, okay.. yeah [S] Other than, other than that he was probably not a very skilled pilot or something
[S] Just the plane is too light [L] That's a really scary experience
[S] I was so scared, I canceled my flight back, I took the train [L]
[S] Um I couldn't, probably is gonna be the same flight, and I wouldn't want to go through the same experience again [L] Yeah
[L] Yeah, of course, this is so bad [S] Yeah, and
[S] Yeah, it scared me for life now, I'm very scared of taking flights already [L] Uh-huh.. uh-huh..
[S] Now, now I'm even petrified of them now, taking it [L] Yeah.. yeah, I can understand
[S] I probably make sure, even if I have to fly, I don't take the night flights
[S] And I don't take these propeller planes, for sure [L] Yeah, exactly, smaller planes
[S] Yeah, but it was just a really, really scary experience and it's [L] Yeah
[S] I'm really still shivering from that experience [L]
[L] I'm so sorry, that's terrible