[S] Hey, how are you?
[L]  I'm fine, how about you? [S] Yeah? Good, good, good, good.
[S] I was remembering some stuff this weekend
[S] You.. how was your high school time? Was it good?
[L] Yeah, I  really good, yeah [S] Yeah, you like it?
[L] Yeah [S] Yeah, ah I've met lot of people and..
[S] I mean it's really half part, some people really like it, some people really, really hate it
[S] I didn't like much, it was really a hard time
[S] I was moving from cities and then I.. [L] Uh-huh
[S] Started on second year of high school in a new school
[S] And I think that makes everything worse, right? I mean
[S] I guess arriving at school, you don't know anyone, or anyone knows you [L] Hmm
[S] And you're kind of flung the kind of apart
[S] Disconnected from everything else, right?
[S] And on top of that I was a very bad student
[S] So I was, yeah.. I was never, I never liked to study
[S] The, the courses they had at high school was always boring [L] Yeah
[S] And I did everything just to, enough to pass [L] Pass
[S] Yeah, never liked to learn or something like that
[S] But this changed when a, a new teacher arrived in the school
[S] And it was a.. history teacher, right? He was a nice guy.. [L] Hmm
[S] He was very young.. uh different from the, from the teachers from the school
[S] They were, the other teachers, they were very old
[S] You know this very old very um..
[S] Aggressive type, this, yeah, authority type, you know?
[S] And that becomes also a very bad thing
[S] How to, a bad way to connect with them, and then to, to, to
[S] There was  personal (days?) of the subject, right?
[S] But yeah this guy arrived, and he was new, he was very young
[S] Uh he was very cool, very light
[S] And.. he kind of taught differently
[S] He had a better didactic than the other teachers at some point
[S] Um.. yeah and I start to pay a bit of attention on his lecture
[S] But not enough because I fail the first.. test
[S] And.. it was like, yeah, wow, that's not good.
[S] But then he came talk to me after the first test and..
[S] Yeah, he say yeah why you fail? Let's see what's happening
[S] You pay attention a lot on the lectures, you're there always, so
[S] And the we talked a lot, and, and he helped me a lot on, on, uh uh uh, yeah
[S] Learning how to get used to, to the lecture
[S] And to get used to study, you know? To, to pass, you know?
[S] And.. yeah, then came the second test
[S] The second evaluation, I fail again
[L] Uh.. [S] Yeah, again, and I was feeling bad
[S] Really feeling let down, really like, wow, yeah, that's not.. helpful
[S] And then he came talk to me again and then I felt even worse
[S] Because we've talked before, you know? And it was like wow, wow, that's bad
[S] And then I study, study, study, uh..
[S] And I was in a pressure, because it was the final exam
[S] And I should pass the final exam, otherwise I would fail the, the, the class
[S] Uh.. and I pressure myself to study a lot.. a lot, a lot, a lot, a lot
[S] But I panicked the night before the exam
[S] I was really like wow I cannot fail this, I will feel bad
[S] Then everything would be going away. I mean, it's awful to fail, right?
[S] And.. then I decided to make some, some strips of paper
[S] And put the, the names and dates of the things happening
[S] And then put on my sleeve
[S] Really not proud of that, it was really bad to do it, you know?
[S] But yeah I was desperate, I was really panicking
[S] And I did the test, I used the, the, the cheats on the test and um..
[S] I felt so bad when I hand in the test
[S] I felt so disgusted with myself
[S] I mean wow, how can I, I break the trust of this guy that really trusted on me, yeah, I..
[S] I did something so bad to me, to myself
[S] I mean I cheated myself, not the exam, right?
[S] And.. in the end I pass the test, I pass the exam..
[S] Uh but.. I never did this anymore, I was really
[S] It was really a strong milestone in my life, really like, wow that was really bad
[S] Really, really, really strong uh.. really, really, really bad feeling
[L] Yeah, that must  really difficult situation  [S] Yeah