[S] Ok, so how are you doing today?
[L] Yeah.. I'm fine, thanks.
[S] Nice
[S] Um.. Do you like traveling?
[L[ Yeah .
[S] Did you travel recently somewhere?
[L] I've been
[S] Ok. Yeah.
[S] I like traveling a lot ah.. but I don't like traveling by flight that much. It is a bit scary for me.
[S] (all the?) experience.. but ah..
[S] Quite recently, actually, a couple of weeks back, I was traveling to Brussels.
[S] Normally I would take the train because It's not that far but I found this good deal on this website so I could take a flight really cheap.
[S] And what I didn't realize that was a evening flight. A evening flight is fine but It was like ten or something.
[S] And you know like er.. It was sort of the last flight of the day or something.
[S] So I went to the airport a couple of hours earlier than the boarding time, as I normally do.
[S] It was this stormy evening, (kind like?) raining and really dark.
[S] As I reached the airport I see this long queue for check in.
[S] Apparently most of the flights were delayed that day and this airport was full of people. It was really so crowded.
[L] Um.
[S] So took me a long for the check in to happen even though I reached like two hours before the time.
[S] Ah.. So I could barely manage to get to the boarding before they close the boarding, like ten minutes before they close the boarding.
[S] Um..
[S] So I went in. I  to board.
[S] You know normally some airport they don't have this bridge to the flight then you have to take the bus to the flight.
[S] It was that and I hate that actually.  just go to the bridge.
[S] But we took the bus and when we reached the plane I see that is not a big plane. It is this small seventy seat propeller plane. So
[S] This propeller plane.. I hate those planes. I fell really unsafe in those planes because, well this is propellers I like to (think?) the jets are a little more secure. I think I fell that way.
[S] So anyway we were kind of like.. the flight was getting late so we were forced to board as quickly as possible and sit down.
[S] Because they wanted to prepare (things?) and leave in time ah..
[S] And as It turns out when the time actually was there for the plane to start
[S] There was an announcement saying that the air traffic control has told us to not flight for now because there was flights before us we were late and
[S] It is stormy so It's better (wise?) we be doing not to fly at that particular time so we sat and just had to wait.
[S] Ya.. (They were literally?) forcing us to seat down now now  we had to wait for some time
[S] The staff was really rude at that time.
[S] Uh.. turns out we stayed for one hour at the tarmac waiting for the flight to take off because they just not move. And they don't even switched on the air conditioning while the flight was not started.
[S] Can't breath properly. It was really hot inside.
[S] Um.. I mean outside was fine so.. but It was really hot inside really really  and I get really claustrophobic and I do not like those places.
[S] It was a really small crowded plane and we hardly had space to move.
[S] Um.. after one hour they started to take off and um..
[S] It's not even the smoothest take off. It was like  a lot of storm so a lot of turbulence.
[S] As soon as we reached the cruising flight I would normally take my seat belt because I wanna to move out and I wanna go to the restroom or something.
[S] And they didn't turn off the seat belt off.. the seat belt signs. You had to keep your seat belts even .
[S] They didn't allow us to go to the lavatory because there was a lot of turbulence. You should not do that. And the plane after some time started to move from left to right. It was just so much turbulence.
[S] Uh.. um.. It was just the weirdest thing. I've never experienced this thing before. Probably the storm was too bad but It shouldn't be that bad.
[S] And that is why I don't like small planes because the wind just moves it around completely.
[S] Um.. Turns out after a fell minutes
[S] We felt.. I felt like the plane was having a free fall or something.
[S] You know sometimes the turbulence makes it falls one hundred feet or something and just keep it falling. And I felt so sick and the lights were turned off uh..
[S] completely and everybody was panicking. We thought that we were going to die we are going to crash or something because.. ah.. I mean..
[S] It was just weird. It was stormy outside and we could see the lightning and the flashes coming in.
[S] Because lights  really scary like a horror movie or something.
[S] Um.. and after some time It was completely falling for a few seconds and suddenly the oxygen masks came down.
[S] And that's when I thought this is the end of my life. Nothing is gonna work for now.
[S] The oxygen masks went down. And er.. I have never experienced this before. Never in my flight experience I had to wear the oxygen masks.
[S] And because of the fall I couldn't breath because I was felling so weird for me. Then (I was?) claustrophobic and with this falls down I felt really odd and I was struggling with the oxygen mask and I couldn't put it on.
[S] So the guy seating next to me helped me  then I could actually breath after that. It was like scary and harrowing I though I would die. Even before the flight crashes if it does, I would just die with a lack of oxygen.
[S] Somehow after a few minutes, a couple of minutes the flight kinds of stabilize and the falling felling stop for some time.
[S] Uh.. and it felt like the flight was again gain altitude er..
[S] And the lights came on again and the air-hostess says that we had this terrible turbulence and that's why it happen. She told us to keep the oxygen masks for some time before we reached stable altitude and the we could take it off uh..
[S] It was just weird. It was the most awful thing I've ever experienced.
[S] Probably (towards?) when we were reaching our destination the flight kind of stabilize and we were told to remove the oxygen masks and..
[S] We were allowed to raise and everybody was panicking and shaking. It was this compact small plane and such thing happened we couldn't move much um..
[S] It was really trouble something. Even the landing.. In the landing we bumped twice before we actually stabilize. I mean everything that could go wrong was going wrong on that fly and I was so scary of flights after that I canceled my flight back.
[S] I took the train even that it took me four times more time, but I couldn't deal with the whole thing again.
[S] And I'm pretty sure I'll never fly in this small planes again.
[S] I'll check before what plane it is, how many people does it have, what time.. I'll probably take a day plane I'll not gonna fly at night.
[S] Yeah. That one scared me for life with this small propeller planes. I don't know how people could do that. I'm sure It doesn't happen every time, but now I'm really scary to actually go on that plane.
[L]
[S] So, It was..