[S] Where were we before we were so rudely interrupted? Ah let's see
[S] Alright, I was gonna tell you. So my friend had moved.
[S] Or what's it called, my friend had moved away essentially [L] Uh-huh
[S] Ah.. and after I had some trouble coping with that
[S] Essentially, it took a while for me to kind of get back on my horse
[S] So I started to actually get really interested in music as kind of a coping mechanism
[S] Kind of, I got really excited about learning how to play and singing and stuff
[S] My, my parents, they wanted like a guitar or something [L] Hmm
[S] They really just treated this as a phase
[S] So they weren't   really too interested in like indulging me in that particular point in time
[S] But uh i did manage to nag them enough to at least get them to send me to kind of a..
[S] Particular like..
[S] When I was transferring from middle school to high school kind of
[S] I had to choose which high school I wanted to go to
[S] So I convinced them to go, let me go to this kind of music oriented like high school essentially
[L] Hmm [S] Ah.. so I kind of..
[S] Got them to do that as long as the school had like maths and chemistry
[S] And like real subjects alongside the weirder musical stuff right? [L] Hmm
[S] Ah cause then my parents were happy with that
[S] So.. I yeah I went to this school kind of, I really liked it there um
[S] I really enjoyed all the courses, it was very nice, the food was very good, a bit better than here
[S]  bit of a low bar but
[S] Um.. I really enjoyed it there, but there was one course I really didn't enjoy
[S] And that course was called classical music theory [L] Okay
[S] And the reason I didn't enjoy that course was cause there was this one particular teacher
[S] She was, I think she was like a demon in the shape of a human being
[L]  [S] Kind of wearing human skin, she was really bad
[S] And she really was very mean and she used to like pull students by the ears kind of [L] Hmm
[S] So it was like half abusive in some sense er..
[S] So that was really bad and I really hated her
[S] But I did actually meet some friends who also went to her classes
[S] Who also like we kind of united around hating this particular teacher
[S] So we used to hang out and talk about that quite a lot
[S] So that's a, there was a bonus there at least  [L] Yeah
[S] Um.. yeah, no, so..
[S] Yeah the school is really good and I enjoyed being there
[S] Except for the class cause being with, that one class was really hell
[S] And that class was very important, cause they actually needed for your exams
[S] So at the end of the first year I think of me being there
[S] We had to give this mandatory presentation essentially like [L] Uh-huh
[S] Uh.. in classical music theory
[S] And I was very scared cause I was still fairly introverted back in this time
[S] And I had to go in front of this teacher kind of
[S] In front of everyone and in front of this particular teacher who I was really afraid of uh [L] Oh god
[S] And so I practiced a lot and I made up slides
[S] And then kind of prepared the presentation and stuff uh
[S] Um when the day came, I did give the presentation, I was fairly happy with it
[S] People applauded, so I thought I did a good job
[S] But then after I was done, like the teacher really started ripping into my work
[S] Kind of she really started to dismantle everything I'd done
[S] And then she's no this is wrong, this is bad, why did you say this [L] Hmm
[S] And that really impacted my self confidence in some sense [L] Yeah
[S] Cause I was still very sensitive at the time so
[S] I really didn't  know what to do kind of
[S] So I went home and I told my parents about this
[S] And then we talked to the school about it, to see if we could do something
[S] Cause I really just can't deal with this teacher anymore, I can't have her for another two years
[S] Um so we talked about it with the school
[S] And they said no we can't really get rid of her, she's a very important person
[S] Kind of she's on a number of steering boards kind of
[S] So she kind of gets away with what she wants in some sense
[S] Um even though they had trouble with her before
[S] So the solution was essentially we came up with was
[S] Was unfortunately that I hate to kind of
[S] The school shared a lot of courses with the normal high school
[S] So I could transfer into the normal high school kind of and complete my courses there [L] Hmm okay
[S] Which was unfortunate for me kind of cause I'd be, also be leaving behind these friends I met kind of
[S] And stuff but at least like I got to avoid cause she was really just making my life miserable
[S] And my parents were also happy I went to a more technical school  [L]
[L] They won  [S] Yeah they won at the end  they always do
[S] Uh yeah but at the end of the day I did finally graduate from this more technical school kind of, I went to high school
[S] Uh after I'd been in high school, oh no not in high school, in college, sorry
[S] And after I'd been in college for a while, I did actually meet one of the friends I met at this music school
[S] Um and then we all got together and met up all of them again
[L] Hmm [S] And they said they were actually playing in a band
[S] Ah okay cool cool, and we were talking about it and like
[S] Hey don't you want to like join us and we can like play this? Like what, me?
[S]  I was like surprised like what they still wanna play with me
[S] Like after all this time, they remembered things
[S] Or remember me at all, so um..
[S] I said yeah we can try it out, so eventually like I joined as a vocalist kind of, cause I actually can sing
[S] Don't know if you knew  [L] Yeah, that's cool
[S] Uh so I joined with them uh we played kind of
[S] And eventually we arranged to have a concert for our like some friends, a couple of months down the line
[S] And it was a really great experience, like just singing that
[S] Er what's it called, no a concert. It was really great. [L] Hmm
[S] Like I really felt free, I felt like I was liberated kind of, it was really cool [L] Yeah
[L] That's cool [S] And that's kind of yeah my experience with music
[S] And the fact that I actually did sing in a band so  in the end