[S] hey hey how are you doing?
[L] nice nice I'm doing well thanks
[S] how was your weekend?
[S] yeah it was really good
[S] yeah?
[L] yeah
[S] I um in a trip I went to Norway
[L] ok...
[S] to Tromsø have you ever been there? Norway?
[L] no never
[S] never?
[L] perhaps someday
[S] it's really cold
[L] yeah?
[S] I visited a friend he's studying
[L] is it beautiful?
[S] Yeah I mean my friend or the city? yeah I think it's nice
[L]
[S] it's a nice city not a lot to do there
[S] Yeah I mean my friend or the city? yeah I think it's nice
[L]
[S] it's a nice city not a lot to do there
[S] so it's really cold and in winter gets you know
[S]
[L] start raining?
[S] all the time
[S] no not necessarily raining just felt again cold all the time
[L]
[L] uh-huh
[S] no not necessarily raining just felt again cold all the time
[S] but my friend is studying there so I just decided you know to
[S] just take a look around you know when you have friends studying abroad um.. yeah we just went around it's really expensive though so you know for a meal and a beer
[L] uh-huh
[S] you really pay a lot of like twenty euros or so so it's not great for students... it's not great for students um..
[L] wow
[L]
[S] you really pay a lot of like twenty euros or so so it's not great for students... it's not great for students um..
[L] better not travel no
[S] I mean he asked me if I ever tried this you know this smelly fish like fermented with salt which is supposed to be the smelliest food in the world
[S] you really pay a lot of like twenty euros or so so it's not great for students... it's not great for students um..
[S] have you ever heard of it
[L] no never
[S] well there's this kind of fish I forgot the name
[L] I'm trying to imagine
[L] uncooked fish?
[L] they call this like it's like yeah it's like a raw (harrowing?) like
[S] fermented with salt
[L] uh I know I know I know I know
[L]
[S] it's supposed to be super smelly and but my friend told me that although it smells really bad it tastes ok
[L] uh-huh
[S] I was like ok I don't believe you so we made a bet then we had you know  to buy it I mean it right
[L] I heard that's a kind of contest to check if you are brave enough like if you eat this kind of fish
[S] yeah I...
[S] only after that experience I checked some reaction videos on youtube to realize that it tastes really bad and I don't like fish in general you know even like cooked fish it's kinda I don't know I don't like it
[L] I heard that's a kind of contest to check if you are brave enough like if you eat this kind of fish
[L]
[S] only after that experience I checked some reaction videos on youtube to realize that it tastes really bad and I don't like fish in general you know even like cooked fish it's kinda I don't know I don't like it
[S] I prefer meat but yeah we just went to supermarket we got these cans they look like tuna cans like
[L] uh-huh
[S] only after that experience I checked some reaction videos on youtube to realize that it tastes really bad and I don't like fish in general you know even like cooked fish it's kinda I don't know I don't like it
[S] I prefer meat but yeah we just went to supermarket we got these cans they look like tuna cans like
[L] uh-huh
[S] you know something normal even the can looks a bit disgusting I don't know I have this feeling for this stuff I don't know whatever so we went there and well you're not supposed to eat this indoors
[L] uh... because of the smell?
[S] 'cause your house is gonna smell like hell um so yeah so they advise you to do this outdoors so we went to this small part uh
[L]
[L] a week or so
[S] 'cause your house is gonna smell like hell um so yeah so they advise you to do this outdoors so we went to this small part uh
[S] close to his place uh you know uh we went there and I was trying to prepare myself psychologically for this I had a bad feeling you know
[S] I could feel that something was like he just kept saying yeah doesn't matter the smell is strong but the taste is good I didn't believe him like from the real beginning and uh
[S] yeah and then we got there we just you know started to open this thing and wow the smell was wow I never smelled something so strong and you know this mix of raw fish
[S] salt whatever and also the look was disgusting 'cause it was this kinda of slices of fish this kind of water, oil, jello
[L] uh-huh
[S] something really disgusting um then I saw his face he was also like ew so then I knew that
[S] it was not going to taste good I knew it was like oh my god but anyway it was a bet.. it was a bet man you know
[L]
[S] just for the bet I wanted to win that bet so so yeah so now you know the hardest part
[S] it was not going to taste good I knew it was like oh my god but anyway it was a bet.. it was a bet man you know
[L] uh-huh
[S] just for the bet I wanted to win that bet so so yeah so now you know the hardest part
[S] you know we  was  but now you have to you know take that thing  you know this texture a bit gluey and oily and
[L] uh-huh
[S] oh my god I don't even wanna think about it so so yeah I wanted to give it a bite but I couldn't the first time the smell was so strong
[S] then I um looked at him and he was like literally crying you could see tears down from his eyes and he was like
[L]
[S]
[S] but yeah I was like uh...
[L]
[S] I just grabbed my nose like we just put it like a medicine you know trying to swallow it
[S] but I couldn't I just gave it one single bite and then it was too much you know it was kind of my whole body was rejecting that piece of fish
[L] uh-huh
[L] did you throw away?
[S] but I couldn't I just gave it one single bite and then it was too much you know it was kind of my whole body was rejecting that piece of fish
[S] I just threw yeah I just like you know I dropped the can with the fish and he was also trying to fake like hey it's not so bad but he also stopped
[S] but he kinda of won the bet 'cause he ate more than me so yeah so I'm gonna remember this weekend
[L] uh-huh
[S] in Norway forever because of this disgusting smelly fish
[S] but he kinda of won the bet 'cause he ate more than me so yeah so I'm gonna remember this weekend
[L] oh...
[S] in Norway forever because of this disgusting smelly fish