[L] Hey. [S] What's up?
[L] Nothing. [S]  cool cool cool
[S] Uh man I was thinking, remembering stuff this weekend, uh remembering my high school time
[S] Was so fucked up. So fucked up. You had good high school time here?
[L] Sure. [S] Yeah? Good memories and stuff?
[L] Yeah, mostly. [S] Okay, yeah. No, mine was weird, I..
[S] I was, I moved a lot from city to city then I end up in a   high school I moved, ended up in a school there.
[S] And was really, I could not connect with everyone, I was always kind of slept over.
[S] The teachers were ridiculously bad. Was so, so, so..
[S] You know these very old teachers who have no didactic at all
[S] Just sit and read stuff and expect you to learn shit
[S] And.. Yeah it was, was awful year, I learned nothing, I was really bad student
[S] Really, really, always, never failing, almost failing. Almost getting D, but was really, really bad, really really was
[S] Er but there is this one professor, one teacher who make things different. He was a history teacher.
[S] He really love his job, he really make it interesting. [L] Ah
[S] And.. I mean history, it's okay, there's a lot of numbers to memorize, a lot of dates. I was never good at it.
[S] But he made it interesting to start with, to get into and etc
[S] Uh but I still was not good enough, wasn't all too interesting to go to school
[S] I was really bad on it. And I did my first examination on this, on this course
[S] I fail miserably, it was the first time I fail, I failed completely
[S] And I was feeling okay-ish, like okay yeah failed, I can deal with that, no problem. [L] Ah
[S] Um.. but then he came talk to me this, this teacher, and he was such a nice guy, he was very cool guy..
[S] He was younger than a lot of professors, very, very fresh, very easy to talk
[S] And he know how to talk to people, I think he knew how to talk to teenagers. Was something different from the other teachers, yeah I mean this helps, this helps.
[S] And yeah the thing is, he came talk to me and.. asking yeah, what's wrong?
[S] Why you did, why you fail? You look so interested on the, in the the lecture and what happened? And..
[S] Was talking, talking, talking and we got um, get together. And I started to realize hmm actually this is not that bad and..
[S] I started to get into the things you know, and to.. [L] Uh-huh
[S] Not study, because I was not much study people, uh studying person
[S] But to, to pay attention on the lecture and, and so on
[S] But then came the second exam and I failed again
[S] And I was like oh what the fuck? What happened to me? I mean I really uh.. I like this story, I like this. What's wrong with me? And.. [L] Ah
[S] But then he came talk to me again and we had lots of conversations. And I was started feeling bad, you know. It was really, really
[S] Start to, to feel guilty because this guy was there and he was doing every thing to, to help me.
[S] And I was still not able to fulfill the, the yeah the best exam
[S] Then the third exam came, was the final exam
[S] And I had to pass this one so I had a chance to pass to, to pass to the course
[S] Otherwise I would fail the course and this was really, really bad. And I was staring to feel guilty already.
[S] Because of the, this relationship with this guy, right? And..
[S] I studied a bit. I was never good at studying, maybe that was my problem. I was never good at studying stuff.
[S] I studied a bit but.. uh during the day before the exam, I panicked
[S] I really, really, completely, completely went crazy. Saying yeah, I cannot do this shit, I really cannot do this exam, I'm really bad on this and..
[S] I start to make uh.. to get some papers and put names and dates on it and put on my sleeves [L] Ah
[S] So I would cheat in the exam, er this was my plan to pass it, right? It was bad but yeah. Teenager, hmm?
[S] And during the exam, I started doing the exam, and I start to get to, to get to the good answers of my, of my uh papers
[S] I started to feel so bad after getting to the end of the exam
[S] And I felt so, so guilty. I felt so.. ashamed that I had to do that to pass the exam, you know? [L] Ah
[S] In the end I did pass the exam and the, the teacher came to me and talked to me and talked to me. Hey, congratulations, this is really good.
[S] You did it. But inside I was so destroyed.
[S] Because I knew that I cheated, I knew that I made something so bad
[S] And I was feeling guilty for the first time in, in this concept of school [L] Ah
[S] It was really, really an awful, awful feeling. So it was really, really ridiculous and pushed me down a lot, really, really a lot.
[S] It was really, yeah. I caught me thinking this this weekend. [L] Yeah