[L] Hello [S] How are you?
[L] Fine, great, thanks for asking [S] Yeah, good, cool, cool, cool, yeah, sure
[L] And you? [S] I'm okay
[L] Nice [S] Yeah, yeah, I was, just something kept me up, I was thinking
[S] About something that happened in the past, I mean you.. how was your high school? you like it?
[L] Yes, I had a great time there, a lot of friends that I made [S] Yeah, was nice? Really?
[L] And I cultivated through my life, so nice [S] Yeah that's amazing
[S] Yeah really, I mean everyone I talk to it's really 50 50, some people really like it, some people really hate it
[S] They really had bad experiences there [L] Oh
[S] And for me I.. was a weird experience I.. I move in
[S] Uh in between so, in the second year of high school I started in a new school
[S] I don't know, I was the new guy, I was not knowing anyone before
[S] And was kind of left out of everything, was not connecting with anyone else, right? [L] Uh-huh
[S] And I was not the best student, I mean I was always the average guy
[S] Who always did the enough to pass and that's all, you know? [L] Uh-huh
[S] Er.. this together with this loneliness
[S] And the, the teachers on this school they were so bad, they were really
[S] These old people
[S] Not, not, not, that, not that because they're old but, they had this, this um
[S] Old didactic way that I am the teacher, I know everything, you shut up
[S] And.. but they don't have the didactic of how to pass this knowledge to people, you know?
[L] Like basically I speak and you listen [S] Exactly, something like that
[S] This was ridiculous, um never, never attracted in me, and that makes me I mean not doing so well
[S] But then everything changed when a new teacher arrived, and was a history teacher
[S] And he was super good, he was a young guy, very dynamic, very easy to talk and
[S] Then the history class became interesting. history was always boring to me, it was a lot of names, a lot of numbers to memorize [L]
[S] Dates and so on. And became interesting for me.
[S] So.. I thought I was okay with it, but I did the first test, the first exam, and I failed
[S] And it's like yeah wow, that's bad [L] Hmm
[S] And then he came talk to me, that never happened before, that a, a teacher come talk to me, you know, right?
[S] And he came talk to me and ask yeah what's happening? You're always there in my class, you're always paying attention
[S] And then we talked a lot and he helped me a lot, understanding what, what I was doing wrong, how I was studying wrong
[S] You know? And then went on, and I was getting more confident with it um..
[S] Until I had the second test, and I failed again [L]
[S] Er like wow, something really wrong, and then I start to feel bad, like really like wow how can I do that, I mean [L]
[L] Basically were you better with the old style teachers than this new stuff [L] Yeah but, I don't know maybe
[S] Maybe they didn't care enough, I don't know [L]
[S] But I was really feeling bad, and then I decided okay yeah, I will have to make it better for the final exam
[S] And then I start to study like crazy, really study, study, study. Really, really a lot.
[S] But.. by the last day before the exam I had heavy panic attacks
[S] I was really, really shaking, and really, really nervous
[S] And then.. I said yeah no, I cannot fail this exam, I mean
[S] It's my last exam, I have to pass it otherwise I fail the, the class
[S] Then I decide to create some, some stripes of papers with the names and dates on and
[S] Cheat on exam, you know? And this was the plan, an.. awful plan sure [L]
[S] And during the day of the exam, I was there and I used my, my cheat folds and [L]
[S] I actually pass the exam but when I hand in the test
[S] I was feeling so ashamed, I was feeling so bad, like I..
[S] I.. I don't know, I cheated on me
[S] And I break the trust that this teacher put on me, after he talked to me so, so, so much
[S] I was feeling so disgusted with myself, you know?
[S] In the end I pass the exam, and I pass the class
[S] But I carry this with me, this milestone of
[S] Wow that's really the low, lowest you can achieve, you know?
[S] Was really, really a bad, bad feeling
[S] And after that thing I mean, of course makes me a better person after that
[S] I really realized wow that's really not the direction I should go
[L] Did you tell to the teacher that you ? [S] No, I never told him, I was really feeling ashamed
[S] But.. yeah was really like, wow that's bad
[S] That's really bad, yeah [L] Uh-huh